No.
It's off-key.
I'm telling you, it's off-key.
Play it again.
Oh, God!
Let it be.
-Why are you nagging him?
-The piano's out of tune.
-Here.
-Play it, come on.
Take this. You are not well.
Get some rest, okay?
Saksham, it's quite late.
You should go home.
No, sit down.
But--
-He's not playing it correctly.
-Teach him how to play it tomorrow.
No, you mustn't stop until you learn
to play a musical instrument properly.
You must respect it.
Otherwise, the notes will be mad.
Even if you play one note incorrectly,
it'll affect the entire tune.
-Come on, play it--
-Do as you please!
You never listen to me!
You've turned the house into a junkyard!
And what's with this gigantic piano!
You're not well,
so I have to do all the cleaning!
Whatever!
Grandpa, I'll come tomorrow
and play the tune properly.
Its notes are out of tune.
It must be restrung.
-Okay, Grandpa. I'll restring it tomorrow.
-Okay.
-Good night.
-Good night, son.
-Good night, Grandma!
-Good night! Go home now!
Who wants to live here, anyway!
We're just stuck here.
He's obsessed with--
Damn music! What a pain in the neck!
Here we go! He won't give up.
What happened?
Did you fall?
What--
Hey, Saksham! Look what happened to him!
What happened to you?
-Saksham, look what happened to him!
-Grandpa!
-What happened to you?
Please, wake up!
It's right here.
-We're here.
-Take the suitcase.
Be careful.
Let's go.
-You remember what I had told you, right?
-Namaste.
You have got my ball, right?
I had told you to pack it.
Keep quiet!
Pankaj is the third brother.
-Isn't the other brother coming?
-The younger son must be on his way.
We've informed him.
Everyone's working now.
-Namaste, Auntie.
Pankaj is here.
Namaste, Uncle.
-Hello, Uncle.
-Hello.
How are you?
-God bless you.
-Come inside.
How are you, son? God bless you.
He's his son.
Namaste.
Dad is no more.
Come on. Give me a hug.
-I'll just go and talk to Mom.
-Sure.
He's gained weight.
-Are you talking about me?
-No, I'm talking about Pankaj.
-Oh.
-He's gained weight.
Yeah.
Brother-in-law has left us, son.
Let's go to that room. Put on your shoes.
-Here.
-Come on, let's go.
-Are you hungry?
-I'll get you something to eat.
He got lucky.
Come on, open it.
-Panditji, will this do?
-Yes.
-Okay, then.
-You should get it checked.
-I think, he's applied some powder.
-It's your old--
-What about the rest of the stuff?
-How many knots am I supposed to tie?
-Tell me!
-Three.
Pankaj… you should have
worn white clothes.
Never mind.
Hasn't Neetu come yet?
His flight got a bit delayed.
He'll get here by 4:00 p.m.
How did you get here?
-By bus.
-Yes!
-Train bookings were full…
-It's right there on top!
Let it be, I'll get it.
…because of the Christmas holidays.
Holiday or no holiday,
getting a train ticket is tough.
We came by taxi.
-By taxi.
-From so far?
Let's go.
They got here on time,
that's what matters.
-Uncle, namaste.
-God bless you.
When did you arrive?
I was the first one to arrive.
I set out…
as soon as your mother called.
Let's go. We have to buy some vegetables.
I knew you'd be late.
After all, she's my sister.
-Work is inevitable, right?
-Yes.
Uncle, it's good that you
came, otherwise--
Otherwise?
It would've been very difficult.
-Right.
-Uncle, you must be tired. Have a seat.
I haven't come here to sit, Gajraj.
There's so much work to be done.
We're here now, Uncle.
Please, get some rest.
What about Neetu? Where is he?
When is he coming?
I just told you his flight got delayed.
He'll be here soon.
-Yes.
-Is there only one flight from Mumbai?
His father just died.
Uncle… he knows that his father just died.
He'll be here soon.
You live nearby, in Raebareli,
-but he's coming from Mumbai.
-Someone, get me water!
-Can't you understand?
-Hey!
Who said--
-Brother-in-law, you're here!
-Please, come.
When did you arrive?
When? I've been sitting
here alone for hours.
I got here before you did.
Yeah, you got here about
seven minutes before me.
-I got here an hour before you.
-Did you hear him?
-We came together.
-You two came at the same time.
Yeah, but--
-Neetu is here.
-He's finally here.
-Hey, check it once just to be sure.
He's come alone.
-Namaste, Uncle Neetu.
-His wife didn't come with him.
Let me get that.
It doesn't matter. He's here.
Let him see his mother first.
-I don't want to do it.
-There's no other way, right?
-Let's go, then.
-Where's Mom?
Panditji, be quick.
Take your shoes off.
Look, your favorite son is here.
Control yourself.
Hey, console your mother.
-Please, control yourself.
-Calm down, Mom.
My son…
Laali, it's getting late.
-Yeah.
-We should go.
-Hurry up!
-Mom.
Dad is no more.
Come on, get up.
Wait. Wait for me.
-Uncle!
How can he just leave us like that?
-Ramprasad!
-Hey--
-Hey!
-Hey, careful!
-Make him sit down.
-Let me help.
Be careful.
-Why did he come here all the way?
-Does he ever listen?
-Why? Is he hard of hearing?
-No, I didn't mean that.
I want to see his face
for my last memory.
-He does as he pleases.
-Yes.
Oh, okay.
-Namaste.
-Get lost!
-Why are you scolding him?
-I knew the car didn't have enough petrol,
-but he said we'll push it if need be.
-And you brought him here.
Our elder aunt is also here.
She is inside.
-Is she still alive?
-Shut up.
-Panditji!
-Yes?
-Is everything ready?
-Yes.
-Shall we carry him?
-Yes, let's go.
-Uncle, wait a minute. I'll get Mom.
-Okay, go.
Go, get her here.
Mom… it's time.
Let's go.
Come.
"Lord Ram's name is the truth."
-How big is the house?
-It's huge!
Yes, it's huge!
We're a big family, after all.
We won't fit into a tiny house.
No more kids now.
-But I want more.
-Hey, let go of me! Let go!
Be quiet, all of you!
Listen! Come home early this evening!
We'll have dinner together!
I'll be waiting!
I'll be back soon, Savitri.
"Lord Ram's name is the truth."
CHADMAL CREMATORIUM
-How much does the wood cost?
-It's 400 rupees a ton.
-Really?
-Yes!
Back in our hometown,
we get it for 200 rupees.
You're right, brother.
Sir, it's the right price.
Who bargains at a crematorium?
What are you--
He's right.
They're waiting for the wood.
He wants 400 rupees a ton.
-What does it matter!
-Who sent him to get the wood!
-Go, Pankaj. Sort it out.
-I'll go.
-Uncle--
-Someone, handle him.
-What's our number?
-Lucky seven.
-Hurry up.
-He's saying it'd cost 400 rupees.
-The day's about to end. Come on.
-Be quick!
-Let's hurry up.
-Why are you bargaining?
Take the dry bits.
Otherwise, it'll take time.
-So what? Do you have to go somewhere?
-Let's go.
-You--
-Ignore him, Uncle. Let it be.
-What's he even saying!
-Come on, let's go.
It's time to say goodbye
Your soul is about to release
From your body
No one knows where you are going
No one will recognize your new face
You will leave behind
All ties and bonds
O traveler, you'll take the path
You must tread
It's time to say goodbye
Why must you depart?
Auntie, wait.
Hurry up. I have to take a shower.
Give me some sandalwood.
I need to massage it on my head.
-Go.
-I'm going to take a shower.
Dhaani, tell me something.
Where is Neetu's wife?
She never comes to family occasions.
But it's her father-in-law's funeral.
We'll ask Neetu whether
she's going to come or no.
Everyone is in mourning.
She is no different, right?
What will she do at home alone?
-Anyway, go and put the mattresses out.
-Sure.
I asked Saksham to play the piano.
He used to love listening to it.
Then, I said it was late
and that he should sleep.
-Then, I went to the kitchen.
-Auntie, are you okay?
Saksham was about to leave…
when he collapsed on the piano.
Oh, no!
I panicked, and I called Saksham.
I asked him to check what happened to him.
He came running, and then…
When your own family isn't around,
the outsiders come to your rescue.
True. Neighbors help you in these times.
Sister… don't lose heart.
Be brave, it'll be all right.
I'll make us some tea.
-Sorry, we're troubling you.
-No, not at all. Actually--
-Yes.
-Move the pillow.
I've asked them to get
some rotis, as well.
I'll get it right away.
She's feeling quite cold today.
Look, she's wearing a sweater
as well as a shawl.
I borrowed them from Mother-in-law
as soon as I got here.
-Oh!
-Father-in-law had given it to her…
-Really?
-on her birthday.
Wow!
He had great taste.
He'd given me a lovely pink sari
on Diwali this year.
He said, "You should wear bright colors.
They suit you."
He was the only one,
who used to get us gifts.
He knew our likes and dislikes.
He took care of us all.
He must've been very
romantic in his time.
Shut up. You're so cheeky.
How do you think he fathered
an army of six children?
Neetu.
Everyone's asleep.
Oh… sorry.
-All good?
-Yes.
Mom, go and lie down.
Yes. Go to sleep.
I'm not feeling sleepy.
If I feel sleepy, I'll lie down here.
Brother has already fallen asleep.
-You should go upstairs and sleep. Go.
-All right.
-Gajraj, sit here for a while.
-Okay.
Don't worry. We'll manage.
Mom, let me massage your feet.
Come on.
He really missed you. All of you.
We wanted to visit you more often,
but how could we? Work kept us busy.
Yes, Mom.
It's not like we didn't miss you and Dad.
Pratibha always talked about
what a nice person he was.
He had a very good heart…
but he was an extremely finicky eater.
No matter what you cook,
he'd always find faults in it.
What are you saying, Pratibha?
He always ate whatever I served him.
I used to argue with Mother-in-law,
but never with Father-in-law.
You know what he used to say to me?
He used to say,
"You're from an affluent family…
so there's a style in everything you do."
He rarely stayed with us.
Later, my husband got so busy
with his work in Ayodhya.
-Yeah, right.
-Oh, really?
I thought, you got fed up with
Mother-in-law's constant nagging.
I'll hit you!
I always wanted to stay here…
but Rahul had important exams then.
How's our brother-in-law, Gajraj?
Does he still drink himself to sleep?
No. He stopped drinking ages ago.
He still drinks.
-Listen, sister-in-law!
-Yes?
-Is our youngest sister-in-law…
coming?
-Where is she?
-I have no idea.
Was our late father-in-law
not up to her standards?
You two are nasty!
Be quiet.
Let's go out, or else, the daughters
of this house will bawl us out.
Yes, let's go. They're very dangerous.
-Sister, take the blanket.
-Let's go.
Everything else is fine, right?
Want a drink, Mom?
-Hey… I meant tea.
-All right.
-Do you want tea? We'll get it.
-We can't make it here.
Why not?
-Why can't we have tea? It's so cold.
-Yes, we want some.
We can have tea.
I'll ask Aunt Sheila to make it.
-Why trouble her?
-Why should we bother her?
Mom, can we make it here?
You're not supposed to cook
when in mourning…
but okay, go ahead.
-All right.
-If you're making it, I'll also have some.
-Let me make it then.
-Please, sit down.
Who wants tea?
-Me.
Make it for everyone, sister-in-law.
-Add some jaggery in it.
-Yes.
Remember how Dad used to love
having tea with jaggery?
If you're making it with jaggery,
I'll also have some.
Serve it in a steel glass.
Can you get me my cough syrup?
-Let's go.
-Where are you all going?
You're going to make tea,
not to exchange chitchat.
-Sushma!
-No, stay here. I'll make it.
-Yes, Mom?
-Use the vessel kept on the top shelf.
The cups are in the cupboard.
Be careful.
Okay, Mom. Will you have tea?
Yes.
-I'll be right back, sister-in-law.
-Go and get the cups.
When did you last see Dad?
Recently. We had come here
with the kids for Diwali.
Tell him, Mom.
I had planned to come, but I couldn't.
I had not come here since last one year.
I thought, we'd celebrate
the New Year's together.
That's what happened.
We just kept thinking…
while Mom was alone here.
She had got used to doing everything
on her own since we got married.
None of you came and stayed
here for a long period of time.
Sister, our kids have schools…
and we have jobs.
I know that, Pankaj, but don't your
kids ever get any holidays?
And what about Neetu?
He doesn't even have kids.
-Come on, sister!
-The interrogation's begun.
I know, we were wrong.
There it goes.
-Such a pain in the neck!
-What's with the blackout now?
-Who's this?
-Hey, what happened?
-Go to sleep, child.
-Careful, sister.
-Somebody, hold her hand.
-Dear, go and get a candle or a torch.
Brother, did you find our wire?
No, sir. All the wires
have been jumbled up.
Auntie, can you get the poha ready?
I'll come back and cook it.
All right.
Do you want me to peel any
other vegetables than potatoes?
Anything will do.
I'm just making poha.
Sister-in-law, give Sister Rani a towel.
Sure.
Also, can you please wake up the kids?
-All right.
-They need to take a shower. It's late.
Sister, please put the mattresses out
to dry! They're smelling really bad!
I'll do it right away.
-Give it to me.
-Okay.
-Listen! What shall we make for breakfast?
-I'm making poha.
Okay.
I end up doing all the housework here.
-Did you take a shower?
-Yes.
All right.
I'm going to wake up
your useless brothers.
Good morning, Uncle.
What is this, dear?
You're still making tea.
Have some, Uncle.
It's already so late.
No, I don't want it.
I'll have it.
Put it back!
Your brother-in-law
wants to take a shower.
-Give me the towel.
-Here.
-Has Gajraj woken up?
-Yes.
He has to attend the prayer meeting.
Panditji is on his way.
Gajraj must be ready before he gets here.
I've given him tea. That's all I know.
-Check if the others are ready!
-That's what I'm doing, sister!
What are you guys doing here?
Sister is hollering downstairs.
-Get ready, and go downstairs!
-We're going.
Hey, Sister Rani!
I can't go to the toilet without this.
Even if you have to go,
there's a long queue for it.
This family is full of jokers.
That's true.
Who's taking so long to come out?
Who else could it be!
Our uncle, who sits inside for an hour.
-Oh.
-I hope he controls himself.
How long are you staying?
I don't know.
What's the plan? I mean…
are you staying until the 13th day ritual
or just until the fourth day ritual?
I don't know what the elders have decided.
Anyway, I've told my colleagues
that my stay might get extended.
But I may have to leave soon.
Isn't Seema coming?
Is that all right?
You know her, right?
What did you tell the family?
I said that she's unwell…
and that she'll come when she gets better.
Good morning, Dad.
Mom will understand,
but sister makes a scene about everything.
She's doing it already.
-Come out.
-Kick the door open!
-Wait, he'll come out!
-Has he fainted in there?
Come out!
Go!
-Hurry up!
-Wait a minute.
-You're always late.
-What?
Must you lag behind
everyone wherever you go?
Hey, brother! Brother!
Help me wash my hands!
Go on, help him.
-Hold it down!
-I can't.
You're so weird.
-Uncle!
-Yes?
Are you constipated?
Yes. I ate something that
didn't suit my stomach.
You should've told me.
I would have given you a tablet.
I wanted it to go out
of my body naturally.
May he rest in peace.
-Look.
-Brother Manoj is here.
Check this out.
-Good.
-It's lovely.
-Namaste.
-Be careful.
It brings out my brother's personality.
Good.
Be careful.
Mom, Panditji was saying…
that he'll perform the ritual tomorrow.
We have to decide whether we want
a 13-day ritual…
or a four-day ritual.
My brother is dead
and you want to shortcut the ritual?
Brother,
Mom wants a 13-day ritual.
All right.
Let's do what she wants.
Ask him.
-Uncle…
-Yes, dear?
Manoj and I are going to Benaras
with Dad's ashes.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
-No, Gajraj. You cannot go anywhere.
-Why not?
You shaved your head for the ritual.
So, you cannot leave the house.
-Why not?
-Because--
-If he wants to go, he can go.
-What are you saying!
What? Is he supposed to help
the women with peeling the peas?
Peas? You had said we
should eat simple food.
-No--
-No, he doesn't mean that.
Don't get confused.
-You should all go. Enjoy the ride.
-Enjoy?
Is this some carnival?
-Everything's upside down in this house.
-You guys are impossible!
I agree.
Uncle, you're like a third umpire.
You tell us to eat simple food,
and then, you say something else.
-Then, you ask us all to go out.
-Listen--
We're talking about going out,
not about eating.
Let's go.
-Take my car.
-Yes, take our car.
But--
We'll get a taxi. It's okay.
Why? Vinod is telling us to take his car.
It's not Vinod's car. It's my car.
-Right.
-Vinod's just the driver.
Okay, then. You can drive from now onward.
Hey, are you crazy?
He just means that you drive the car,
so he's calling you the driver.
-Sit down.
-I was thinking I should also come.
-Uncle, can all four of us go?
-Yes, why not!
After all, we're a family. Take the car.
He said we can't eat green vegetables.
And now, he wants peas.
-Let it go.
-We were talking about the car, brother.
-About the car?
-Yes.
Boys… have you just woken up?
You're young.
Don't you go for a run in the morning?
Are we here to mourn or to run?
If you're here to mourn,
you should wake up early.
Grandpa, we slept late.
That's why, we couldn't wake up early.
I didn't sleep the whole
night, yet I am awake.
Why didn't you sleep, Uncle?
-Prakash's snoring kept me awake.
-What?
Mom, can we cook today at home?
Well, the daughters-in-law can't
cook today… but you daughters can.
-Namaste, sister.
-Namaste, Uncle.
Namaste, Uncle.
Go and take a shower!
-Will you have some tea?
-No, we just had some.
-How did it happen, sister?
-Keep quiet!
Hear the story.
He had his dinner.
Then, he asked Saksham
to play the piano.
He was listening to the music.
Then, I said, "It's late, go to sleep."
-Then, he--
-Mom, who is going to do the dishes?
-Munni will do it.
-Okay. She'll also make the khichdi then.
-Then--
-We'll need extra quilts and mattresses.
Hire them from the tent vendor.
Do you have his number?
It's in the diary.
Ask Aunt Sheila.
She'll give you his number. Go.
Go to Aunt Sheila's house,
and ask her for the tent vendor's number.
Munni? In a tent?
You're shameless!
-Just do what she said!
-Go, get the number. Be quick.
-Brother--
-He collapsed on the piano.
Who is it? Come in.
Namaste, Auntie.
-Who is it?
-I'm Samay.
-And I'm Rahul.
-Yes.
Oh… come! Sit down!
I didn't recognize you.
You're all grown up.
Bittu!
-Bittu, come here!
-Yes, Mom?
Look who's here.
-Hi.
Get them something to eat.
What will you have? Tea or a cold drink?
No, we're not staying. We need Munni's
number. It gets very cold at night.
He wants the tent vendor's number,
so that he can do the dishes.
What are you saying?
You mean, you need Munni's number
so she can do the dishes.
And the vendor's number to hire
quilts and mattresses, right?
-Right.
-That's what we said.
Oh, okay. Don't worry.
Bittu will go with you.
Sure, I'll come with you.
There's no need. We'll go on our own.
If it's nearby, we all can go.
We've come here after so long,
we might not remember the way.
Bittu will go with you.
Here we are!
Auntie Munni, come to the music
teacher's house from tomorrow.
Mom has called you.
Brother, come to the music
teacher's house tomorrow.
Isn't he dead?
That's why, we're calling you.
Don't forget.
All right.
Where are we going now?
-I'll drop you off at home.
-Let's ride around Lucknow.
No, everyone must be waiting.
Oh, shut up. We'll go home eventually.
Let's go for a spin before that.
-Is that a problem for you, Bittu?
-Let's go.
-You'll get us thrashed.
-Stop worrying!
A faraway wind makes my heart soar
Why do I like the words you speak?
Why does everything feel different?
We don't know.
-We don't see it that often.
-This is our uncle.
Where were you?
-We had gone to see Munni.
-What?
I meant, we had gone to see the vendor.
You're going to get
thrashed very badly, got it?
-Why?
-I'll tell you before I thrash you.
Get lost! Wash your face!
Go on, get lost!
Send your uncle here!
Here they are! Why are you so late?
Just look at you!
Were you swimming in dust?
You'd only sent us to the tent vendor.
-Yes, but you're late!
-So what?
He's so insolent!
It's getting late. Hurry up.
The indicator's not working.
Put your hand out.
I've been driving this car
since before you were born.
Let's go!
Make sure you do everything properly.
-Hey, Brother Pankaj…
-Why don't you go?
everyone's waiting for you in the car!
-Yes, I'm coming. Wait for me.
-Let's go.
How should I get in?
-Right there.
-All right.
-Where are you going?
-Brother!
Let's go. Are you planning
to stay here tonight?
I taught you how to drive.
-Why are you driving so slowly?
-Sorry, brother.
Yes?
So, when will you get here?
Okay. I'll let them know.
What happened?
The car broke down. They won't be
back before tomorrow afternoon.
-Oh, no!
-What a nuisance!
I knew this would happen.
That car's a wreck.
Where will they stay tonight? Now,
we have one more thing to worry about.
Brother…
you started smoking when
you were young, right?
Yes! I remember, I was very young…
and when I first saw him smoke,
I got scared.
-Oh.
-I thought, his mouth was on fire.
-He's got thrashed many times.
-Yes.
How, brother?
Nothing. I was just puffing away…
when someone came from behind
and said, "Give me a light."
I turned back, and it was Dad.
I got whacked on the spot.
No, I'm not talking about that story.
Once, he had talked back to Dad.
He said, "Why are you scolding me?
I've seen you and Mom sleeping naked."
Say what you want, but I'm the eldest.
-Of course!
-You're all like my children.
I've seen Mom and Dad very closely.
Often, I have seen them naked.
-Not once, several times!
-Brother, let's call it a night.
No matter how much our father--
Don't make such a racket!
The others are sleeping.
-Yes.
-Sorry, brother.
Sorry.
-Speak softly.
-Dad was a great man…
but what did he do for us?
Nothing. Music was all he cared about.
And our mother…
she's a very cunning lady.
She turned our dad against me,
and had me thrashed.
-Enough, brother.
-Neetu, let him speak.
A man shouldn't keep things bottled up.
It causes heartache.
We're talking so openly
to each other for the first time.
Look at me.
Brother Gajraj,
whatever I've tried to do until now…
has always failed miserably.
-Pour me another.
-Look at me.
It's been tough for me to make ends meet,
but have any of you…
ever asked me, "Manoj,
are you able to manage everything?"
When I was born,
I was considered the lucky one.
Remember, you used to say…
"His birth has brought us luck.
We own a shop now.
He's lucky, he's very lucky."
The shop…
Dad said that shop was his dream.
My shop's the real deal.
My in-laws helped me run it.
I respect them because they respect me.
My in-laws are useless.
No, our parents were useless. Right?
They kept complaining
that we never visit them.
But tell me something, did they
ever step foot outside their home?
Neetu, you're doing fine.
You're the youngest.
You're everyone's favorite.
You always do whatever you want.
-Maybe.
-Your wife listens to you.
You even have dimples.
And you…
you used to sing really well, dear.
-Why did you stop singing?
-Right. You're the best singer in Lucknow.
-Yes!
-Sing us a song.
-No, brother--
-Go on, sing for us. We rarely meet.
I've stopped singing.
Sing us a song, or else, I'll do it.
What was the song that Dad used to sing?
"I will take you around the world."
-Yes.
-What was its tune?
I know.
He used to count to four.
Yes, I remember.
There's an unfinished task
That I want you to finish
Today, I'll explain to you
What life is all about
It's a beautiful, deep secret
I'll tell you all about it
Do you see that village far ahead?
Today, I'll give you a tour of it
The darkness of the night
Descends on time
What you hold in your hand
Is all you'll take with you
On days like these
I will teach you how to walk
There's an unfinished task
That I want you to finish
I will make you sit by my side
And explain the tune to you
-All together!
It's like a drop of water
Granny used to say
"Let me hear you sing!"
Tell me the story
Of the king and the queen again
Let me hear it again
Grandpa used to say
"Take me for a ride
On the rocking horse!"
Do you see that village far ahead?
Give us a tour of it today
Tell us the story
Again today
Give me those blue marbles
Of memories again
Let me fly that kite
Of my childhood again
Make me finish the unfinished task
That you wanted me to finish
Make us finish the unfinished task
That you wanted us to finish
I have diabetes. I don't want tea.
Namaste.
-Namaste.
That's my uncle and aunt.
Sister…
I hope she doesn't ask,
"How did it happen?"
…how did it happen?
He had his dinner.
Then, he asked Saksham to play the piano.
You'll get us killed.
Hey, what happened?
You guys are shameless!
I'm not making fun of anyone.
Poor Grandma repeats
the same thing again and again.
What choice does she have?
Everyone who comes here
asks her the same question.
What else can they ask
in these circumstances?
We should print a leaflet with
details of how Grandpa died.
"This is what happened,
this is how it happened."
Sister Paakhi, today is Sunday.
There comes a cartoon film on
TV on Sunday. Can we watch it?
No, we can't put on the TV in this house.
But we can watch it in
the neighbor's house.
-At Bittu's.
-Oh, really?
The kids won't be able to enjoy it alone.
So, we should also go with them.
-Right! Let's go!
-Get a permission from the elders first.
Forget them! They'll say no.
-Let's go.
-They'll make a scene.
You're going to get in trouble, anyway.
Aren't you supposed to go to the airport?
Instead of doing that,
you're busy in chitchat!
You're doomed!
-Oh, no!
-Aunt Seema is coming! Let's go!
Let's go quickly.
-Hey, watch where you're going!
-Oh, sorry!
-Such insolent boys!
-Hey, let's go!
Hey, please don't mind. They're just kids.
Tell Nishant not to worry.
It's okay even if his in-laws don't come.
-Everyone else is here.
-All right.
-Why aren't they coming?
-They're big shots.
Bigger than me?
-Not agewise, Auntie. Statuswise.
-Are they so educated?
Auntie, listen to the devotional song.
-Pankaj, Neetu, come over here.
-Yes.
Wait a minute.
Panditji! We're supposed to write
just five letters, right?
-Yes.
-No one writes letters anymore.
It's the era of SMS.
Even if it's an SMS,
you have to type it.
Read its content.
Brother-in-law, come forward.
-Help us compose the message.
-I'm all ears. Go on.
Hey, come on! Help them!
-Brother Manoj, read it out.
-Yes.
"We deeply regret to inform
you that our father…
Mr. Ramprasad Bhargava
passed away on 19th December.
The final day of mourning
is on 1st January--"
-What… 1st January?
-There he goes.
-No one will come on 1st January.
-Why not?
Brother Gajraj is right.
-Let's keep it on 2nd January.
-What?
-We can even keep it on 31st December.
-How can we do that?
-That won't make it 13 days.
-Everyone parties on 31st December.
We can't start others' new year
with the 13th day ritual, right?
Are we supposed to consider
their happiness or our grief?
What's the problem?
Keep it on the tenth day.
Those who love you,
will definitely come.
-What!
-That's nonsense.
According to you,
I always talk nonsense.
-Yes--
-You think I'm a fool!
When you were in school, you had revised
geography chapters for a history test.
-You had messed up the entire test.
-What about you?
For the home economics class,
she had to do some cooking.
Instead of adding salt,
she added soda and ruined everything.
It was delicious!
-Come to the point.
-Wait. Leave the space for the date blank.
-We'll decide it later.
-Why later, Gajraj? Let's decide now.
But sister--
-Panditji.
-Tell him.
-Make it 1st January.
-As you please.
-It's settled.
-But--
What do you mean?
Think about it. Once the date is
fixed, it can't be changed.
-Do as Manoj says. He's an elder.
-Have you lost it? I'm the eldest!
Calm down. Why are you making a scene?
Don't you know the sequence
of the alphabets? "M" comes after "G."
Mr. Prakash…
every family follows its own rituals.
Mr. Ramprasad was a great believer in
tradition. He was your father-in-law.
Is this how you discuss his rituals?
What are we doing wrong, Uncle?
We're following the tradition.
Is this the way to talk to me?
Uncle is right.
Let's do it the way he's suggesting.
-Don't do it my way!
-We will do it your way.
You'll have to tolerate me
until my sister is alive!
-We can part ways later!
-Uncle, come with me.
No, listen to me…
No one understands a thing here!
Brother, listen to me!
-What happened?
-Brother Gajraj!
Aunt Seema is here!
Uncle, Auntie has arrived!
-Namaste, Auntie!
-Tear an end of the letter
before sending it.
-Should I tear it?
-Yes.
All right.
Auntie, give it to me.
She is an actress.
Just tear the corners of the letters.
-Mom, isn't she an actress?
-The corners… yes!
Hi, Seema! Seema's here!
-After that, just post them!
-Seema!
-How are you, Seema?
-How are you?
-I am so glad you came.
-Finally, you're here.
Is she the youngest daughter-in-law?
She's rude!
She didn't pay her respects!
Never mind, Auntie.
You mustn't stop until you learn
to play a musical instrument properly.
You must respect it.
Mom.
What's wrong, Mom?
Are you missing Dad?
Everyone's sleeping.
Let's go to the courtyard and talk.
Come.
Mom, did anyone hurt you?
They're all crazy.
Don't pay attention to them.
What happened? Tell me.
I don't understand, Dhaani.
I wanted us all to live together.
All my children,
daughters-in-law and grandchildren.
And now that we're together…
I am feeling so lonely.
Mom…
You're going to stay here
until the 13th day, right?
Yes, Mom. We're going to be here.
Whom are you going to stay with now?
Have you decided?
Mom, you can't live here alone.
Tell me something.
Is everything okay
between Nishant and Seema?
Speak softly. She's here.
Is there any problem
between Nishant and Seema?
Looks like it.
She seems distant.
She never got along with us.
Never mind, Mom.
It has always been like that.
She moved to Mumbai to become an actress.
Did she make it? No.
Have you ever seen her on TV?
Or in a film? No.
She lives off her brother's fame.
Her brother's nice.
Nice? He's an actor.
He's good at pretending.
Never mind.
Let's go inside. It's getting cold.
-Let's go.
-Come on.
-Yeah.
-You go ahead. I'll go to the washroom.
-Careful.
Careful.
-Let's go down this way.
-Why this way?
-Dad had fallen down these stairs twice.
-Yes, I remember.
-Nothing had happened to him then.
-Watch your step, brother.
-Careful!
-This long dhoti…
Why are you getting down backward?
This is how you go downstairs…
-if you're wearing a dhoti.
-Careful.
-Did you see how smoothly I came down?
-Yes, awesome!
-Speak softly, you'll wake up Mom.
-Oh, right.
-Let's go.
Hey, this way.
-Where's Neetu? I didn't see him today.
-That's because Seema is here now.
I see!
-He must be busy.
-Speak softly, or else, Mom will wake up.
-We won't tell anyone.
-Keep quiet. Everyone's asleep.
-Let's go.
Sister, look. They match perfectly.
Let's go inside.
-How is it?
-The ghee you've ordered is perfect.
-After all, it's my choice.
-The laddoos smell delicious.
The kachoris should
also be fried in ghee.
-Right.
-What is it, Uncle?
-Are the kachoris ready?
-Don't worry, they're frying them.
No, I am not worrying.
Just add some pulses into them.
Don't worry. You'll love it.
Why are you discussing all this here?
Is this a funeral or a wedding?
The food needs to be simple.
Make it bland, then.
-You twist everything I say.
-No, I know it's for the 13th day ritual,
but people must like it.
The food must be tasty.
The rice is full of stones.
Let me make the tea.
The tea's ready.
Make some for yourself if you want.
I can't make tea without
milk the way you do.
I'll make it later.
Let me serve it.
-Why is she so keen on helping today?
-There are guests, that's why.
She wants to show off her talent.
She's an actress, after all.
You're wicked.
Sister-in-law,
can you please pass the water jug?
-It must be there.
-I just filled it.
Thank you.
I wanted to talk to you about something.
Mom was weeping last night.
She must be missing Dad.
Yes… she's the only one who misses him.
I think we don't miss him.
What are you saying?
You're taking this the wrong way.
-We were just laughing--
-No, that's okay.
I'm talking about what I'm seeing
in this house.
What do you mean?
Speak more clearly.
The truth is that
Mom cannot live here alone.
So, let's decide whether you'll stay here
or take her along with you.
How can we decide that?
Mom should tell us what she wants to do.
Mom won't be able to do that.
I'll be right back.
How could she say that!
It's between Mom and her sons, right?
Who are we to decide?
You're right.
Who wants to open a Pandora's box, anyway!
The Pandora's box has been opened!
-It's gone.
-Hey, Auntie!
Seema!
Seema.
-What happened?
-Nothing.
Then, why did you walk away from there?
-Did we say something wrong?
-No.
Then, what happened?
If you don't like me, be honest…
but don't make fun of me.
-Who was making fun of you?
-Am I a child? Can't I tell?
You're always gossiping about me!
Are you crazy? We don't gossip about
you at all. Dhaani was scolding us.
-That's why, we kept quiet.
-Why are you lying?
When I was serving tea, you were
smirking as though I am an outsider.
Seema--
I'm trying to fit in,
but no one really wants me to do that.
Speak softly.
Look! When Father-in-law was sick,
I told Nishant to send him some money.
I thought you all have responsibilities,
so you won't be able to help.
-Look, Seema--
-It was not that easy for us either…
but we helped.
Did anyone thank me for that?
Look, this isn't the right
time for this talk.
Whenever you need money,
you think of us.
Hey, what are you saying?
Who begged you for money?
I agree, we once took 25,000 rupees
from you for Rahul's school admission…
but we returned it!
You returned it, but Brother Pankaj
swallowed 50,000 from us!
I don't know about that!
That's between you two.
We've cleared our debts.
Yeah, right.
Do as you please, but keep me out of it!
I'm already worried.
Go and take a shower, or do you want
to remain filthy like your father?
Look, I've been facing some financial
difficulties since past four years.
So, I thought the rent from Dad's shop
might help.
He always said I was lucky for the shop…
but he got sick,
so I couldn't say anything.
-Calm down.
-Why? Do you think I'm drunk?
Yes, you are drunk.
I'm not drunk, Brother Manoj.
I'm hurt. That's it.
I've been humiliated in front of everyone
for mere 50,000 rupees.
Brother Pankaj,
no one has humiliated you.
I don't even know about all this.
Sit down.
-Let's call Seema, and ask her.
-Forget it.
Speak softly.
They can hear you downstairs.
People enjoy conflicts, anyway.
Don't add fuel to the fire.
Who's adding fuel to the fire?
-Are you talking to me?
-Speak softly, brother.
Tell me something…
who brought up this topic?
Seema.
She said it to my face.
No one cares for anyone here.
I didn't say a word because…
I'm neither the youngest nor the eldest.
I was born as the middle
child, by mistake.
Me, too.
Eldest sibling gives advice…
while the youngest sibling gets pampered.
What about me?
I'm just stuck in the middle.
I am useless!
-Why are you--
-They tease me saying that…
I belong to my wife's family now.
-Let him say it!
-Yes, I belong to my wife's family.
Don't think like that.
Keep it down.
-Uncle, let's go downstairs.
-Let's go.
We'll just clean this, and join you.
Did he urinate here?
-I'll clean it.
-Should I help you?
Seema, can you serve the tea?
Here.
Who wants to handle her mood
swings, anyway!
Forget it now, Seema!
Just remember why you're here!
We can sort the grievances later.
We won't meet again anytime soon.
Mom is going to live a long life.
What did she say?
Keep quiet.
People get what they deserve.
Why talk like that about Mom?
Why? It's not like Mom's an angel.
She cursed Dad all her life.
Then, why is she grieving now?
-Don't say that.
-Don't we fight with our husbands?
What are you saying?
Of course, you'll defend Mom.
You always got what you wanted, after all.
-Sister--
-Everyone turned a blind eye toward me.
It's not the time to discuss all this.
I was so young when it all happened.
-I don't even remember.
-Yeah, right. I grew up too soon.
I was 16 years old. I wasn't allowed
to study or train for any job.
They just married me off.
She's right.
Yes, but things were different then.
No one knew your husband
didn't have a steady job.
They knew. Mom knew everything.
She just wanted
to get rid of us, one by one.
Speak softly.
If Mom overhears us, how would she feel?
Whether you agree or not,
your husband loves you a lot.
Love, my foot!
He lied about his job, so obviously,
he'd pretend that he loves me.
I've always had to entreat my
parents to fulfill my wishes.
It's okay to ask for help from our family.
No, Pratibha!
I got an earful about it in return!
What was I supposed to do?
Whom should I have asked for help?
Tell me, has anyone ever respected
my husband in this house?
Whatever may be the occasion,
he's made to work the hardest.
But that didn't make any difference!
They still complained about him!
Sister, no one's complaining.
Don't say this.
Everyone respects him.
Forget it!
I see how everyone respects him!
Everyone's always in a bad mood.
Move!
She always enters at the right time.
Please, come.
Sister-in-law, this is Mr. Awasthi.
He works at your bank.
I was very sad to hear…
about your husband.
After all, no one can interfere
with the God's will.
This isn't the right time…
but I have to say this. A few years ago,
your husband had taken a loan.
Initially, the monthly
installments were paid on time…
but then, they stopped.
The bank even served him a notice.
Now that the interest
rate is going to increase,
the repayments will also be higher.
There's enough money in
his account for this month.
You two have a joint account,
so I'll need your signature.
I don't understand all this.
-Can you please talk to my son, Manoj?
-Sure, I had met him once.
-What's the amount of loan?
-Well--
Wait! Sir, let's talk outside.
Uncle, I also need
a loan for a motorcycle.
Shut up.
Please, come.
Brother Gajraj,
Dad took a loan of a million rupees!
He only returned three lakhs.
Seven lakhs are still remaining.
-Eight, not seven.
-How?
Interest of a lakh rupees.
-Oh, no--
-He also mortgaged the shop.
-What are you saying?
-Yes, I'm telling the truth.
But what did he need this loan for?
We all must discuss this. Not just
us brothers, but our sisters as well.
He might have taken the loan for them.
I had also borrowed money from
him, but I returned it immediately.
Well, we all have borrowed
money from Dad at some point.
I haven't.
You have no responsibilities.
-Stop it!
-What?
As if you have heaps of responsibilities.
-Of course, I have responsibilities.
-You take money from your in-laws.
Responsibilities, my foot!
-I'll talk to Mom.
-Let's do it right now.
Now? She must be asleep.
Too many people visit us during the day.
On top of that, our uncle keeps
poking his nose in our business.
You rascal!
You're always picking on him.
-You've pampered him too much. Let's go.
-You're going too far.
Let's go.
-Where is he going now?
-Dad had fallen down these stairs twice.
-Let's go down from that side.
-Come.
Come. Walk straight.
What is it?
-Dhaani, is Mom asleep?
-Yes.
-Wake her up. We want to talk to her.
-She's asleep.
-Switch on the lights.
-Why are you--
What's happening?
Mom.
Sit down.
-Everyone's here.
-What's wrong?
-Nothing.
-What is it?
What happened?
Tell me.
Mom… we wanted to know why
Dad took such a big loan.
I mean… why did he need so much money?
Tell them, Mom, why he needed the money.
They'd never come to discuss
anything with you before today.
What!
Now that they found out about the loan,
they're all over you.
Go ahead, blame me.
I've always been
the needy one in this family.
-Sister, we're not talking about you.
-Why are you--
Are you talking about me then?
-Be quiet, Uncle's asleep.
-Don't start now.
Dhaani… get me Dad's diary.
-His diary?
-Yes.
Yes, that's the one.
What's in it, Mom?
Here.
Yes, that's Dad's diary.
Had he taken any more loans?
-He must have mentioned why he took it.
-What's written in there, brother?
FINAL TALLIES
The tallies.
-What?
-Read it.
"On 23rd June 2013,
I gave 125,000 to Manoj."
-Yes, but we'd returned it.
-We had returned it.
-You'd returned 75,000.
-Did you hear that?
Only 75,000?
"On 4th June 2013,
I gave 35,000 to Rani's husband."
We didn't even ask for it.
Mom forced it on us.
Sister, I'm just reading what's
written here. No one's blaming you.
"On 5th July 2013, I had given them
30,000. They haven't returned it."
"Once, I gave 20,000 to Gajraj.
He returned it."
-That's what he's written.
-We had returned all of it.
What about 50,000--
-"Pankaj took 75,000."
-We'd returned it.
"In 2013, 50,000.
In 2014, another 75,000."
But we had returned all of it.
-Oh, you returned it.
-How much did you return?
I guess, 30,000.
You've returned just 60,000.
You'd borrowed 25,000
for your brother-in-law's
-daughter's wedding.
-Mom, where are you going?
-Why would I do that?
-It's all written here.
Tell me if you need anything.
-What is all this?
-What's your problem?
Saksham was about
to leave, and right then…
he collapsed on the piano.
I called Saksham.
I was so scared.
I asked him to see what had happened.
He just left us.
Grandma, why are you crying?
Come here, dear.
-Please, have something.
-I don't want to eat!
I've been eating this bland
food for five days now!
-Here.
-It's tasteless! How can I eat it!
-Auntie, take this.
-I don't want to eat!
-Grandma…
-She doesn't want to eat.
put your dentures in.
I'll order a pizza for you.
Go to hell!
Even if we manage to save 100,000
each, it still won't be enough.
From where we're supposed
to get even 100,000?
We barely cover our monthly expenses.
How are you dividing the loan, brother?
Everyone must return what they owe.
What about the interest?
We need to pay that as well.
Okay, then.
Let's sell the shop.
Why are you after the shop?
Anyway, we can't sell it.
It's been mortgaged.
Brother, if we keep the shop, it'll
be of some use in such times of need.
You should've let me run it.
I would've made it work.
-Yes, but--
-You simply mortgaged it.
As if you could have made it work!
Let's sell the house, then.
The house?
-Which house? This one?
-Here's tea.
Put it down.
Why did you sit down?
You'd better go.
What will I do downstairs?
-They're quarreling.
-Who's quarreling?
Well… there's only one
conflict in this house.
-Okay.
-I'm better than you all.
You think I'm bad because
I cut ties with the family…
-but I didn't land the family in debt.
-Seema, keep quiet!
What's wrong with you? You're
always creating trouble! Enough now!
If you can't be polite,
then at least, stop fighting.
Brother Neetu, please go. We'll handle it.
-Don't get involved in their quarrels.
-Come on, go.
-It's late. You should sleep.
-Right.
Drop it.
Let's go.
Seema, don't make a scene.
There are guests here.
Don't shame the family.
We'll talk when they leave.
Why? Are you scared of the outsiders?
Tell me.
Carry on with your charade later.
Tell me, who's really bothered
about Dad's loan?
You're just worried about saving
your own money.
Don't even get me started.
I can say the same thing, Seema!
If I started talking, you'd be in trouble.
-What have I done?
-Drop it. Don't act so innocent.
As if you don't know what
happened to Brother Neetu.
Let it be. Everyone knows
why Brother Neetu had to get a job.
-He loves children so much, and you--
-Sister-in-law.
They'll have children soon.
They've only been married for six years.
-Exactly.
-He had to leave this house…
because she wanted to be an actress.
Look what happened to the most
loved son of this family.
Forget it.
Seema, I'd suggest you move
into the room upstairs.
It's for the best.
How is she going to manage alone?
What now?
I want to go back to Mumbai.
I looked for the tickets…
but all the flights are booked
because of the New Year's Eve.
There's a flight on 2nd January.
If we stay here until then,
we'll be here for the 13th day ritual.
I feel suffocated here, Nishant.
Want some?
No.
Seema… the situation
is quite tense right now.
Manage for a few more days, please.
If you want,
you can sleep in the room upstairs.
You don't need to come down.
I'll make them understand.
Will they understand?
Nishant, don't you think
we've tried enough to fit in?
But they're just--
They ask us for money when they need
it, and humiliate us otherwise.
-How is that okay?
-What choice do we have?
There's been a death in the family.
This is not the time to argue.
I'm not asking you to argue with them.
Just tell them to accept the truth.
Which truth, Seema?
Who accepts the truth?
You talk about others.
Do you have the guts
to accept your own truth?
What truth are you talking about?
-You're also blaming me just like them!
-Drop it, Seema.
Pack your things.
I'll find you a hotel tomorrow.
Nishant, wait a minute. Just hear me out.
Auntie?
Auntie.
Hey!
Why are you crying?
It's nothing, Rahul. Don't talk to me.
I'm a bad person.
-Why are you talking like this-- Wait!
-I'm going.
-Where are you going?
-Mumbai.
Mumbai? Wait a minute, Auntie!
-No one likes me here.
-I do. Anyway, let me open it for you.
There.
So, you like me.
Yes… I like you.
You're my aunt, after all--
Not in that way.
You like me as in you "like me."
What?
-No?
-No. Why are you saying this?
Another lie. You're also lying.
If you like me, then say it!
Whom are you scared of?
-I'll talk to them.
-Auntie! Please, wait!
-Let go.
-Yes.
Sit down.
The thing is…
all your uncles and aunts…
keep lying to each other.
They don't like each other.
Your grandma doesn't like them either.
She dislikes me the most.
Never mind.
But they're our blood relatives,
so we must respect them. Right?
I was an outsider, who was expected
to please everyone in the family.
I couldn't do that,
so they labeled me as a "bad" person.
-Am I boring you?
-No.
No, why would you bore me!
Okay… you better go.
-It's very late.
-Yeah.
-Let me take this.
-Go, Rahul. You must sleep.
-Yes. You should also sleep.
-Yes.
-Okay, good night.
-Good night, Auntie.
-I'll lie down.
-Sure.
Don't tell anyone about this.
-No, I won't.
-Good.
Who is it?
Oh, no! Today's the 31st.
No one remembered.
-What?
-It's the New Year's Eve.
As if we were celebrating it.
I'm not talking about that. We forgot
that it was Mom's birthday yesterday.
-Oh, yes!
-Oh, yes! I completely forgot!
You started your chitchat again!
You're always talking!
Sister Rani, we were just wondering…
how old is Mom?
Must be about 60 or 62.
-Her hair's still black. How is that?
-What?
So, Dad was younger than Mom!
Are you crazy?
If Dad was 60 years old,
then how could Mom be 62 years old?
Who told you that?
There was a gap of 12 years between them.
Then, how old is Mom?
I was born when she was 16 or 17.
You're 54 now.
I'm only 53.
-You're still very young, then!
-She's so insolent.
-What is it? Tell me!
-What happened to you, brother-in-law?
I didn't like the tea.
Oh, no. Here. Sister, have tea.
Shall we leave?
-How long are you going to sit here?
-How could I forget that she's my aunt?
How am I supposed to face her now?
Forget about it. I was the only one who
saw you. I doubt, she'll tell anyone.
She has a bad character, I'm telling you.
I always knew it.
She is good at heart.
She's not like the other aunts.
-Do you mean my mother?
-That's not what I meant.
I mean, she's not the person
you think she is.
Seema is very pure.
Did you smoke hash this morning?
She's our aunt.
Don't think about falling for her.
Sometimes, I feel like hugging her
and showering her with love.
-Are you crazy--
-Whom do you want to hug?
This one.
What's going on?
Brother Samay, let's go home.
Let's leave the two lovebirds alone.
Let's go!
-Take your hands off me!
-You're looking beautiful.
-All right, calm down.
-Hey, why do you misunderstand me?
The tea is ready. You can have it.
Hope it doesn't get cold.
You are funny!
Seema, come! Will you have some tea?
-Sure, I'll make it.
-The tea is ready. Here you go.
Check if there's enough sugar.
We have added very little sugar in it.
Sister-in-law, can you please pass me
the biscuits? Auntie is feeling dizzy.
-What happened?
-Relax. Sit down.
-Be careful!
-Have a seat.
-Have some water.
-Yes. Give it to me.
You'll feel better in no time.
And what about--
Seema, you woke up late today.
Yes, I had a headache.
Take care of yourself.
It's so cold and your room
is on the terrace.
-Yes.
-Nishant slept downstairs with Mom.
-Oh, really?
-Check if the stove is vacant.
Make some ginger tea.
-Yes.
-Sure.
-I'll make it.
-Do you know how to make tea?
Auntie, Seema cooks really well.
Really? How would I know?
I've never tasted her food.
My husband's been unwell
since he got up today.
-What's wrong?
-The usual.
-Oh, you mean cold?
-Yeah, it's freezing outside.
Right.
Listen, add some black pepper to the tea.
-All right.
-And some cinnamon, as well.
Also, add a few tulsi leaves
and ginger powder.
-Should we also fry it with cumin?
-You're so cheeky.
Auntie, you carry on. I'll get the tea.
All right.
-Will you manage, or should I help?
-Be careful.
Are you staying, Seema?
Yes.
Good. Otherwise,
things would have gotten worse.
I hope, you're not mad at me.
No, sister-in-law.
She's moody.
-Give me the newspaper.
-Yes, even I want to read it.
-Happy New Year!
-There are always people around--
-Someone's here.
There's no one here.
Happy New Year, sister-in-law.
Come… sit down.
You're wearing Dad's jacket, right?
-Mom gave it to me.
-Yeah, right!
Everyone's already started
cleaning out stuff. So shameless.
Hey, what are you doing?
-Hey, wait!
-I'm leaving. Bye.
What's with these tantrums?
Give me a kiss!
-What happened?
-Nothing.
Go away. Go!
I'll see you tomorrow.
Auntie!
Why aren't you sleeping?
Everyone's asleep, so I thought
you must be sleeping as well.
It's so cold out here.
They'll be dividing this house very soon.
You should sell it.
No one has offered to help you.
No. Actually,
Nishant had asked me to stay with him.
So, why don't you go with him?
How can I go with him, brother?
Seema's there with him.
Seema and sister-in-law never got along.
Then, take turns.
Stay wherever you feel happy.
Your other daughters-in-law are nice.
They're just show-offs, brother.
They're nice, but only from a distance.
You're right. Now, look at us.
Who bothers to come and see us?
They just call me
and say, "I love you, Mom!"
Don't go on about yourself!
Tell me. What will you do now?
I don't know.
I never imagined I'd be so alone.
It hasn't even been
13 days since he died…
and they're already squabbling.
Sometimes, it feels as though…
they're celebrating a marriage
or a happy occasion.
Just because you're offering flowers or…
lighting a lamp in front of his
picture, doesn't mean you're grieving.
I'm not saying that they
should cry for 13 days…
but at least, they should
not forget why they're here.
They shouldn't forget whom they've lost.
I know what they've been doing.
They're constantly talking
about the things…
they've done for you and their father.
Have they no shame?
Did you ever make a list of
the things you've done for them?
All his desires were crushed under
the burden of our responsibilities.
But he never complained to anyone.
He kept himself happy
by playing the piano.
He'd say…
"I could make these musical
instruments sound melodic,
but I couldn't bring harmony
in the lives of my children."
I never really understood
what he meant then.
I'm sorry I couldn't help you, Laali.
They're just ungrateful.
It's not their fault.
I guess, our parenting was wrong.
We never taught them…
to be grateful for anything.
We always take our near
and dear ones for granted.
We never thank them…
or apologize to them.
We think it's their duty
to do things for us.
We forget that they are just helping us.
Would you please sign that?
You're having an abortion… why?
Because I want to.
We must thank them…
before it's too late.
How did your hand
Slip out of my hand?
Thank you.
You were never so unfeeling
Toward us
I have always yearned to pause
The time in my hands
Time that just slipped away
Never to be shackled
Take me in your arms today
So that I fall asleep
Without you by my side
My sleep has evaded me for many nights
Uncle!
I hope you'll come out today! Are you
planning to catch the train from in there?
Check once if he's got
down at the last station.
Just check. Oh, he's come out.
You're a pain in the neck! Should I
just flush myself down the toilet?
-Help me wash my hands.
-There's such a long queue.
-No one lets him take a dump in peace.
-Here's the towel!
-What are you doing--
-Take the towel.
-What about the bucket?
-Oh, right.
-Here it is.
-Hey…
-take it from him.
-Move aside!
-The water's hot.
-Step aside!
-Come on, take it.
-Move out of the way!
-Take the towel.
-Here, take it.
Take a shower out here now.
I've ironed your kurta.
Put it on after taking a shower.
Listen…
thank you.
-What are you doing?
-I'm taking a selfie.
Stupid!
Tell him it's not done!
What-- No!
Don't do that!
Don't!
What are you doing here? Come on.
-Don't you understand why you're here?
-Let's take a photo.
-We also want to join!
-Yes!
Auntie, can you move a little bit?
Yes, thank you.
Rahul.
Go!
Hey, can you please pass the sabzi?
We want some more.
Hey, have some more.
Yes, sure. Wait.
-You're looking nice.
-Thank you.
The people we thought of as our own
No more puris are left.
-Did the kids have their breakfast?
-Give them something.
To imagine we had to explain to them
The meaning of rituals
The roads, the alleys, and every corner
Of the house were left behind
Who could say that I once lived here?
The garland of breathes is now undone
How to weave it together again?
No one listens to the old songs
We once sang
-Are the rituals done? Is anything left?
-All done.
-Can we get up?
-Sure!
-Let's get up then.
-Let's have some food.
-Where's Uncle?
-Hey, watch out!
-Oh, no! Be careful!
-Brother!
-This means, Dad has left the house.
-What happened?
How could he just leave?
He hadn't even eaten yet.
The soul does not care for food.
It's free from all the things.
-So, does the soul go away hungry?
-This ritual is for his salvation.
Laali, now,
it's our duty to release his soul.
So that when the soul is
freed, it can find peace.
-Right, Panditji?
-Yes.
After a year, you'll have to repeat
the same ritual.
-You'll have to come back.
-Everyone?
-Yes, everyone.
-But why everybody?
What if someone can't come back?
Then, let's complete
that ritual today itself.
-That ritual can only happen after a year.
-Okay, let's complete it today.
-Sister--
-I want to set him free…
as soon as possible.
-But Mom--
-Brother, listen.
Come on.
-Sit down.
-She's right.
Okay, then. Sit.
-What are you doing, sister-in-law?
-Please, sit.
Careful.
Look after your mother, son.
She's all alone now.
I'm still here, Laali!
Let's go.
Brother, drop them off carefully.
Thank God, they're gone.
Let's go. They're gone.
Let's go, Mom.
-That's mine.
-This is yours.
Hi!
You're glowing in pink.
-Are you leaving, Rahul?
-No, I just got here.
Take this.
We look nice together, right?
-When will you come back again?
-I don't know.
Hey, stop it! Are you crazy?
-I love you, Rahul.
-What?
I'm in love with you.
It's true love.
Before you go, just tell me
what you think of me!
-Bittu!
-I'll wait for you.
-What are you doing?
-Just tell me, Rahul--
What should I say?
Have you lost it? Grow up.
We're friends with benefits.
Do you understand what it means?
I'll see you if I come back,
but not every time.
What?
Why are you staring at me
as if I've betrayed you?
Two people just celebrated
the New Year's Eve together. End of story.
What's the big deal?
Leave. Don't chew my brains.
I don't have time for this.
This time, the laddoos weren't that good.
Last year, they were just delicious.
I'd got them made under my supervision.
-Let me see.
-How can I eat them, then?
-What?
-They're too hard.
No problem.
When it'd be your turn,
we'll get the better ones.
-Oh, no.
-So, are you waiting for me to die?
I didn't mean that.
-But--
-Look at yourself!
You may die before me.
-Is your packing done, sister-in-law?
-Sulekha, listen.
I'm glad you're here.
What should we do about Mother-in-law?
Our husbands haven't decided anything.
We'll have to decide.
These brothers are totally useless.
-True.
-Isn't it their responsibility?
Must we do everything?
We're the daughters-in-law.
People will say that we
abandoned our mother-in-law.
Now, we'll have to look after
our husbands and their mother.
Listen, let's work it out over the phone.
-All right.
-Whoever has the time,
-can spend a few days here.
-I don't even have a minute to spare.
I can't have my children miss
school, and sit here.
As though I have time.
You know my husband's condition, right?
So, do you think I have
all the time in the world?
What about the fourth daughter-in-law?
Listen, what should we
do about Mom's loan?
Our parents never gave
us any responsibility.
That's why, even we never
shouldered any responsibility.
For the first time,
we're getting to behave like adults.
We shouldn't miss this chance.
We will… always be there for her.
Let's go.
-Let's go.
-Give that to me.
Pay your respects to your aunt.
-No, it's fine.
-Hurry up.
Take him with you.
He keeps talking about you.
Do you want to go with her?
Seema, call us whenever you
get time from the shoot.
-Yes.
-Don't feel bad.
-Don't lose heart.
-We'll meet again soon.
-Goodbye.
-Yes, I have told him.
-Come for my birthday next year.
-Sure.
-Visit us in Agra.
-Keep in touch.
-We'll show you around.
-You packed everything, right?
-Yes.
-Now, I'll directly come to your wedding.
You should also visit
us during the holidays.
Sorry, Mom.
Bye, Auntie.
Bye, Paakhi.
-Hey, Paakhi!
-I'm coming!
Take care of yourself.
Yes, I will.
Keep singing.
I'll give you a call.
I'll come back soon, Mom.
I'm always there for you.
Come on. I'll show you out.
Mom…
our shop has been mortgaged,
so we can't sell it.
So, I was wondering-- In fact,
we all were wondering…
what if we sell the rest of the house…
except for this part?
We'd be able to repay
the loan from that money.
Yes, Mom.
You'll get lonely in this big house.
-Yes.
-How will you manage all the cleaning?
We won't be here to help.
-Right?
-Mom…
we can't arrange such
a huge amount in a short time.
We can't make this decision.
You must say something.
Mom, say something.
Why are you so quiet?
What are you thinking about?
You all should leave now.
It's time for your train.
You don't want to miss the train.
How is she going to manage
everything on her own?
She's hiding something from us.
She won't say what she feels.
-What's this? Show it to me!
-Hey--
The loan papers?
Are you going to pay it?
Stop blabbering!
Just have your tea!
Mom must have hidden
some money somewhere.
That's impossible!
Do you think she has a job? Nonsense!
It's all a sham.
Mom is very cunning.
She's kept her children in the dark.
Did you fix it?
Yes.
One chord was faulty.
I fixed it and it's playing well.
Great! Play something for me.
Our life is like the seven musical notes.
You have to find the note
that suits you fine.
When you find the note,
your life will become easy.
This life belongs to you.
So, the musical notes
should belong to you as well.
RAMPRASAD MUSIC SCHOOL
Welcome!
Namaste. Please come in.
Why didn't you come yesterday?
Namaste, my child.
Namaste.