"Innocent eyes try to convey something."
"Then gradually the heart sways."
"With open arms, but hesitant."
"Fly slowly, says the heart."
"Innocent eyes try to convey something."
"Then gradually the heart sways."
"With open arms, but hesitant."
"Fly slowly, says the heart."
"Just like you speak in dreams."
"Sway in the arms, dwell in the eyes."
"Something similar is happening."
"I am falling
for...something like love."
"Innocent eyes try to convey something."
"Then gradually the heart sways."
"With open arms, but hesitant."
"Fly slowly, says the heart."
"I am not the fragrance,
nor the dewdrops."
"Yet I am present in the air."
"Tell me something."
"Express your feelings."
"I say to my loneliness."
"I am not the fragrance,
nor the dewdrops."
"Yet I am present in the air."
"Tell me something."
"Express your feelings."
"I say to my loneliness."
"Just like you speak in dreams."
"Sway in the arms, dwell in the eyes."
"Something similar is happening."
"I am falling
for...something like love."
Madhu, only our newspaper
is delivered late.
Did you hear?
Hello. Listen. Listen..
He doesn't listen..
Dear..
Ankita. This is the library book.
You have to take it along. - Yes, mom.
Amit, did you drink your milk?
- Yes.
Drink your milk.
- Wow, really.
Who are you talking to? Sumeet?
Are you lying?
- No, mom.
Did you write a letter to grandma?
Gangu bai isn't coming today. Eat.
Everyone has to do their own job.
Did you make your bed?
Did you make your bed? Do you remember?
Yes, I made my bed.
Mama, I am so sleepy.
I know, but what to do?
I don't want to go to school.
- What happened?
He's just like me, Madhu.
- Good morning, papa.
No need to remind him anything.
He remembers everything.
Isn't it, champ?
Maybe you don't know that
they have to go to school.
We are getting late.
The bus driver is honking away. Come on.
Come on, move, move.
Mom, my bag.
Lunch-box.
Lunch-box. Lunch-box.
Hello.
- Careful.
Bye, daddy.
- Bye.
Mama, bye.
- Bye. Take care, baby.
Oh, God. Getting late.
Hey, I found it.
Very good.
How can you forget your things?
Do you remember everything?
Thank you. Come on, move, move, move.
Bye, bye.
"Bye mummy."
"Bye mummy, bye mama."
He remembers everything except for me.
Okay, relax.
Just breathe.
See no evil. Think no evil.
Say no evil.
Yes, I am answering it, but where is it?
Hello.
- Happy birthday, darling.
Thank you.
What's wrong with your voice, dear?
- Nothing.
Is everything fine, dear?
- Perfect, mother.
Our trip to the US has
finally been confirmed.
Here, talk to your father.
Happy birthday, dear.
What is wrong?
Any problem?
- Nothing, papa, I am fine.
I am...I am so happy for you guys.
You guys just have a blast okay.
Have lots of fun.
- You too, dear.
And listen, this year is going
to very exciting and very happy.
Did the priest say it?
- No, it's written in the paper.
Yeah, right.
- Read it yourself.
You get three newspapers.
Papa, I think Shravan
has sent a surprise.
I will call you later, bye.
- Bless you, dear.
Garbage.
No.
Was...that Raghav's call?
- Yes.
Three blank calls.
Is that your signal?
Yes. It was Raghav.
- Come on.
Good morning, boss.
- Shravan.
You were waiting for me.
- Thank you. That's it. We'll do it tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
I...I..
- Another problem at home?
No, no, no problem.
Actually my wife wanted
to go on a holiday.
So I was thinking I should
take a break as well.
So where is the problem?
- Not everything is a problem.
But I just don't understand where to go?
Leave that to her.
Let her choose.
Now that is a problem.
What about my choice? What about me?
And don't be silly, Shravan.
What are you talking about?
- You are being silly.
What do you mean?
That's what your wife will say, not me.
Look, Mrs. Modi should feel that..
..she was taking the choices.
She is buying the tickets.
She is making the plans.
If you suggest to her then...do
you think she will like it?
No, she won't like it.
Then why play a match..
..where it's mandatory to lose.
Solution.
Tell me what the solution is.
The solution is simple.
Tell your wife that she
is free to go anywhere.
Mark my words.
She won't go anywhere.
Problem, bad idea.
Hello.
Shalini.
- So.
I was thinking that this
time we go to Mauritius..
..and then..
- Don't be silly.
It's no rocket science
to know women, sir.
Why does it take so
long to answer the phone?
Listen, Hitesh will come
home from the CA's office.
Give him the pink file.
Right.
- Which pink file?
The one I gave you to
keep near the computer.
That's orange.
- Whatever?
Listen, he will come after 11 o'clock.
You will be at home, won't you?
- You shouldn't even ask.
Where will I go?
When I call home from
the office, darling..
..please don't sound like this.
It's fine to sound like this
if you call from somewhere else?
What do you mean by "Somewhere else"?
Madhu, have you seen
your husband do anything..
..except for office
and office related work?
Thankfully you said it yourself.
What else should I do?
Stop working?
- Oh no.
Won't your office shut down?
Didn't your office stop functioning..
..when you are talking to your wife?
Go on, go on.
You have got a long
day, Mr. Shravan Saxena.
You don't have to tell me what
needs to be done, Mrs. Saxena.
I know what to do.
- Yes, right.
You know everything except for home.
You know this place
called home depends on me.
If I am not there a single day..
- Frankly I don't have time.
But let me tell you one thing.
Have you heard that story of the lizard?
Yes, she feels that she
is holding the ceiling..
What's it called? Oh yes,
the roof of the house.
If she moves, the entire
roof will come crashing down.
Do I look? Are you...are..
No, no, I am not saying anything.
Twisting the words doesn't
change the subject, okay.
Please, don't be so ordinary.
Get a life, I mean...stay happy.
And..
Yes, sir.
- The fax from Mittal and Mittal's..
..could you please send it in.
Yes, father.
What were you saying?
I was asking what time the party is.
When do we have to be there?
- I don't know.
There will be one if
it's supposed to be.
It's just my birthday,
what's the big deal.
29th February doesn't
come every year, okay.
Thanks for telling me, papa.
So will you just waste four years?
- Yes.
Will you stay upset like this?
I am like that.
And I am not sitting idle.
I have many things to do.
Cook food. Clean.
Curse the maid.
And then mother will call.
Look, so what if the
husband is busy and..
..the children don't have time.
You should get on with your life.
Maybe you can't do this anymore.
"I stepped on the clouds
and touched the sky."
"Today I have done."
"What I never did before."
"I don't have anymore desires."
"I have finally found peace."
"I have handed over
my life to my wishes."
"It's great, it's special.
Life is now like a dream."
Madam.
Tomorrow morning, 6 o'clock sharp.
Taxi.
Hey, come here.
- Coming, coming, coming.
"I have discovered paths."
"Which were never meant for me."
"Where the sun shone on dewdrops."
"Where everything seemed dreamy."
"I lost my heart."
"Like it never was mine."
"What I never imagined."
"Has finally happened to
me. It's a unique blunder."
"I have handed over."
"My life to my wishes."
"It's great, it's special.
"Life is now like a dream."
Come on.
Catch him.
Stay back.
Stop.
Where are you running to?
A fast local will pass from platform
number one. Please keep distance.
Catch him. Stop.
Catch him.
Where did he go?
- That way?
Sexy and cool.
No, that's fine. But..
But what? What's fine?
Understand girls, Monty. Okay.
You mean to say I don't
know women psychology.
Hello, hello. It's very important
to understand this consumer.
What do you say? -
Yes. - Yeah, I guess.
This is not the way she is
Now tell me what do girls like?
Girls like...chocolates.
- Right.
Diamonds.
- Yes.
Romance.
Yes, in fact girls prefer to be hugged..
..rather than have sex.
Who said so?
Hrithik we just love you.
- That's the thought.
I think we should go
for the 'so-sweet' types.
They last much longer.
Okay, what do girls don't like.
No dieting.
- No violence.
No maths. - No bad
breaths. - No smoking.
You be quiet, please.
Pink color.
- Yes.
Did anyone come from the
CA to collect the pink file?
Wrong number.
Bad joke, Mads.
Tell me quickly I have a meeting.
Do you talk to wrong numbers?
What's wrong with you?
- What's right with me?
You want to argue?
- Who is arguing?
I see, you are speaking
to a wrong number..
Maybe it's my first day
to talk to wrong numbers.
There's always a first
time...for everything.
Madhu..
Well, sir, Monty has given
these atrocious designs.
They are very tacky.
When you have to make an investment..
..like for buying a flat or bungalow..
..then the middle-class
housewife will never go alone.
Any guesses.
How much a middle-class
housewife spends on her own?
Monty, get me a proper figure. Okay.
- Yes.
Now tell me what will be
the maximum excitement..
..in a middle-class housewife's life?
Buying movie tickets.
Or flowers to decorate her house..
..or a small frame.
Excuse me.
Yes.
- Good morning, sir.
May I speak to Mr. Shravan Saxena?
- Speaking.
Good morning, sir, Ashmita from Town
bank. We need to verify your address.
Ashmita, can we talk
about this later, please.
There's been a purchase of 200,000
on your add-on credit card, sir.
Can you please confirm your address?
Sea-shells, 2400, Pali
mala, Bandra West, Mumbai..
Sir, shall we stop the payment?
No, no. Don't.
- Mind your business.
It must be my wife.
She must be settling medical bills..
..or buying online tickets...whatever.
No, sir, your wife is buying a car.
You have just received 100
more points on your card, sir.
Wow.
Hope you enjoy your new car, good day.
Thanks a lot, Ashmita. Have a nice day.
So where were we?
You were saying that
middle-class housewife..
..cannot spend so much.
But suddenly...why does..
- Suddenly?
..that same middle-class housewife..
- The same middle-class housewife.
..spend so much?
- Spend so much.
Write it down. Why are you looking
at Tarana? I am giving the dictation.
Hey, leave a message. -
No, she's lying. - Darling.
Okay, were busy. Please
call up.. She broke the cup.
Good morning, sir.
Get me buttermilk.
- Sorry, no buttermilk.
Make that fettuccine.
Fettuccine.
- That will be all, sir.
Coffee.
- Will the coffee be black, sir?
Latte?
Americano?
Cappuccino? Espresso?
You don't understand coffee?
Do you want me to explain it?
Will you run over us?
Good morning. Ma'am.
You would want non-smoking, right?
Did you ask or suggest it?
- No, ma'am, looking at you..
Looking at me what?
- I mean..
No, no, no go on, go on.
"Looking at me what."
No, I am sure you don't smoke..
..so I thought you would
want a non-smoking table.
You can guess just by looking..
..what one would like to
have and where they will sit.
No, no, we can make out.
Slightly. Just a little.
By looking.
Men can't see.
My husband can't even see
the socks lying before him.
He empties the entire
cupboard looking for one paper.
And then "Madhu, where
did you keep that CD".
By the way..
What do you feel looking at them?
So I was wearing boot cut pants.
By the way what do you
feel looking at him?
Has he lost his job or
thinking about his marriage?
Or he's an escaped convict?
Ask him.
- No, ma'am.
Go on, check with him.
- Pinto.
Hello, sir.
- Hello, ma'am, how can I help you?
Some ice-tea to start with, please?
No, dessert to finish with.
Can I have the sizzling brownie, please?
Good choice.
That's the best we have.
Thanks.
Enjoy the day.
Please let me know if
you need anything else.
Sure.
Excuse me.
- Yes.
Can I have a lighter?
- Yes, sure.
I think I left it in the car.
Thank you.
- Welcome, ma'am.
Madhu.
I heard.
And your name?
Cigarette will be better.
- Its not good for health.
When 84% Indian women say
they have a big problem..
..it doesn't mean that they
are looking for solutions.
It means that they want a good listener.
They want someone to hear them,
hear what they have to say..
Sorry.
Don't worry; I will mail you
all the facts and figures.
Let's get going, brother.
Come on.
Sorry.
Mahender.
How many times have I told you..
..don't call me Mahender
publicly. Call me Monty.
Chill.
Despite all the surveys,
there is always a first time.
Keep this in mind.
Alright.
Monty.
Where do you work?
- Here and there.
Global firm.
You must have your own business, right?
That must be fun.
I don't like to discuss too much.
Insolent.
You should have told me this earlier.
About my work.
Trade secret.
Smart.
- Ladies change their mind in 10 seconds.
Insolent and smart.
How did this happen?
I was trailing goons.
Yeah, right.
Are you a policeman?
Something like that.
- Something.
Detective.
Yes.
Bill. Get the bill.
Are you following someone?
- Secret.
Oh.
What's the secret in that?
Must be some poor helpless woman.
She must be tired of
her husband's escapades.
Now you have to keep a
watch on him day and night.
Isn't it?
This happens a lot on
television, isn't it?
Can I make a request?
No, forget it.
Can I say something?
I... Can I be a part of
your case, just for one day?
It's a very special
day for me, you know.
Hello.
Yes.
Your picture's on the wireless.
Where else will the police
flash my picture, in your brains?
It's written, "Raghav Passport escapes".
"Raghav Passport escapes."
Good.
Did you book the flight?
- I didn't get an evening one.
If you can't get the evening
one then book one in the night.
Fine.
And book...book a ticket to Delhi.
- By plane?
No, by train.
August Kranti, 6 o'clock.
- Okay.
And book another ticket for Kolhapur.
How many tickets for Kolhapur?
What do you mean?
- I mean..
One ticket for each destination, Chandu.
I am alone so I will book
a single one, isn't it?
You called again.
Make it two tickets.
- For each one?
Yes, each one. Plane, train, everything.
Who is going along?
- It's a lady.
Lady.
Be careful.
Today's a special day, isn't it?
Sometimes Chandu gives the right idea.
Let's go.
- Special day.
Yes, I should get married this year.
Yes, baba.
- Whose car is it?
Who parked it here?
Him.
It's my car, wait just a minute.
Today's case?
- Yes, let's go.
The car.
Yes, guru. Okay.
The case is leaving.
Oh no.
It will.
Try again.
It will, it will. Come on.
Let's go.
Have you heard anything about it?
I will tell you at the right time.
By the way what do you feel?
He must have visited
the gym in the morning.
He is wearing a tight T-shirt.
To impress his girlfriend.
What do you feel?
Will there be any other
problem in my marriage?
But yellow?
Who wears yellow?
Did you talk to the bride's family?
But why is the car so old if he
wants to impress his girlfriend?
So that the wife doesn't doubt him.
You know I really think that..
There.
Anything else.
Send flowers for ma'am.
- Why flowers?
Today's her birthday, sir.
I thought that..
Will you please answer that?
- Sorry.
I will call you back.
I can't talk right now.
Today's 29th Feb and you
haven't sent anything yet.
Oh no, right away, sir.
I will just do it.
- Just a minute. What "Right away"?
What are you sending?
- The usual, red carnations.
Red? No, no.
Red is too much in the face.
But red means love, sir.
Very good.
I am impressed you are
attentive in the meetings.
So fine, red carnations.
Red carnations, two dozen.
- Four.
Four?
- Four as in four dozens.
Four dozens, right away sir.
Oh, God.
Can I be a good husband?
Is there even a good husband?
Hi, Mads. It's me.
- Yes, I heard.
Who is this speaking?
Hello. Will you please
give the phone to Madhu?
Give me the message I will inform her.
No, no, give her the phone..
- Call later.
No, I will hold on.
It's futile.- I want to wish my wife
happy birthday, damn it.
Just put her on the line.
She is busy at the moment.
- Hello.
Be a complete detective
if you want to be one.
Did you ask or suggest?
Hello, guru.
Who? Sorry, wrong number,
Stupid.
You are watching ahead, aren't you?
Please watch ahead.
I am driving.
You...you focus on the target.
You know focus is very
important in life..
..that's what... People say.
People also say 'Sada Suhagan Raho'..
..meaning die before the husband.
Sir, sir.
There was no one at home.
This came back.
The security didn't take it as well.
They didn't take it even
after they took your name.
Keep it inside.
- What happened, sir?
Nothing, and will you please answer your phone.
- Sorry.
And leave me alone for a while.
- Sorry, sir.
Hi, Mads.
- Hi, but this is not Mads.
Jai.
So sorry, I didn't store this number.
How is Madhu?
- She is fine.
Did you argue or not?
- How did you know?
Sorry, come again.
I didn't..
- You two fought, didn't you?
See, Shruti says that
you two can never fight.
We two are the only couple..
..that fight on special days.
That's why we had this bet.
No, we never fight.
Lucky you.
Look at us.
Four years now.
Whether its anniversary or birthday..
..we always end up fighting.
- Oh yeah.
No matter where he goes...we will follow him?
- Yes.
Did Madhu call?
- No, I didn't talk to her.
But I think Shruti called her.
But her call was on waiting.
Anywhere.
I mean, no matter where he goes..
..we will follow him there.
Yes.
No, I get it.
She must be talking to her mother.
Complaining about the husband.
Her favorite topic.
Catch you later.
Say hi to Shruti.
Okay, be happy
- Bye.
Anywhere means anywhere.
Seriously anywhere... I mean..
Yes.
Let's go.
Pandey sir.
Hello.
Actually I am here to see you.
My marriage has been fixed.
You go on I will join you.
Come on, come on.
We will need the
orchestra the entire night.
We want to dance and
have fun the entire night.
Pandey sir.
Pandey sir, listen to me.
Hello.
I know that the police
don't know about this.
But you have to be a complete
detective if you want to be one.
You are leaving.
Whatever you think to do
in life do it perfectly.
That's what Shravan...doesn't say.
I say it.
There's no one at home.
The flowers came back.
Called me a wrong number.
Car purchase.
Someone says "Madam is busy".
What the hell is..
You okay, Shravan?
- Fantastic.
You don't look fantastic.
No, I am fantastic.
Are you...sure?
Yes, yes. It's just all work and
no play...makes Jack a dull boy.
Come on, we have to follow him.
By the way, why is
buying so much phenol?
Does he want to kill his
girlfriend too along with his wife?
Oh my, God.
Spinach.
For ten rupees.
Back at my place we get only
two bunches for 10 rupees.
Here they are selling four
bunches for such a low..
He's..
Why did he need that?
He will put the wife's dead body inside.
He will either burn it or dispose it.
Will your husband kill you and burn you or..
- Excuse me.
Enough.
I didn't hear anything
about him from you.
'Chandramukhi,
'Suryamukhi', 'Jwalamukhi'.
Do you know who they are?
Are they sisters?
It's the same girl
but different aspects.
I mean three versions.
- Split personality.
Wow!
And this man must have an
affair with one of them.
But how will we know
who he is meeting today?
There's place for three
cars. Three, three.
There's so much space
here. Do you want to fly?
Life...must be so different
for some people, isn't it?
Before marriage the
wife's 'Chandramukhi'.
Then after two years she's 'Suryamukhi'.
And after a long period..
- Jwalamukhi.
So who are we going to meet today?
Suryamukhi.
- And me?
Who do you feel I am?
What?
Nothing.
Raghav.
Raghav, the police is highly active.
- That's okay.
Hari was so careful, yet he was caught.
I've heard that they first
pull out your nails in torture.
That's okay,
What okay? How can you be so relaxed?
Get out of the city before evening.
Meera.
For you guys it's like...
Old car, old clothes, old phone.
I feel he has an old girlfriend too.
Come on.
Where are you going? Hello.
There she is? Meena, listen.
- Pancham, you here?
I have been searching
for you for so long.
Girlfriend.
- Why not his wife?
Come on, I mean she's so hot.
She can't be married.
"Sometimes I want to live."
"Sometimes I forget."
"Sometimes I wish a hundred times."
"For just a little love."
Come on.
No, you go ahead.
I don't believe in these things.
Then what do you believe in?
In taking risk.
Try it sometime.
Taking risk is very powerful.
Otherwise wherever you
stop in life that's the end.
"It's slightly changed."
"It's slightly glad."
"It's slightly restlessly."
"This heart."
"Even I have a wish."
"To belong to someone."
"To be angry."
"And argue naughtily."
"Just a little love."
"I just can't find it,
I searched everywhere."
"That face."
"The one who I think of everyday."
"In my heart."
"I just can't find it,
I searched everywhere."
"That face."
"The one who I think of everyday."
"In my heart."
"I search for her everyday."
"I forget about her everyday."
"Everyday I find her."
"In my thoughts."
"Just a little love."
"Wonder why its loss of words."
"My story."
"It's best that I narrate my thoughts."
"In my own way."
"Even I have a wish."
"To belong to someone."
"To be angry."
"And argue naughtily."
"Just a little love."
Did you wish mummy or did you forget?
- Did you forget?
By the way, if you haven't wished her..
..then you better have a plan.
Baby, papa always has a plan.
Papa, if you tell us your plan..
..then we will tell you about our plan.
Ankit.
I suggest that you
tell me your plan first.
Sister has asked me not to say it.
Then your sister must have a big plan.
Did you call mother or did she call you?
I spoke to her in the morning.
She was sounding happy.
Papa, why don't you
join Facebook or Twitter?
Very nice.
- Then there wouldn't have been a problem.
Okay, bye kids.
- Bye, papa.
If my husband would be ditching
me like this then I would..
Not straight, left.
I wonder what I would have done?
Why?
Hasn't anyone ever ditched you?
Amar ditches me everyday.
- Amar?
Our shopkeeper.
And when we bought the flat..
..that broker certainly up to no good.
And have you seen the bills
of the credit card companies?
It is cheating after all.
This is cheating.
Where did he go?
He's gone.
Hey, Ramesh, good to see you.
Tonight is rain dance, will you attend it?
- Yes, sir, I will.
You will also do rain dance.
- I will, sir.
There must be some kit in this bag.
Some mike, radar, gadget. Something.
Everyone will know that
we are following someone.
You..
Didn't anyone tell you?
- What?
You really don't know
how to talk to a lady.
Where is she? Lady?
Hello.
What am I?
You haven't learnt manners.
I didn't have a mother.
- Right.
Someone picked you
from the garbage dump..
No, I was lying in the garbage dump.
You know.
Then the crow started eating me.
They like child's meat, so..
Didn't someone take
you to the hospital?
Someone must have
taken you to the clinic.
If this... Tetanus is important.
Vaccination is..
- No, it's not that.
Someone must have taken me.
Why are you sounding so stressed?
I don't know whether Madhu will
like this surprise party or not.
It's her birthday, she
will enjoy it. What else?
You know ideally what
Madhu will really prefer.
What?
Just the two of us...facing the ocean.
So his name is Samunder (ocean).
Interesting name.
Who are you talking about?
Madhu was with him in the car.
She was driving at full speed.
Ask her to drive the car slowly.
Or she might drown in the sea.
Single room.
Two.
How will we follow him
if we go in the room?
I mean...what if he runs away?
There are no rooms available today.
If you want I can give you next dates.
I think someone's with him.
You should have had a camera.
You don't have a camera.
Look properly.
Sir, all rooms are full today.
We cannot do anything.
Sir, sir..
There's one room available.
Get them checked in.
I will check, sir
Hello, sir.
Hello.
Mr..
- Joshi.
Sir, please sign here.
She loves me. She loves me not.
She loves me. She..
Stupid flower.
Welcome, madam.
I am Manish. Room service.
This is the AC remote.
This is the television remote.
What else, madam?
There is no table here.
We need a writing table.
And get some papers.
- Yes, sister-in-law.
Is this necessary for the case?
If you come in the room
will it change anything?
Isn't the sofa too small for you?
Do you want to stay for long?
There's no place for two
people to sit together.
He has seen us.
No, it's a one way glass.
He can't see anything.
Room service.
- Yes.
How may we help you Mrs. Joshi?
Mrs. Saxena. What's wrong with you?
Room service.
- Yeah.
I would like..
Clear veg soup.
- Just one?
Make that two. And stewed
veggies. And I want carrot juice.
That's all.
- Will that be all?
Hello.
Hello. 'Biryani' (Pilaf),
two. Mutton and chicken.
Get kebabs and 'kofta
curry' (Meat balls).
And chicken fry, fish fry, prawn fry.
It's not fresh, sir.
- Yes. You don't have it fresh.
Forget it. And get a glass of buttermilk.
- No.
Two.
- Anything else, sir.
Two glasses of buttermilk.
As you can see we are
standing before Shamina temple.
Yes, the same place
where Raghav passport..
Yes. It must be him.
Where did you receive the report from?
Raghav?
He has been spotted somewhere.
But he isn't alone.
What are you doing?
- I..
Writing a report?
- Yes, reporting.
He will spot us.
He doesn't know what we are doing.
Yes.
So where does Joshi belong to?
I am not Joshi.
What difference does it make
whether its Joshi or Doshi?
Not to you but it does to us.
Us?
- As in we women.
Whether its Mrs. Joshi or Mrs. Doshi..
..it does make a difference.
It's bound to be different.
If marriage is everything
then it does make a difference.
That's what happens maximum times.
Parties, picnic, movies.
Then one day...marriage.
That's not right.
Everything has changed now.
Come on. Ms. Universe. Ms.
Scientist....Ms. heroine.
When are you getting married?
When are you having children?
Whom does she meet? How does she walk?
Does she laugh too much?
Does she speak less?
All that matters, the
rest doesn't matter.
Just keep following the rules.
Where is it written that
it will all remain the same?
It does change.
Clothes, hairstyle, home address.
The ladies even change
their name after marriage.
Then..
I mean come to think of it..
..it does take a moment
to bring a change.
Revolver?
- Pistol.
It's the same thing. Whether
it's a revolver or a pistol..
..what difference does it make?
The design's different
but it does the same job.
Can I?
Your husband won't like it.
Shravan won't say anything.
- Nice name.
Yes, papa.
- Five minutes please.
Okay.
Hey. Shravan, all well?
- Yes, fantastic.
Are your parents coming to
the party in the evening?
No, dad, in fact they
are visiting my sister.
By the way is Madhu there?
Will you give the phone to her?
No, son, Madhu isn't here. She did call.
Did she say anything?
- No.
She didn't say anything, son.
Alright. No problem.
But don't tell Madhu there is a
party in the evening. It's a surprise.
Why will I tell her anything?
By the way, where is Madhu?
Oh yes, Shirin was
saying that he saw her.
Just check with him.
- There's nothing to check.
She always calls and she didn't today.
She is the one who calls me.
You never answer my calls.
You must have yelled at her.
- Me.
Come on, why would I yell at her?
All of you take her side.
Today is her birthday, do you know that?
I know today is her birthday.
This is not good for you.
I mean, it's not good for anyone.
Drink your soup.
Drink your carrot juice.
Eww, he would never do that.
What? I didn't hear you?
Nothing.
Your husband eats very
decently, isn't it?
He must be scared of you.
Do you want a toothpick?
If you want one then I will
order it from housekeeping..
You can see inside.
- Yes.
It's not one way glass?
- No.
No?
You said its one way glass.
Hello.
You can see from the other side.
You want to help, don't you?
- Yes.
Sure?
- Promise.
Then go and sit in the room.
I need a car.
You will get a car but you
will have to wait for it.
Raghav passport makes fake
passports for Tabir Potli gang.
Yadav gang's sharp-shooter
Kartik Dongre..
..was aided by Raghav Passport to
flee from India, its so believed.
Since then..
- And domestic airports.
We are waiting for inputs
from Railway terminals..
..to know if he's
escaping the city by train.
"It's the reason of many sorrows."
Yes.
Did you find out anything?
The information is right
that's why I said sorry.
Look, if the information
turned out wrong..
..then I won't spare you.
The information is absolutely correct.
That...Riya...double-crossed you.
'Ma'am, we heard that you and Raghav
had an affair for three years."
'Did he promise to make you a star?;
'Your lover Raghav didn't keep
his promise so you took revenge.'
'Ma'am, ma'am, ma'am, one last question.
Have you got a call from Hitchcock?'
You steal as well.
- I am learning.
Did you have to steal my phone?
Why isn't it working?
It fell in the water. Keep it to dry.
I don't believe you guys.
You men do as you please.
How will I understand your
detection sitting here?
That man must have killed his
wife by now and buried her.
And I couldn't even stop him,
How will I know anything by
sitting in the room like this?
What is there to know?
Why do you want to know?
What's the point in knowing it?
You shouldn't consider
everything as a problem.
In life things happen,
they appear differently..
..but the truth is...it
boggles your mind.
Even He doesn't know everything.
Why are you telling me all this?
Because this is my bad luck!
Why did she deceive me?
Who? Who?
Who deceived whom?
A girl. My friend.
To a client. She deceived him.
The reason could be anything.
Maybe that girl loves
your client's best friend.
Or maybe she never considered
your client as her future.
Or maybe your client
became too possessive.
Or anything.
Or maybe that girl
fails to understand him.
Have you ever done
anything wrong in life?
Forget it.
- No, no, no.
I have copied.
In school, I had copied.
I had copied a handwriting,
Your life is very nice.
Just like they write on the board.
Beautiful, blissful, peaceful,
Your life is just like that.
In the morning, drink
tea. Read newspaper.
Go to parties in hi-fi
cars. - Just a minute.
Everything..
- Just a minute.
Just because I am not saying anything..
..doesn't mean that you
just keep blabbering.
Yes, I am an educated girl.
I live in Bandra.
The wife of an important man.
Mother of two children.
A daughter-in-law
of a big family.
What is Mrs. Saxena's problem?
That she doesn't have a problem.
Because she lives in Pali Hill.
She has a nice big home.
A nice life.
You know I could've been anything.
For my husband, I am a housekeeper.
A nanny for the children.
Doctor for the watchman.
A marriage counselor for my brother.
And on top of that I
have to look good at it.
Sleep with my eyes open. And
stay awake with my eyes closed.
I could have been anything.
I can be.
Its not that I..
"Sometimes I want to live."
"Sometimes I forget to."
"Sometimes I wish a hundred
times. For just a little love."
"Sometimes I want this."
"Sometimes I want that."
"Sometimes even I wait for
someone. For just a little love."
"It's slightly changed."
"It's slightly glad."
"It's slightly restlessly."
"This heart."
"Even I have a wish."
"To belong to someone."
"To be angry. And argue naughtily."
"Just a little love."
Hello..
- That client has called thrice since morning.
Sit down. Sit down here.
Sit.
- Yes.
You know we are going to crack this.
This nail polish won't complete her.
I mean that woman is...
She is always complete.
When she's pregnant.
Or in her face mask.
Or while yelling at the children.
Or while getting pest control.
You see this nail
polish is like a friend.
And a friend is all we need.
You know what I am saying.
You made a blank call.
- No.
The line was connected
but you didn't speak.
It was a wrong number,
How could it be a wrong number?
Don't you see the number
here? Can't you read?
Give me three rupees.
Get change.
- I don't have change.
Which room are you staying in?
That...that..
- That? There. Here.
A number will be better.
The one close to the river.
I think...it must be the last room.
River?
That suite. That room
which is like a suite.
A man comes there every week.
With different women.
He brought you for the first time.
Very, very sweet.
Where did you come from?
That..
- You took the long route.
He showed you the longer road.
This would've been a shortcut.
What are you blabbering?
It's my car. I drove it.
No one brought anyone here.
Blabbering nonsense. I don't
know what's wrong with you.
Madam, suite... madam..
I will get you change..
Excuse me.
- Yes.
Are you talking to me?
- How is your wife?
Wife. Look, please don't make fun of me.
Where is your wife?
Wife? Seems like it's the
stress of planet Saturn.
I will have to wear my Neelam.
Who is Neelam?
- Neelam.
Mother says it costs 5000 rupees Rati.
- There's a Rati as well.
Rati, Neelam...who are they?
Seems like this girl is
a problem from my past.
There is a detective after
you, do you know that?
Detective.
There's a problem in
your marriage, isn't it?
So..
- No, no, no...I am not married yet..
..so how can there be a
problem with my marriage?
Actually my problem is
that I can't get married.
Yes.
Will you marry me, please?
No. No.
No, no. What are you saying? No.
Then what are you saying, ma'am?
Actually I am doing my job here.
I came here to organize a party.
I was setting up my tent and you..
It's not fair, it's not fair, ma'am.
Happy birthday, darling. Happy birthday.
You can't talk, right.
No problem.
But you can hear, can't you?
That how much I am missing you?
You don't need to say it.
I can understand.
I will wait.
I just wanted to say that..
..don't get angry over
the morning incident.
I didn't know that
they are coming for you.
I was told that someone
died in the next room..
..and they are only
coming for an inquiry.
Hello, are you there.
Find out from the control
room where this call came from.
How was the walk?
I want to go.
I want to go home.
Drink something. Tea, lime water.
- Why?
So that you can mix something
in it and render me unconscious.
They have told me everything about you.
Who you really are. Who you come with.
And you come here often.
I..I trusted you.
I should have understood before.
You don't work at all.
You are no detective.
And this man isn't your case.
Just like every weekend..
..you must be thinking that
on this weekend this girl..
Do I really look like that to you?
Do I look like that
kind of a person to you?
I am not scared of you.
I am going.
I don't care what you do.
I don't care who you are.
I just..
Keep the gun down.
- Hands up.
Keep the gun away.
You can think anything you want.
I don't want to say anything.
One of your friends had called.
She was saying something.
But maybe there's a
lot she couldn't say.
I shouldn't have heard it. But
I just think there's a problem.
Ma'am, please. Ma'am. A
little to the left. Yes, ma'am.
Mumbai Police made a sensational
breakthrough in the Raghav Passport case.
Someone bearing a striking
resemblance to Raghav..
..has been spotted at both Dahisar and Karvi
check-posts in a brand new red car..
I want to share the bill.
I will share the petrol expenses.
You ordered for coffee.
They asked me... I signed by your name.
A person resembling Raghav has been
spotted with a women in a brand new red car.
Its clear that Raghav's
outside the city..
..planning his next
move with his friends.
What will be their plan?
Stay with us to know.
'Are you a policeman? Detective?'
'You can try if you want.'
'He doesn't know. What difference
does it make? Joshi or..'
'It's a different design.
- I didn't know..'
'Raghav Passport, in the
Haji Ali area of Mumbai.'
'Its believed that Raghav Passport..'
What?
I looked all over for you.
You are concerned about me.
Yes, actually you should be.
After all, today I am your..
What is it called? Shield.
You passed your entire day so easily..
..using me as a shield, isn't it?
Mummy, papa, always
say don't trust anyone.
And never a stranger.
Just leave.. But I don't understand.
It's not your problem, its mine.
I actually thought we
are investigating a case.
I am such a fool.
You didn't think about me even once.
You have been taking advantage
of me since we met in the morning.
You have been planning and
playing and then using me.
What...what are you made of?
Crime is a habit.
Just like morning breakfast,
evening snacks afternoon tea.
Life is not as bad as you think it is.
Life is not as bad as
you burden yourself.
Even you...even you can
make it better if you want.
If you haven't noticed..
..I can look after myself,
you think about yourself.
Don't touch me. Are you
even listening to me?
I heard.
I heard what you said.
I even heard what you didn't say.
There are many who speak..
..but few who understand.
Madam. Where were you?
I looked all over for you.
I had to return your money.
You gave me the wrong number.
- I didn't give you a room number.
Fine, its my mistake..
- Just a minute.
You were talking about him, isn't it?
Who?
- About him.
No, madam.
- You said all that about him, isn't it?
Are you crazy?
You told me the room
along the riverside..
..and only one guest comes
there with different girls.
That's why I thought..
But that's not him,
Now my shop's open, Your
money is right here, count it.
These girls drive me crazy.
Sit.
How many murders have you committed?
Two? Three? Five?
- More than that.
Whether I commit one murder or ten.
The sentence will be death.
Stop, stop, stop. Reverse it.
Can't you see such a big board?
Take a left. We have found the place.
Yes, dear.
- Sonia hit me.
Are you okay? What did you do?
Smiled.
- And her?
What did she do? Did she hit you again?
No, she started crying.
That idea to laugh was great.
Who gave it?
- You forgot.
You only said it.
Can I go for football?
- Yes, sure.
But the shoes will get dirty.
- That's fine.
I love you.
- Love you.
Yes.
- Finally. Finally I got through to you.
- Madhu,..
..I couldn't get your phone all day.
- Really?
What is wrong with you?
Someone else answered
the phone in the morning.
I...I was wondering who is he?
You okay?
- Yes.
I mean yes, what can happen to me.
Where are you?
- I just set out..
Why was your phone out of range?
It happens sometimes, Shravan.
Madhu, didn't you feel like
calling up your husband today..
..and telling him your plan for the day.
No.
- What?
I don't.
I don't believe it.
My...my battery's really
low, can I call you back?
Saving it for emergency. Bye.
Do you plan to elope?
Yes, it will be safer.
Are the police only in Mumbai?
They are waiting for you in Mumbai.
I have to go. There's something.
But.
Stop the car.
Will you shoot me if I keep driving?
I have a doubt.
- You shouldn't doubt friends.
Friend?
You know me only this much.
- No, this much.
Do you know who is a friend?
One who knows everything
about you and still..
I have to go.
- Where will you go?
Someone's waiting.
That..
- Yes, her name is Riya.
Riya.
The same...girl that..
- Yes.
She betrayed you.
And you are that client?
"Sometimes I want to live."
"Sometimes I forget."
Happy birthday.
"Sometimes I wish a hundred times."
"For just a little love."
Wish?
"Sometimes I want this."
"Sometimes I want that."
"Sometimes even I wait for someone."
For just a little love."
"Was it a dream?"
"Or was it reality?"
"What I saw with open eyes."
Hi, mama.
- All okay, baby.
Mama, happy birthday.
- Happy birthday.
You know, mama, there is
a surprise party for you.
Don't tell papa I told you.
Our secret, mama.
What took you, mom?
"Was it a dream?"
"Or was it reality? What
I saw with open eyes."
"Was it good or was it bad?"
"I never thought about it."
"My heart doesn't know what it was."
"Was it good or was it bad?"
"I never thought about it."
"My heart doesn't know what it was."
"Neither a companion."
"Nor my shadow. But yet.."
"..he treaded along.."
"..with me."
"Like a dream."
"Like an assurance."
"Set along like the day.."
"..with me."
Where are you?
I was right before you?
- Never mind.
Hello.
Did you have an argument?
- With mother? No.
Did you tell mother
that you are missing her?
Tell her, then she
will beat you just once.
Tomorrow we are meeting
at tuitions, right?
You know I have kept my hair open.
I will call you later, bye.
Mom.
You look hot.
- You too, baby.
Why did you disconnect the phone?
Nothing to... We were
talking about the annual day.
And then..
- I didn't ask what you are talking about.
Baby.
I..
Are you in love?
Mom.
No need to disconnect the
phone next time when you see me.
And it's fine if you want
to tell me his name later.
Pappu.
Is he in school...or tuitions?
- Chill, mom, why do you get so serious?
Okay.
Mom.
Actually thanks.
Did you...
Ever..
If you ever, Ankita..
Ankita, have you.. Ankita..
I didn't do it, mom.
What?
- Sex.
Thank you.
Thank God.
Thank you. Thank you.
Mom, love isn't sex, isn't it?
And sex isn't love, isn't it?
You okay, mom.
- Yes, I am fine.
"Her words.."
"..is what I cherished in my memories."
"I don't know why."
"Her memories are.."
"..are now my companions."
"I don't know why."
"She's neither a kin."
"Nor was she a dream."
"Yet she treaded along..
..with me.""
"Like a dream."
"Like an assurance."
"Set along like the day.."
"..with me."
Mama, you saw your gifts?
Hey.
Hi.
- Hey, Shravan.
Here she comes.
'Happy birthday.'
Sir.
Yes.
Ma'am. Ma'am.
We have to go to the police station.
"Whenever anyone asks me.."
"..what was the connection between us."
Who was the girl in the red car?
"What do I say?"
Happy birthday.
- Happy birthday.
Can I borrow my wife for a minute?
You two are behaving like you
are meeting after a long time.
It's something like that.
- By the way, do you spy on her?
That's a bad habit.
Come on, don't be silly.
Why were you saying
"Give the phone to Madhu".
Because her phone was unreachable today.
Mayank and Seema were
saying the same thing.
He's calling up frequently.
He's inquiring around.
Madhu had an appointment
today...with the dentist.
Oh, dentist.
- No, piano teacher.
Playing the piano. Play it.
I had a meeting with the architect.
And Madhu is always
frustrated to meet him.
I didn't want Madhu to be tense.
Aren't you ashamed? You're still lying.
"Like a journeyer. Like a companion."
"Who treaded along with me."
"Like a dream."
"Like an assurance."
"Set along like the day with me."
Nice perfume.
Why did you want to meet me?
I am getting married.
Congratulations.
- You too.
What happened this morning is history.
And I was never good at history.
No, it's not a joke.
One more thing, Riya.
- What?
I want to thank you.
Thank you? For what?
I will tell that only to our children.
You will feel jealous right now.
Do you know what you are saying?
I do.
We will drink tea in the morning, Riya.
You will make it.
Good tea, special.
That white shirt, silk one suits you.
You wear that.
Or salwar kameez.. That will do as well.
You can say, "Four spoons of
sugar is too much, bad for health".
I will reduce it.
- You are shocked.
We will get a doctor for you.
I am getting late and I
have a flight to catch.
Have you seen yourself?
I am looking hot.
This... I feel you should
have worn the other one.
That diamond shaped one.
I am not asking you.
It feels like..
..I am meeting this
girl for the first time.
Today or first time after college.
Yes, right.
You know...their guess work...
..is true.
I mean I...was...worried.
That where are you.
Etcetera.
Will it lower your etcetera
feelings if I tell you?
Don't tell me.
You should have your own secrets.
It makes you more exciting.
If it still matters.
Happy birthday.
Madhu. Madhu, come here. See this.
Raghav's surrender has
surprised the Mumbai police.
They hope that there is
no new strategy to this.
And while surrendering,
Raghav has said..
..in his statement that
he hasn't murdered anyone.
And whatever the court's
decision will be..
..after his statement but
he would like to live..
..like a normal man after today.
If Jai had listened to me
it would've benefited him.
What do you say?
Jai?
Look, the shares of
Nascor chemical shares..
..are up 495 points.
Have gone up 40 points.
But he doesn't listen to me.
In fact it will go
higher than 40 points.
Very few people believe in taking risks.
- Sorry.
I want to see.
And not on the basis
of guns and explosives.
He is so cute.
Who, Jai uncle?
- Who is talking about him?
Then who?
"Innocent eyes try to convey something."
"Then gradually the heart sways."
"With open arms."
"Yet hesitant."
"Fly slowly, says the heart."
"Innocent eyes try to convey something."
"Then gradually the heart sways."
"With open arms."
"Yet hesitant."
"Fly slowly, says the heart."
"Just like you speak in dreams."
"Sway in the arms, dwell in the eyes."
"Something similar is happening."
"I am falling
for...something like love."
"Innocent eyes try to convey something."
"Then gradually the heart sways."
"With open arms."
"Yet hesitant."
"Fly slowly, says the heart."
"I am not the fragrance,
nor the dewdrops."
"Yet I am present in the air."
"Tell me something."
"Express your feelings."
"I say to my loneliness."
"I am not the fragrance,
nor the dewdrops."
"Yet I am present in the air."
"Tell me something."
"Express your feelings."
"I say to my loneliness."
"Just like twisting words."
"Breaking habits, interpreting dreams."
"Something similar is happening."
"I am falling
for...something like love."