Stop there.
Dont come ahead
A bad smell in coming from you
A smell of all your bad works
I know.
Now you have to pay for it what you have done
Since last 8 years your soul is not free yet
And you also know that for how much time I have
do live like this more?
I'm not god.
I'm just his man
Who can understand good and bad work
And can tell too
When my punishment will be
completed?
Do you really wanna know?
Fire of forgiveness
can burn human being
but not his bad work
i know you are tired of forgiveness
i also know that before coming here
you have taken decision of your life
To keep you stay away from your life
Whatever I tell you,
you will do what is written in your destiny
but you have to obey one thing
before you can go
you have to write all your works and put it
on the same place from where you start it
one day this will help you
your punishment wont be
completed in this birth
you have to take one more birth
the persons who will take your interview,
they have to be nervous
there is a very big difference in learning
and teaching law
your law will work here like
it works in our house
what you are not saying by looking
at the reports
if you will not help yourself then
how will i help you?
I have tried to tell you this alot of times
If you do like this then one day...
death is in hands of god
but doctor work is to save people
reality is this without his permission nobody
can do anything
may be will not meet next time
you told me everything is in
god's hand
so Professor i want party
Please dont be late tonight
where are you son?
You did not come on this saturday
you have forget your parents
is Siya at your house?
I have tried to find her everywhere
I dont know where she is?
Today she got the new job
I know you went there late and
then she was angry
where she will go?
She will come
she must be at any friend's house
tomorrow she has to go to university
you will go there and say sorry
to her
I'm university and Siya is not here
I dont understand.
Where is Siya?
You should know this
If she is with you then
please give her the phone
If not then please me so that I
will go to the police
I'm also the another friend's house
Are you sure your wife is not
kidding with you?
She wont do that big kidding
There must be something wrong
I will send this photo and picture to
all Police Stations
Nothing will happen to Siya
Police is doing there work
Siya will come back to us soon
You haven't eaten anything
since yesterday
In this jungle I also found this
Dont say thanks,
atleast give me smile
From where you got this in jungle?
You took it from any tree?
Yesterday I went to my uncle's Farm House
I think the company is giving me from there
I dont think I have seen this
car number before
I have just come froom Green Street
I showed everyone her photo
near restaurants
Someone has seen Siya going in
this number car
He did not see this
The way Siya was sitting in that car,
like she was sitting by herself
May be if this is a kidnapping case
Then they haven't call for ransom?
We have to send your wife's photo
to hospitals
Now we cant deny any possibility
I wanna talk to you about your wife
What you know about Siya?
Not yet.
But I can help you in finding her
What is special today?
Today is not my birthday,
neither Valentines Day nor Girlfriend's day
I wanna do one important work
And I promise we will go next week
This is made only for you
I like it thats why I
buy this for you
You are the first girls who is tensed
after taking the gift
I'm tensed about that gift which
God gave me
Wherever you are going today,
dont go there
The way you are thinking...,
I'm not thinking, I can see
Why you let him go?
If you didn't believe me then
why you let him go?
If you trust me then why you
did not stop him?
If you tell him that thing,
then you had to tell him about him
Leave it
This time I wanna say thanks because
you help me
Whose father will was lost
He got the will,
and he won the case
Thats why he give you 20000 pound cheque
Give this cheque to Charity,
you know I dont do this for money
I wanna talk to you about your wife
I think I can help you
tomorrow when you were leaving
from police station
then you saw my upset face and you thought
you got a new customer
do you think I'm doing this for money?
Or you want cheap publicity?
I came here to help you
what do you you will worry?
Lts the thing to worry
yesterday whole day Siya did not come home,
and we got this news from media
I was about to come home first
Then I thought anyone should
stay at home
may be any call of Siya come
ok I will be there
Do you know anything?
Car was registered on a name of Allan Pary
and he has complaint about it
2 days ago
we are trying to take finger prints
may be will be get any clue
it often happens
a simple can be understand very difficult
and somebody cant understand a simple thing
police have less force or
you have forget how to do your work
you are different things instead of
searching of my wife
tomorrow you will say that you could
not find my wife because you dont got good time
because of her we reached this car
instead of this you insult her
yesterday she is helping you
leave it.
He wont understand this
I think Forencic persons have
finished theirjob
I dont you before we will
not find anything here
I'm sure Siya came here by that car
then where she went?
I cant tell you now
You can know anything
You can say about anything if
you touch it
if she was in this room then why are
you not feeling her?
I can only understand the signs of God
I'm not the magician so that
I can know anything
Whatever I saw till now I told you
already
and I will tell you whatever I will see
If you wanna famous then go somewhere else,
dont play with my wife's life
They have find and Indian girl dead body in Mall
Prescritions are same like your wife
I know but you have to recognize the body
if you or any of your guy come near
to that girl
then I will kill him
Marry me
I cant live alone nor I
can let to live alone
nothing will happen to you
i promise you
i will give you every happiness of life
even Medical Science dont have this
how can you do this all?
I never do anything.
It happens by itself
Sometimes I feel it and
sometimes I dont
Sometimes I wanted to help people but
people dont wanna take my help
Sometimes people wanted to help me
but I cant help them
Sometimes I feel I dont control things,
things control me
what is in this?
Memmories of me and Siya
she is our best friend
she introduced us first time
I have seen her going to Bank
yesterday I went to Uncle's farm house
the company is giving me this
I think Monica is behind all this
Whoever do this,
knows Monica very well
door is not broken,
its open from inside
there are no marks of struggle
and nobody hear her voice
with in 3 or 4 hours we will get
Fouransic report
but i dont think it will happen
i dont know anything
there was only one way to reach Siya
I dont know she is fine or not?
I have to perform at evening
I have to go
yes.
You did not sleep at night
who else touch this letter?
Me and my servant
good news is that Siya is still alive
and bad news is that someone
has kidnapped her
this is Siya's appointment letter?
And this writing letter means they will
call at 1 PM
please let me do my work
this is microphone
by pressing this you can talk to us
you tell them you wanna talk to Siya
I know until you talk to Siya you
wont listen to us
We haven't do anything with her
if anything happen to my wife,
then you wont do anything
now listen to me carefully
I will call you at 7 PM
after taking the money will she
free Siya?
Take the money and sit in
your car
where i have to go?
Money is ours, we will take it
you sit in car,
we will tell you everything
i think we no need to tell that you
will leave all the police there
we have fitted microphone in front
tyres of your car
we are also tracking your handphone
what are you doing?
You and your wife are safe
until they got this money
your phone transmeter is gone
listen to me carefully,
there is a bus coming from that side
cross the road and sit in the bus
keep it in mind
the magnet is showing that where you
have hide transmeter in your body
if you dont want that we will
kill your wife
then go to night club
take care of this bag
you will have to keep your
happiness in this
I know where is Siya
you are reading this,
it means you have reached here
in this birth your forgiveness
will be completed
but for punishment you have to
take one more birth
whatever bad work you have done
you have to pay for it in
another life
I'm the responsible for this
nobody else.
I'm the one
body is just a fake
soul is reality
whatever I did, you are
getting its punishment
in 1971 I came to England
from Uganda
we love each other alot
I love her alot
but something else was written in
our destiny
his name was Virath
he was my friend
but I did not know that he was not my friend,
he is my enemy
if you move near me then
I will tell this to my husband
Virath could not tolerate this
he could not get the Namrita
I wanna see Namrita as my wife
this is only one boyfriend's photo
he put lots of poison in me,
then I hated my life
he give me trust that Namrita
is deceiring me
she is cheating me
she was praying for my long age
and I killed her
I hide her body here
I told everyone that she go back
to India
after sometime I knew the reality
it was late
to make your lie into truth,
a single birth is not enough
you have to understand love and
sacrifice in next birth
then this will be finish
whatever happened to a person,
he is responsible for everything
I still cant understand
why this is
happening to me?
Now I understand
that I'm not a human being
whatever I did in my last life,
now I'm getting punishment for it
it seems like its just the beggining
you have meet him before?
Thats why I think about law before
breaking the law
then I will go to our dad
I will tell him my kidnappers
were bastards
after taking the money,
they tried to kill me
Kabir fought with them with
so braveness
I will have to cry
try to act like widow
then your father will transfer his
all property on my name
then after some months we
will kill him
like we kill Monica
she helped us alot
you have meet him before?
If I stay there then would
kill me
then Kabir gave me his swear
he told me to run away from there
then I saw they kick Kabir
I'm feeling shame on myself
I hate myself
we also hate you
and after knowing the truth,
they will also hate you
you also killed your best friend
Monica agarwal
its too late
I told you I'm not God,
I'm just his person
who can understand destiny
you had a doubt on your love
you killed your love
you save this thing,
you did one more bad work
in this birth you did forgiveness
and you got punishment too
you earn good work by saving
people
but your bad work load
still not finished
you had to live without your wife
you got deciere
to save someone else,
you give your life
then your forgiveness and punishment
both done
but still one thing is left
one responsibility is left
for this you have to go back
what did you think?
You will get rid of me so easily?
Then I again reach that palace
then I found this
you knew about this?
Because I thought I will fell
in love one more time
do you know why I'm alive today?
Because of that love
I got my punishment
but who love me in my last birth,
what she got?
My responsibilty is that
I say sorry to her
and give her love