Ten minutes earlier...
'Dry day.
Liquor won't be sold today.'
l'm asking politely...
Just hand over two
bottles of Gulabbo.
Today's a dry day!
lt's Friday.
Who are you?
Saturday...
l'm Saturday... you jerk,
open the store!
And you think l'm Wednesday?
Now, get lost!
Hello...
There's no reason to get angry,
brother.
l asked... you refused...
That's it!
You are right...
100%%%
ln fact, today is a dry day.
Here, take this thousand rupees...
give us one bottle, if not two.
As you wish!
Get lost, you drunk morons!
Howzzat!
Last time both of you
brawled with the truckers...
you destroyed bottles
worth a 1000 bucks!
This old owner had
his license revoked.
l'm the new owner...
forget the booze,
l won't even sell my piss to you!
MATRU Kl BlJLEE KA MANDOLA
Matru...
Why did your dad
take a loan from me?
Not my dad, my grandpa did.
For my education.
- How much?
- 150,000.
That would have fetched me
36,500 bottles of Gulabbo!
lf you wanted to
become a servant...
why did you study law?
Just to blow up my money?!
To punish you.
Why? Am l a thief?
No...
You're the Prince of thieves!
Fellow farmers of Mandola village!
l know the injustice you suffer.
l share your pain.
Land owners are being forced to
turn into labourers...
so that a car factory
can replace your farm land.
Ever since the factory
was proposed...
there are no seeds or
fertilizers in the market.
And the electricity supply
has been reduced to 1 hour.
lnstead of wheat, we have
bank loans swaying in our fields.
They want us to get
buried under our debts...
and we have no option
but to sell our land.
So they can declare it
a Special Economic Zone.
We won't let our farm land
be turned into concrete jungles!
One man alone is
the root of this exploitation.
One man...
Who is that filthy dog?
Who is that dog?
Bloody buffoon!
Speak up!
Fear not,
l'll fix that son of a gun!
Who is it?
After whom this village is named...
Mandola.
Me?!
We have to claim our right...
and if we don't get it,
we have to fight for it!
Enemy of the rich.
Friend of the farmers.
Mao Tse Tung.
Mao Tse Tung?
From China to Haryana?
Such injustice to my brothers
and l'm responsible?
l'd rather die
than do such evil!
Granted l'm a scoundrel...
Mandola... idiot... scoundrel.
But why are you behaving like
Gandhi's three monkeys?
Why haven't you fought yet?
What can we do??
Sue me...
file a complaint...
report to the press...
The police is yours,
the law is yours...
and the government belongs
to your mother!
Then why don't you organize
a procession against me?
Revolution!
Lower your bucket
ln the well
Claim the water of every well
Lower your bucket in the well
You're the owner
if you own the soil
He who tills must own the soil
No big shot can force his wishes
lf the sugarcane's mine
so are its pieces
Out plunderer, Out! Out!
We'll not give the seeds
Yesterday's debt
Won't be paid today
Your arms and sticks
will no longer work
Your bullying and hectoring
Let hammers bang
Let sickles clang
Out plunderer, Out! Out!
Keep going!
Now l'll enter the mansion
through the back door...
come out as
Mr. Harphool Singh Mandola...
and approve all your demands.
Okay?
Okay.
Hold on, Harry...
What happened?
Smart boy!
Better?
Much better.
Come closer!
What the hell is happening?
Sir, farmers... from the village.
What do they want?
Their land.
Your tyranny
We'll no longer heed
Our protest
We'll no longer cede
Your umbrella we'll hold no longer
Now your feet the sun will smolder
He who digs
Must own the well
Out plunderer, Out! Out!
Run for your lives!
Take that!
Hukum Singh Matru.
The gambler of gamblers!
Okay boys...
see you.
Hold on...
one more hand.
No way, the monster will
awaken any moment.
So what?
Now, his dream factory has been
flushed down the pot!
Precisely why he'll wake up
and hunt for me.
Look at the time...
l'd say times are bad.
Run... there is a storm coming.
Good morning, Mr. Mandola.
So, have l hired you to gamble?
No, Mr. Mandola.
Then why?
To drive your car.
There are 50 drivers in the mansion.
Why did l hire you?
To keep you from having
more than four drinks!
And?
To control you
when you're drunk.
How many drinks
did l have last night?
20 last night and
20 night before.
The other 2?
You had those in your sleep.
l led a procession against myself?
Yes, Mr. Mandola.
Did you stop me?
l did try but you said...
'lt's my factory,
it's my land...
so why do you care?'
Then l asked you, what about the
6 billion rupee housing project...
but you replied,
'To hell with the project!'
Then l reminded you...
...about your daughter's marriage
to the Minister's son...
you replied...
'that loser is not worth
marrying a village pooch'.
And then l said...
You've said enough.
Pay attention...
l've quit drinking from today.
Why?
So that you and the villagers
can't take undue advantage of me.
Get the car out.
The Mercedes or the Bentley?
Why you...!
Limousine.
There's no way you can quit drinking.
You bloody buffoon!
You're in for a long suffering...
as long as a limousine!
Hello Harry...
Not the answering machine again!
Where are you?
Madam
Minister has reached.
lnspector, hurry up.
The chopper is here.
Just a minute, brother.
This is the problem
with whiskey drinkers...
their breath stinks like
a goat's behind the next day.
You walk straight.
l'm walking straight!
Stop acting like kids!
Here...
have some mint.
And drink only
as much as you can handle.
Whiskey might give
you a hangover...
but you don't throw up
like these wine drinkers!
What's wrong with them?
Food poisoning, madam.
What?
Remove the handkerchief.
Food poisoning.
What?
Look at me when you talk.
How can you do this
to yourself, Mr. Mandola?
Three years of hard work
down the drain.
All the farmers had agreed.
Clearance by the environment ministry,
approval by the standing committee...
everything was in place.
l... l don't understand this.
The farmers would have
signed the agreement...
our children
would have gotten married...
and we would have begun work
on your factory.
And who is this Mao Tse Tung?
Whoever he is,
we'll arrest him soon.
The police is investigating, madam.
Your police is throwing up on the
streets, drunk out of their wits!
The last thing l want in my state
is the Naxalite movement.
Got it?
What is this?
Wheat fields, madam.
And you think l can see
fields of eggs? Blind am l?
Your report states that...
these fields are barren.
They were barren
for the past three years, madam.
But, this year...
What happened this year?
lt rained...
on time.
Peace.
Declaring this land as Special
Economic Zone is political suicide.
Mom...
why don't we destroy
these crops?
There are many ways of doing that.
Right?
So sweet!
What?
lt happened right under your nose
and you didn't get a whiff?
Right under the nose are the lips!
Your lips are looking hot, babe.
lf not for the factory, quit
drinking for your daughter's sake.
l've quit... from today.
Really!
Swear on my life...
That l can't do.
But you'd gladly have me?
You're delicious.
A small little gift for you.
lf a rat doesn't get caught
in the trap the first time...
you have to tempt it with
twice as much cheese.
We have to double
the farmer's compensation.
That means...
you'll lose 150 million rupees.
Sorry, darling.
ls she Mandola's daughter?
Yeah...
Bijlee Mandola.
Fix her onto your well...
and your irrigation problems
will be solved, for free.
Guruji...
greetings.
How many times have l told you...
not to go swimming in
just vest and shorts.
Well then, what should l take off?
The-shorts or the vest?
Bloody
male
chauvinist
piggy...
The whole village will be
fantasizing about you all night!
You can look... but with love!
This model is named after me...
everything should be perfect.
Or l'll stall the launch.
Did you check the gearbox?
Yes, madam.
And the logo?
l'll get it.
Let's go!
Where?
You're wanted at the mansion.
Why?
Your deal's being worked out.
What?
Wedding...
Baadal's here?
And he's got a gift for you.
Baadal!
l'm coming!
l'm coming...
Baadal...
where are you?
Bijlee!
Here l am!
Baadal!
Where are you?
Bijlee!
Here l am!
Baadal...
what is this?!
The Zulu tribe from South Africa.
For you my love.
But why?
You told me you love
African folk music.
Yeah, but...
what l meant was...
l went to South
Africa last month...
to inaugurate our new resort.
l bought them on a 30 year lease...
and the best thing is,
they have no idea.
l love you, Baadal.
l love you too, Bijlee!
So, you can see a buffalo?
No.
A pink buffalo.
Harry...
it's a typical symptom
of Delirium Tremens.
What?
Your mind is chemically
dependent on alcohol.
You quit drinking suddenly,
and the panic set in.
This condition causes
hallucinations...
making you delirious... afraid...
so that you start drinking again.
People imagine seeing bats,
hippopotamus, demons, aliens, worms...
You should be happy
all you see is a buffalo.
Pink Buffalo.
Gulabbo?
Gulabbo is a reflection of your fear.
You have to face the buffalo.
Next time, grab her by the horns.
At that very moment,
Gulabbo will vanish.
Chikoo...
where are you?
Bye Chikoo...
l am going to the gym.
Hey Harry!
Look at you dear...
What happened?
Nothing... he saw something.
What did you see?
A buffalo.
A pink buffalo.
lt's not funny, doc.
Pink buffalo!
Chinky!
Scrub the floor properly.
l want it spotless.
ls the bathroom clean?
Yes, madam.
Get clean sheets from the mansion.
They are cultured people!
Who will remove the cobwebs?
Go get the broom, the long one.
Yes, madam.
About time you got rid of
cobwebs inside your head too.
What?
Cobwebs...
clean them.
You're looking
like a haunted house.
Why can't you ever get
straight to the point?
And why don't you brush
your teeth at night?
Oh God!
You and your sense of humour.
Mulchand.
What's for lunch?
Mincemeat.
Why are you making
mincemeat of your life?
You tell me? Why?
Because you suffer from the
Meena Kumari complex.
Who is Meena Kumari?
The kids of today!
Superstar of yore...
tragedy queen...
She was gorgeous.
A poetess...
but she found joy only in sorrow.
Deep down you're
a sad soul yourself.
How?
Because you're marrying a moron
and you're okay with it.
Shut up.
l genuinely love him.
l've known Baadal since college...
been 5 years now.
l've known you for 20 years now.
Since you were this little.
l used to drop you
to school on a moped.
So?
So, l know.
What?
You don't love him.
Ya!!
Because...
l love you!
Marry me!
Marry you?
No way!
Baadal has businesses
all over the world.
A house in every city.
Do you know that?
Of course!
We've funded all of it.
ls that so?
His mother has been in power
for 20 long years.
She's been sucking us dry...
and we've been letting her.
ln complete silence.
The farmers love their land
like their mother.
And setting up a factory on
their land against their wishes...
is not acceptable to my government.
But the land is... barren, madam.
And no farmer has paid
any installment of his loan...
in the past three years.
We don't even have electricity!
We were promised 8
hours of electricity...
but we get one hour.
While our crops
dry and wither away...
our quota of electricity is used to
light up the malls in the cities!
Uncle, we will increase
your compensation.
850 was the rate decided earlier...
we'll make it 900.
You'll buy it for 900
and sell it to Mandola for 5000!
And he, in turn will sell
the apartments at a rate of 18,000!
Okay, you fix the price.
Tell me.
We need to ask.
Whom?
Mao.
Oh my!
Who is Mao?
A friend of the farmers.
Are your banks open tomorrow?
Why don't you read it aloud?
What does it say?
lt's a bank notice.
We have to repay the loans...
'REPAY WlTHlN THREE DAYS'
or they'll seize our land.
l warned you that...
we should take what we get.
What does Mao have to say now?
He's left us nowhere!
We're ruined!
Fellow farmers...
Don't lose hope...
We'll fight fire with fire...
We'll strike the oppressors
with our hammer...
...and cut them with our sickle!
We'll resolve this at midnight.
The red flag is Mao's symbol...
assemble where you find it.
Your friend, Mao.
Okay...
Knock, knock...
Who's there?
Repeat.
Repeat who?
Who... who... who...
God!
Stop it now, Baadal.
Come on, Bijlee, he's so cute.
Baadal, one more.
Okay... knock, knock.
Hukum Singh!
Mr. Mandola?
Do you see a buffalo behind me?
Yes.
A pink buffalo?
Dark pink, Mr. Mandola.
You've quit drinking.
That's why the
damn buffalo's stalking me.
She's coming your way.
The pink buffalo?
The dark pink buffalo.
What's wrong?
Nothing... l thought it's the...
What?
Buffalo...
The pink buffalo.
lt's not funny, Harry.
Do l look like a buffalo to you?
When the heart beats like a bull,
every girl looks like a buffalo,
my dear.
Girl?
You just called me a girl!
Knock knock!
Who's there?
ldiot!
ldiot who?
The idiot who is looking at me.
You're funny!
Uncle, you're so funny!
You've got a funny
sense of humour!
How can you spend your life
with this moron?
ldiot has no sense of decency.
And you...
you have no sense of drinking!
No more drinks for him.
No more drinks for me.
Bijlee...
Lock up all bottles in my cupboard.
Hurry up!
What are you doing, Bijlee?
We've got guests.
Drinks anybody?
Bar is getting closed
and the food is laid.
One last, one fast.
Every bottle!
One, one last
Just one more, please...
No! No more.
A small one?
Do you understand English?
Yes, l do...
l don't think so.
No more.
l'll quit drinking
day after tomorrow...
Can you hear me?
Fine, l'll quit from tomorrow.
Give me a bottle of beer...
Bijlee...
All the things l did for you...
Dad...
l want to study in Delhi.''
Sure, apple of my eye.
l want to go to Oxford...
London to study...
Darling,
l'd even send you to the moon!
You know...
it's because of you that
l didn't marry again.
And you won't give me
two bottles of beer!
Bijlee!
Two bottles of beer, please.
You know...
l kept away from you
because of your drinking!
And you didn't marry
again because...
after mom passed away,
no woman would've put up with you.
Why?
This is why.
Everyone knew
that you have two personalities.
One sober...
and the other drunk.
My child...
even if l mention
alcohol tomorrow...
you can cut off my tongue.
But today...
Okay.
Move your hand away...
What?
There's a lizard...
Dad...
Baadal...
don't let dad get away.
Here...
Matru, catch!
After him!
Matru, you bloody buffoon...
Matru, let's go!
Hurry up!
We'll open the bottle,
once we are out.
Knock knock...
Who's there?
Mao.
l know where Mao is.
We lost those idiots!
My throat is parched.
You ride, l'll drink.
Stop, l'll ride.
Unless you stop, l can't ride.
Unless you ride, l can't stop.
Stop!
Ride!
Stop...
Ride...
Stop!
You stupid well!
Move out of my sight!
You broke my bottle!
Gulabbo...
Where will l get
another at this hour?
Speak up!
Are you mute?
Stop!
Have you lost it?
This stupid well blocks
my path every day.
He has to move from there.
l'll talk to him.
Listen carefully, Mr. Well...
He is talking sense.
Children walk to school,
women go to the fields...
anybody could run into you
and get hurt.
Because you are in an
accident prone area.
You have to move out of the way.
Listen, Mr. Well...
your self-respect
is in your own hands.
Step aside or l'll drag you
out of the village!
Did you hear, you jerk!
He is calling me a jerk!
How dare you called him a jerk?
You bloody buffoon!
Now he is abusing me!
Let's drag him away!
Where are you taking him?
To the dyers!
The splashing paint
will make the water dirty...
and everyone will fall ill.
Near the bullock cart?
Sounds good, let's do it.
Pull...
harder...
with all your energy!
Come on, Harry...
come on!
Come on!
What the--
Give me a hand and pull!
Come on, Matru!
Let's pull it together.
Let's pull it!
Pull harder...
it's moving...
keep pulling...
Keep pulling...
lt's moving!
We're almost there...
We made it.
That's enough!
We've made it!
Now that's a job well done!
Matru...
Get some Gulabbo...
From where?
The liquor shop.
No Gulabbo there.
Then where?
ln the aeroplane.
Don't you remember?
We hid a few bottles in it.
Matru, my dear...
You bloody buffoon, my friend!
Give me a kiss.
Today you want a kiss,
tomorrow you'll want to marry me.
l'm not really who l seem to be.
You wait and watch.
First, l will give the land
back to the farmers.
Then, l'll get both of you married
and go on a pilgrimage.
Hey Ram...
Who both?
Bijlee and you.
l won't let her marry that dimwit.
l don't want to get married.
Why not?
ls Bijlee ugly?
No.
ls she mad... illiterate... sick?
ls she not suitable...
or is she a man?
She is your daughter.
What?
l've seen both of you since you were
kids... what a lovely pair you make.
You're like Mukesh and Nita Ambani.
Have you lost it?
l don't want to be Mukesh Ambani.
Then become his brother,
Anil Ambani.
A servant can never
become an Ambani.
l'm leaving.
Where you off to?
How about a night
walk in the plane?
Sit.
You are right.
Once you marry Bijlee, Ambani will
be your servant and you his master.
l'd much rather be a slave.
So you won't?
No.
Think about it.
Thought about it.
l'd rather die than
have you as my father-in-law!
Fine!
Then prepare to die with
your never-to-be father-in-law.
Harry, what are you doing?
Harry...
We're going on a night walk.
This isn't a joke!
Stop!
The night walk will be fun...
Harry, are you crazy?
We'll die!
Are you ready to marry?
No.
Then die!
Please forgive me...
Forgive you?
You fool!
Your daughter,
your buffalo, your car...
trousers, shoes, shirt, watch...
l'll marry all of them!
Thank you, Almighty God.
Thank you.
Now let's go down.
Damn!
So many switches!
What is it?
l know how to take off
but l don't know how to land.
Don't worry!
There are some
parachutes at the back.
ln case of an emergency...
strap on the parachute
and fasten the buckles.
Do remember to open
the parachute upon jumping.
lf it opens, you're lucky!
lf it doesn't, well...
you've had it!
Matru... grab the controls.
l'll have a sip...
one for the road.
Whoa!
You're crazy, Harry!
This is no time for a drink.
Jump, you idiot!
You got a light?
Fire!
Fire?
Then give it to me.
The engine is on fire!
Jump, will you!
Hang on!
Let me light up my cigar.
Where are you going?
Harry!
Harry, get inside!
Harry, for the last time,
are you jumping or not?
Smoking kills...
Then die!
Matru...
God have mercy!
Gulabbo have mercy!
Matru, my luck held!
My parachute opened.
lt's past midnight.
Where is Mao?
Look... there he is!
Look!! Mao!!
Mao! Mao!
The court has increased the
loan repayment time to 3 months!
Mao... this way...
Careful Mr. Mao...
Ni hao, Mao.
Huanying... Mandola village.
Ni hao, Mao!
Hello morons!
Matru?
You are Mao?
Yes.
Until we get our land back...
this should remain a secret.
The red flag is Mao's symbol...
l want that son-of-a-gun Mao alive!
Mandola's peasants!
Mao offers his red salute!
Mao is a cross-dresser?
Mao speaks through me.
You scoundrel... don't you
have any shame?
Why don't you show yourself, Mao?
l will, when the time is right!
Danger is lurking around.
The enemy is very...
ls very what?
stab me in the back... knife...
Got it.
That's him.
The enemy wants to
ruin your mama's pudding.
Before he can do that,
we must ruin his mama's pudding.
You hear me?
Just repeat what l'm saying,
you jerk!
Repeat what l'm saying, you jerks!
Say it!
Mama's pudding!
Naseeban, you moron!
Naseeban, you mo--
What did you say?
Are you calling me a moron?
l'm leaving...
Naseeban...
Sorry...
Please, come back!
Just repeat after me...
That's what l'm doing...
Mao has got a stay
order from the court.
And he gives you his word...
that our crops will sell
at the rates we want.
Let's hear it for Mao!
The court has given
us three months.
But in three weeks
we'll harvest our crops...
and repay all our debts.
We won't let them build a factory
on our farms.
A UFO crashed in Mandola
village last night.
This has led to hysteria
amongst the nation's scientists.
Senior researchers from the
lndian Space Research Organization...
are here to investigate
the crash site.
Fortunately, there was
moisture in the fields...
otherwise the explosion
would have caused a fire.
What's shocking is...
not a single fragment of
the UFO...
has been found at the crash site.
Shocking!
The precinct was up all night
clearing the rubble.
Shocking!
Nainsukh is the only eyewitness
to the crash.
Kindly tell our audience
what happened last night.
Loose motions...
Loose motions?
Last night l had chicken for dinner...
and that filthy chicken was clucking
away to glory inside my tummy.
Chicken clucking in the tummy!
lncredible...
And then...?
l ran to the fields
barely able to control my motions...
And crapped for two hours straight!
Crapped for two hours straight! Wow!
But...
What about the UFO?
l was done crapping and
was pulling up my underwear...
when a mighty gust of wind
blew my underwear away.
Tell us, did you see the UFO
with your own eyes?
Are you blind?
You idiot!
Can't you see
that l can't see??
Where's your camera?
Why do you want that?
Careful, it might break.
Step aside you jerk!
l have a humble request
to the viewers...
if anybody finds my underwear...
red colour, VlP brand with 5 holes.
2 in the front and 3 at the back!
Please return them to me.
Don't wear them.
Now you know? What sets
you apart from Rahul?
Or Varun?
Or Jyotiraditya, Sachin and Milind?
They are all responsible kids.
They don't go around
risking their life.
And that's why their parents
are happy and prosperous.
What are you doing, you bitch!
That's no way to speak
to your fiancee.
Sorry...
What are you doing, darling?
- Bijlee...
- Babe!
l'm sorry... come back!
Mom...
Why is she marrying you?
For love.
And her father?
For land...
And we?
For power.
Mom!
lt's not about love or power...
not farmers or their land...
or about villages, towns and cities.
What's at stake here, is the nation.
A nation is made up of its people.
People, the masses.
And the masses have no identity.
lt's their leader
who gives them an identity.
My character is the
character of my leader.
and thus the character
of my nation.
When l was spiritual,
the nation was Buddha.
When l was sensual,
King Mihirkula.
When l was weak, Alexander
and when l was divided, Babur.
When l traded,
the nation became a slave.
And my rebellion led to freedom.
Freedom led to greed...
greed to corruption,
corruption to wealth...
wealth to success,
success to progress!
Progress!
So, tell me...
why are you really getting married
to Mandola's daughter?
Progress...
For the country's progress.
For the country to progress,
my personal progress is necessary!
lf we get a rate of 1500 rupees...
What does it add up to?
3 and a half million.
Deduct labour charges and transport.
Even after repaying the loan,
every family will save 50,000 rupees.
Matru...
thank god you're back...
or we would've been doomed.
We would've been doomed.
Chaudhary Devi is performing
a ceremony to pray for rains.
So that our crops are destroyed.
[Chanting]
Nonsense!
So if its raining in Chennai,
do l shift the land there?
When is it going to rain here, dammit?
l had warned you...
stop the supply of seeds.
But you chose to ignore me.
Now good luck
with your ritual and...
pray that the crops get destroyed.
Bad news...
the MET department says that
the monsoon clouds may head this way.
They say, it might rain
day after tomorrow.
Even the gods can't make it rain now.
Now what?
l don't know.
Atrazine...
What?!
ClA's secret formula...
a herbicide.
Spray a little bit and
the pests are destroyed but...
spray just a little bit more
and the crops get destroyed.
And the land remains barren...
for years.
l hope you are not angry anymore.
Scared, aren't you?
About the marriage.
Hmm...
Don't worry.
This time nothing will come
in the way of our marriage.
Really?
Tomorrow morning the crops and land
will be destroyed.
lt'll happen tonight.
What?
Operation Mao Mao.
Mao Mao...
Have you seen Matru?
Matru!!
Up here!
What's wrong?
Why are you yelling
like crazy?
l finally know...
What?
That l have it.
Have what?
l...
l have the Meena Kumari complex.
lt's exactly 2300 hours.
And we will
strike precisely at zero hours.
ls that clear?
Sir!
This operation will be called...
Mao Mao.
Check it properly.
Sir!
At ease!
Every commander will have
25 soldiers in his unit.
You will lead from the north...
you from the south.
Sir!
- You from the west.
- Sir!
And l from the east.
Copy that?
Copy!
Good.
The code for danger is Mao.
And the code for danger averted is--
Where is it?!
The code for danger averted is
Mao Mao.
All the best for the operation!
Rain drops are falling on my head...
falling... on my head?!
Smells like cow dung.
A buffalo in the sky?
Hello...
Team A reporting Mao.
This is team B reporting Mao Mao.
Mao Mao.
Not Mao Mao.
l say Mao.
You hear Mao Mao.
Not Mao Mao, Mao.
Mao!
Who's there?
Mao or Mao Mao?!
Shokeen? Dahiya?
Hello, this is Team B reporting...
M-A-O... M-A-O
Mao Mao.
Now listen to me carefully.
Take cover and no
movement till my next order.
Copy!
Sit down!
Lie low...
Lie low...Sit down you idiot!
Copy copy!
Mao... Mao...
Fire!
Yo mama's pudding!
This is good grain, Patwari...
brilliant!
1000 rupees.
That's it?
Come on guys,
you can do better than that.
1200 rupees.
1400 rupees.
1500 rupees.
1500... 1500 going once...
Patwari... 1500 rupees?
1500 going once...
1500 going twice--
Hold on!
There is an order to not
buy grain from Mandola village.
What?
Yeah!
Get rid of this rubbish.
Let's check the next lot.
What happened?
Your grain failed
the quality control test.
What?
You were quite excited when
you saw it this morning...
ln the morning, they didn't know
the name of your village.
Tell Mao to get a stay order
from the court.
Let's go!
Matru...
They have got our grains rejected
in all the markets.
We can't sell our grains anywhere.
What can we do now?
She is in a board meeting,
and l can't disturb her right now.
Okay.
l'll wait.
Hukka!
This is a surprise!
So good to see you.
l can't believe you are still alive,
you dog!
Well so are you, you witch!
So...
when's that revolution of
yours coming?
As soon as you buy the grains.
There is a system for that, Hukka.
System... in this country?
Kiddo, there you are.
Look at this e-mail, listen...
The Australians are getting
really impatient. We have to--
Who's smoking a cigarette?
lt's a beedi, actually.
Hukum.
JN University...
Hukum?
Hukka!
When's that revolution of
yours coming?
Actually, she has told me
a lot about you guys.
- Except that l never--
- Percy Shroff, my husband!
Oh yeah!
Hello!
So you were saying...
Yeah...
Until there is a middle man
in the system...
Yeah right l understand--
Middle man.
Sure, l understand.
l'll go.
Hey, l didn't mean that!
Coffee?
Kamini...
300 families will lose
their land and livelihood.
Somebody has to do something.
We have an urgent delivery
to Australia.
lf you could arrange the delivery in
the next 5 days then...
We have a deal.
Should l say thanks?
Why not?!
l need an advance.
You commie bastard!
You bourgeois bitch!
Stop this racket!
Stop!
What's with this racket!
The first installment of our loan.
And in 10 days you will get
the last too.
Here... have some sweets.
What happened to the music?
Every time l see these hideous crops
in this green wasteland...
my dream stings my eyes.
My dream of...
gigantic earth movers...
bulldozers, stone crushers...
industrial cranes...
dry cement floating in the air.
Thousands of labourers
toiling away.
Smoke spewing factories...
howling furnaces...
and bellowing chimneys.
On one side,
a housing project for the workers.
And on the other...
gleaming, high, twin shopping malls.
Do you see the film posters
on the billboards of the multiplex?
l see them!
With one hand we're
paying money to the factory workers...
and taking it back with the other
at the shopping malls.
The serpentine smoke rising from the
factory chimneys is...
painting our destiny on the canvas
of the evening sky.
Mandola's...
Harry!
This isn't a dream.
This is the mother of all dreams!
l can do anything to make this
dream come true.
Anything?
Anything.
Such as?
Go on Harry,
why did you stop?
Tell me...
What can you do to
make this dream come true?
Say it...
Please!
l will give up alcohol.
Forever?
Yes!
You swear on Bijlee?
l swear on Bijlee!
Harry, it's raining!
Everything is washed out.
Ruined!
Rush to Chaudhari's farm,
he must be alone.
All of you meet me
at the warehouse...
the harvest is there,
rain water shouldn't leak in.
Hurry up!
Wow!
Bijlee!
This is not the time
to lose hope.
lt's time to keep
the fire burning inside you!
A prayer from the heart,
always comes true.
This isn't just rain,
but showers of blessings.
Thank god!
Remember...
Unless we concede defeat,
they cannot win!
They have no way out.
Shokeen,
prepare the acquisition papers.
Farmers all over the country
are with us.
Tomorrow, we will march
all the way to Delhi.
New Delhi, the seat of power,
is within reach!
Cheers!
Lalbihari!
Patwari!
l, Lal Bihari Sarohi,
son of Babu Lal Sarohi,
resident of Mandola...
have freely and without encumbrance,
handed over my land
to the state government.
l accept the compensation
given in return for this.
Generally l'm not so corrupt...
you know that.
l'm doing this for love.
Not for you!
For the love of Baadal.
Also my son-in-law.
Not yet.
There's many a slip,
between cup and lip.
On the day of the marriage,
give your daughter...
and take the signature.
- Call the PM's office!
- Yes, Madam.
Guess who told the villagers
about Operation Mao Mao?
Who?
The fan?
The bulb?
What are you saying, mom?
Tube light?
Bijlee!
l will kill the--
Shhh..!
Silly boy...
lf you kill her,
who will you marry?
And anything is possible
after marriage...
anything!
Our progress depends on
Mandola's property...
and Mandola's property
depends on this marriage.
Therefore,
nothing should stop this marriage.
And nothing will.
l promise!
What will you do?
ln Delhi?
l'll work for the community,
teach at the University.
Don't you care about me?
Nope.
Do you have a girlfriend?
ln Delhi?
Do you?
Yeah.
What's her name?
Sheila Dikshit, the Chief Minister.
Listen!
There is something l have to say...
l have...
l've started brushing
my teeth at night.
l don't have the heart to watch
the factory replace our farms.
Once you get married your
mother-in-law will sign the papers...
and declare the farms a
Special Economic Zone.
What if there is no marriage?
Matru!
We love you!
Daddy...
Which one of these should
l wear this evening?
This or this?
As you wish,
you'll still look the same.
Fine, l'll ask Bijlee.
Bijlee!
Matru!
l'm scared...
What do l do?
Tell you what...
don't be scared.
Be serious.
Are we doing the
right thing?
Fair is foul and foul is fair.
Hover through the fog
and filthy air.
Excuse me!
Yes?
Have you seen Bijlee?
Yeah!
Where?
You know the lake inside,
she is swimming there.
Thank you... thank you very much.
You are welcome!
Are you ready for
Operation Wedding Night?
Of course l am.
l'll add sleeping pills
to Baadal's glass of milk tonight.
And l'll make sure he has the milk.
Before he can even touch me,
he'll drop unconscious!
Great!
Making the guards unconscious
will be my responsibility.
As soon as l get the signal...
l'll take out the knife...
hidden under the bed...
and cut Baadal's heart
into a million pieces.
And l'll place the knife in the
hands of an unconscious guard.
Then l'll scream!
Murder... Murder... Murder...
The guards will be
accused of the murder!
And l'll be yours forever.
That's Bijlee's voice, right?
Why are you crying?
And why is she laughing?
You're like thunder in the sky,
you blow my fuse away!
ls it an electrician?
l didn't send him.
Then one day we'll get rid off
his evil mother...
and get our hands on her money...
get married and sail the seven seas.
Sail the seven seas!
My Lady Macbeth, well done!
Bijlee, somebody will catch us.
Have mercy on me.
For gods' sake, let me go!
How can l ever leave you
even for the sake of god?
Thank you.
Bijlee!
Who's inside?
Nobody.
This 6 foot tall thug is nobody?
Oh... you're not Baadal?
What were you doing inside?
We were reading...
Shakespeare...
William.
ln the swimming pool?
l fixed the leaking tap...
until the pool could fill up...
we thought we'd try,
reading Shakespeare under water.
Shakespeare...
Bastard, do you think l'm a moron?
ls it a crime to read
Shakespeare in this country?
Careful...
Matru is like a brother to me.
And if he says they were
reading Shakespeare...
then why don't you believe, that
they were just reading Shakespeare!
Who are you to doubt
my fiancee's intentions?
Her father.
Once when you were a kid,
your mother spanked you a lot.
You were playing truant from school
to go for a movie.
l didn't talk to her
for months after that.
Now l think she was right
and l was wrong.
l think l should spank you.
Who am l dreaming
these dreams for?
This lifestyle... this wealth...
for whom?
For me.
Go get dressed.
Matru...
Matru.
Are you an idiot or a coward?
Are you blind?
Or are you diseased?
l am Mao.
Look what l've found...
What is it?
See this!
Extend your right hand.
Please bring the bride.
Bijlee, are you ready?
Bijlee!
Bijlee, where are you?
Daddy!
Cheers daddy!
l've been stuck in here for an hour...
Help me out, please.
Sorry...
What have you done?
What?
Oh!
The booze?
Now l know why you
love alcohol so much.
The truth doesn't seem so bitter
when you're drunk.
No pain... no sorrow...
lt's so much fun living a lie...
thanks to the booze.
Daddy...
You know, l even thought
of committing suicide...
then l thought
l might as well get married...
Same thing...
Never mind...
Let's go...
Thank you for coming.
Hello...
Oh... here...
Mom!
Hold this, please.
But...
Mom, your daughter-in-law is
so uncouth.
So sorry l'm late!
- Where should l sit?
- Go there.
There?
Sit here.
Shift.
But where?
l'll sit here.
You look handsome tonight!
Pundit sir...
begin the chant or...
the factory inauguration--
Sorry!
l mean the wedding will get delayed.
You bloody buffoon!
Get started, Pundit sir.
Hukum Singh!
Who put bottles of
liquor all over the house?
Mao did.
And who is Mao?
l am.
lf your Mao,
then l'm Veer Bhagat Singh!
lf you're a hammer,
then l'm a sickle.
God to the farmers, Mao.
l grovel at your feet
you bloody buffoon!
- Leave this one.
- Give it to me!
You can take one!
Okay... this one.
No!
Take the one on your left,
you're Mao after all.
But why hide it from me?
Why didn't you tell me that
you're Mao?
l was...
waiting for diesel prices to
go up.
Even the radish has
shot through the roof.
Your aunt eloped with the watchman.
And my daughter is getting
married today.
But the minister has
not signed your file yet.
Hurry up.
Place the flowers...
Please stand for the seven steps.
Yes, okay...
Bijlee... wake up!
The steps.
What?
lt's the time for the seven steps!
Take the flowers.
Get up.
- Get up?
- Yes.
Help me.
Careful!
Not that way...
Why didn't you say so.
- Sorry.
- Let's start.
Look sweets!
No no... don't do that!
Stop right there.
You bloody buffoon!
Daddy!
Stop it!
You bloody buffoon!
Daddy...
My darling...
Bless me...
How many steps are complete?
Only four.
That was close...
you bloody buffoon!
Anyway, better late than never.
What happened Mr. Mandola?
That which shouldn't have happened.
Gulabbo in... Harry out.
Just a minute!
First you sign the file...
then we move ahead.
Bloody buffoon!
Are these real?
Yes!
Mom!
Pen.
You look hot!
What are you doing, Mr. Mandola?
l'm playing
People-Politician!
Politician-People!
Alright, give me my pen back.
Stop it!
Stop it, Mr. Mandola!
People-Politician!
Politician-People!
That is cops and robbers,
not People-Politician.
Cops and robbers...
For the amusement of all gathered here
This is the tale of a crook
Lend me your ears
Here's how it goes
Politicians of all hues,
use all their might
Walk all over the peasants,
pocketing everything in sight
Sports scams and rail scams
Cops and ministers, hand in glove
Laughing all the way to the bank
Telecom, airwaves, 3G,
how hard it all sank
That's how it goes
The tale of a crook
The swindles and the scams
Oh how badly it stank
Madam...
Mr. Mandola.
You are under arrest.
Come here you jerk!
Now!
What do you mean under arrest?
Section 290 clause 510...
consuming alcohol on a dry day
and creating nuisance in public.
He is right.
You sellouts!
Leave him.
Let him go.
Daddy...
You've shown your true colours,
finally.
There are only three steps left,
complete them properly.
l don't want to get married.
You are drunk right now.
You can't decide what's
right or wrong.
Like your father!
Daddy!
You better listen...
Or else your kids will laugh
when they see your wedding video...
Oh! Mom got married in handcuffs.
Come dear.
Your tyranny
We'll no longer heed
Our protest
We'll no longer cede
Your tyranny
We'll no longer heed
Our protest
We'll no longer cede
Your arms and sticks
will no longer work
Your bullying and hectoring
Your arms and sticks
will no longer work
Your bullying and hectoring
Let hammers bang
Hammers, Hammers,
Let sickles clang
Plunderer, Out! Out!
He who tills must own the soil
No big shot can force his wishes
lf the sugarcane's mine
so are its pieces
Plunderer, Out! Out!
The consequences of this will be dire,
Harphool Singh Mandola!
You have no clue who
you're messing with...
l'll make sure you rot in jail!
Once you're sober you'll come to me
like a sad little puppy.
Get lost, you jerks!
You scoundrels!
You called me a sad little puppy?
Daddy!
l am such a bad father...
l was about to get you married
to a beast.
Forgive me, my darling.
Now l'll get you married
to a human being.
Come.
Who?
Who else but you.
Where is that Pundit?
l'm not a human being...
l'm a servant.
So what...
l wanted to be a servant's wife,
since my childhood.
You fool,
you can't marry a servant!
Why not?
Does a servant's wife
have three udders?
Or four?
This man, your father.
He'll have us both
killed tomorrow morning.
You get it?
And why would l do that?
Because you're drunk right now.
Remember what l said?
l'm not really who l seem to be.
l swore on Bijlee.
This poison would never
go down my throat again.
You failed to notice, Matru!
The bottle's seal is intact.
l am not drunk.
You bloody buffoon!
Daddy.
Give me a hug!