The website of Bollywood Won
Bollywood1.co
Custom from the owner
India's Top Cinemas in Bollywood Van
1Bollywood1.INFO
Intagram Bollywood Van
@ Bolly1official
Bollywood Van Talking Telegram
@Bollywood1official
It stays here
Great City
Here, Shiva's bayonet governs everyone
Here you are in Varanasi, your dash lives under his shadow. He rules all
I am dard i am
... I've given you my life, Don (big criminal) Yuppy
There is no one who does not know me
There is no one who can confront me
I was born
Now listen more, act (reader)
says
No one is like me
All my little brothers
Anyone who attacks from behind shoots it
He takes everyone, removes his head
He completes his throat
Whenever you fight, you will surely win
Together with the lion, it's like a winner
John Doon, my dad
This is yours
Swallow and Nightingale when the voice comes in, sing
Do not hate
Daddy dan
Translator: Sepideh and Yasin
Professional and audio translation from Bollywood Van
Bollywood1.Co
"Your daddy does not speak"
Translation from Bollywood Web site
You fool, you steal and run away?
Your dad will build your life
Are you betraying her with her?
Do you have friendship with Mishra helicopter?
Do you participate?
Listen, it was Miashra's gun
What should I do on my head?
Daddy John, who disappeared in the last 3 months
Gupta
... If you do not listen to the prayers for three months, God
Do you change your god
No, I'm sorry, this is not at all
It was a bad situation, I'm doing anything for you
Excuse me, I can not see you
Have you studied English for three months?
How is this possible? English?
Your dad is dying to educated people
... how much respect
You know Gupta this
Yes of course
Make sure you have a chance
Ask two questions
Two questions
What is the Taj Mahal?
Agra
Arifin Gupta
The second question
Do you have a ridge with a few rupees?
Three hundred crore?
If a builder wanted a theft like you
It would be so great
You make that time with 25
Do you have a degree, John?
I sent the king of the world from the grave and asked him
She said, "I'm dead."
I made 25 crore, let me sleep, please
Now I'm sending you to the king of the world
Go there, ask yourself
Gupta
what is this?
I'm pregnant
stand up -
Gupou dear
Do you remember Caravagh today?
All your day is yours, but this one day
Is not your wife?
If Pato out of this
I do not want to get back
! I see
Let's go out
Come back inside
Come go out again
Sapna Dupe is the boss
I am my boss
Okay, your support is coming, he's going to go
Caravecate? Today I am alone
Why are you feeling upset
Control your self -
Gopu you go
I do not think so
Waitress -
Thank you, John, I always love you
Now you see what it's like
Seeing your dad, John, you have to go before him
Doctor ward
He is Dr. Bisigar
come come
What happened to my dad?
Sit down
They are two years old who did not read
two years?
Yeah -
Smile early
Laugh loud now
Sir, I'll laugh at this for 2 minutes
Sir this is your bullet and bullet. With
Your bullet just happens
Go now
Whenever you see me you should be lazy
Sit down
You sat down
Who is sick
What disease do you take? Who is sick
Daddy dan
What is the master
Daddy John is feeling angry when hearing some of the things
what?
It makes you feel painful -
He pays the money he must take
Who needs to kill you
Because of this business we are in danger
No problems
Yes! Yes
Volt, so easy, no? -
Did I say right? -
Seven months
Seven minutes
Seven o'clock
It says the harmonic imbalance
Your dad, your life, these conditions sick
Instead of crying, laughing
That's what happened
... sometimes
Ask me for 20,000
Twenty thousand this
Come on this 3 rupee varnishes
It's like this
No, I did not mean that
That's exactly for me
Let it happen
Daddy dan
Doctor Dr
Is all this colorful tablet?
Do not be afraid, these are different drugs for
Different modes
You look at me
Do whatever you want
Do it from the bottom of your heart
Do i do -
Yes sure
Really?
Saw, the doctor is telling you
Right now?
Do my dear, do it
Well then I'm doing it now
Daddy John has a good feeling
I said what you want to do, do what your hands do
Do not take meendo
I'm comfortable with stress today
I encountered myself, I saved myself
Doctor Hevrhta stresses, he sings the song
!Stress! the doctor
You dying
Accept my words
Go away, give it away, and cut it off
You are very good doctor
I introduce you everywhere
Wait my life, wait
Daddy John, listen
... Where does love come from? But everywhere it may be
This is not here
Bangles, Bangles
My diamond bangs
Tell my beloved, do not bother me
Bangles, Bangles
My diamond bangs
Tell my beloved, do not bother me
Since last June I have not talked about it
Come on, I'm tired of waiting
I kept open my sleeping eyes
... you
You are mine
Seeing you this sentimental heart
go to hell
Without you, the spring is fantastic
Make a compliment, let's join our hearts together
The link between you and you is definite
I kept open my sleeping eyes
My diamond bangs
Bring to my beloved do not annoy me
I talked to him since June
I did not go, I'm tired of waiting
I kept my sleepy eyes open
Give me your hand
I'm coming home
Behold, I can not live without you
Am i oxygen
For me, you have oxygen
... I smiled at you, danced with you
.... This does not mean that Sapna Dupe has believed her career
And give it away
I have a lot of work, I'm going
Go to Pinkie
sister-
what are you doing?
Eight months waiting for sister's husband
Who will come and get you
Now what's up, what do you do?
Pinkie! You do not know the marriage policy
... Now that I've come, I'm fine
... I get everything that I want
Then i go
Greeting
Live my daughter -
Have not you gone yet
Let's go
... Sapena ... me
Let's go my son
Kayal again, this day is revealed, O God
It does not look like anything today
Daddy John, you're welcome
You put me in front of all my little ones
I went to see my wife
I'm all small before
Did not accept his wife?
Did you go away?
Said you have come Did not you do anything
Where do you know where you say what he said?
Psychology tells you that something is happening
Come on, it's the habit of all the women
I cry for a change in my body
Get the women out, they're creatures unknown
no no no. You do not understand
This is the problem of all women
But you said something about that
I pay tribute to you
You went and loved your wife
You voted
He did not accept
What does this prove?
You like him
I love it-
If you have a woman about her, okay
Friend if you can not
Excuse me, as the doctor said,
Wait a few days for her woman
Think sick and do not care about it
But what can you do?
The husband is the husband
I'm not talking about daddy
What should a husband do?
Daddy sit down
Look at the husband for a look
How do you feel about your wife?
How many months have you gotten your cartoon?
Do you like a woman?
Someone will tell you the good news, your wife
likes?
If your dignity diminishes, the woman will love her?
So then something else is done
The whole country knows you
Every attack and every street is just your poster
Do you know, don. Big don
Defeat the enemy
It also takes the name of the cat
They are Helicopter Mishra
You have a purpose in life
End your dash administration
He rules himself to Varanasi
Mishra helicopter does not lift, he raises the rest
Respect me
Get the paperwork you want to sign
We can not sell this land
About our land and our destiny, we just gave her the decision
Kidding
Time is dead, John is dead, now is the time
The helicopter is mythical
Your dad will decide
let's go?
Bollywood Van Talking Telegram
@Bollywood1official
Hello friends, today we want to bring you with one of the people
... get acquainted with Bollywood
A person who has earned three movies of a thousand crore
... and theirs
Goldie Kapoor
You only care about one thing in my life
Money
Money supplier
My next movie has at least 500 crore profits
Five hundred crore?
It's a trade
It talks about a thousand crimes
I know we're kidding for a thousand crimes, which one?
I do not know, investigate it
Number and address
cut
I'll show you, go along
Sorry
who is it?
His dad John Terry di speaks
Watch my dad for the kids, three-dimensional
And that's brash
Hey listen
Do you understand this phone?
Do you know what your dear Time is calling, then call
Okay, I'll call for a few more minutes
where were we?
Sorry
who is it?
Lucky Singh, on behalf of his dad
Mr. Goldie is filming
When will you return
I do not know-
what happened? What does he say?
I do not know -
How stupid did you say two hours later
She said she did not know when the director came back
Sorry
Stop filming
Who's this?
Mr. Goldie Kapoor
The last three years have been filming since
Get started
But my movie has not started yet
Just for the sake of you, Guldi Kapoor
Do something, get my money back
Today, right now
Make a check
Mona is a long time following this director
From that time on, it just cuts off the phone
Give the phone, I'm talking to him
Hi what
Bobby speaks
Hello uncle, sir, your dad rusty
Daddy dead, how rusty
Yes daddy
I am a jerk
I will not make a 3D movie
Talk to Vikram
Check out who you are
My phone is cut off
Call her again
! Cut off
Give me a boat
Take the check -
The phone rings, give it
Three-dimensional "speaks"
Jackie
3D -
I'm free time
Jackie Shrove or Jackie Pattenager?
Jackie Chan
you got it?
You see Hong Dang
I call Varanasi
Tom, how are you?
3D -
Tom Smell or Tom Holter?
Tom Cruise
Fool
Jackie and Tom?
I do not understand Thierry Dm -
Mission Impossible 3D
It can be, do not worry
Now I understand Thierry D
What do you think, do you think?
Tom Cruise, Jackie Chan, Amir Khan, everyone
The world is for us
A budget of $ 500 for a film, its revenues
Unmatched
Keep this check on you
no no no -
Please!
Please do not ask for this -
Why? - Making my first film again
Come on to give me your money
If I'm dead, it does not matter to me, this is your check
Ok, Allens tell them the rest of the details
please come
The money for Goldie Kapoor, just goes
Does not go anywhere
good morning
Welcome to Yuppy
Yupi?
I am ui ui
Mirzapur here 300 km, me
How did i come here
My daddy was telling the move ... You came here too
Come here, dear director
You walked in the city with Inver Overnight car
Today, go to the traditional way
What is your life for this life?
Man is a moment, it was a moment
As it was yesterday in Bombay, you are here tomorrow
You are astmona
Hey, I do not scare you with this
I made the same black scenes, did you know?
I'm not a little kid, very famous
... What was his name, colonel Matar
Come on, I know, you're all in prison
What sound was this from behind?
check it
Oh damn
How many times did I tell you after we killed someone?
Do not challenge your own land
Put it in the water
Who is this miserable?
This is a niche
Your face is broken, look right
Challenge everyone, call your name
Which one to understand
Come see her watch
Auraa, this is my life
see
No, not this bitch, Colonel Maturue
What was your director dear, did you want to talk to?
Come talk straight away
Mr. Dadash John Turdi, you do not need this
You get involved with me this problem
Just a thought, about the smurf
You should not be dragging a little something like this one
Daddy dan
Studied
what's up here?
Your exam is John
what is this?
Two questions
The first question
Amitab Chikara Abishik?
It's easy
Amitab Bachchan, Abishik's father
The second question
Amitab, chikare amitab?
This is what the question is! Not a question at all
The question is true
I am answering this, Amitab, the name of Amityab
That question was rejected
Congratulations
You've lost 11 crushes you have to pay in 11 days
Your appointment has started now
Eleven crore eleven days
Where do i go
That's wrong
I know and you ask me two questions
I'm answering two questions right now
I'm poor, do you know?
Famous director
Goldie Kapoor
So what about me?
You do not understand
Take a picture with such a famous director
You are also a famous doctor
My head explodes
Mummies swallow
My blood pressure is high
I'll call you later
What's your head
Do you like it?
Do you have blood pressure?
Where do you know
I heard this here, God listened to me
Lulu
My name is
Introduce me Lulu
They are my boss
Dr. Bodsaygar
Famous psychologist from Mirza Pour
Mirzapur?
How do you live there? -
Just let's go sir
Are you going? -
It's yours, it's yours
You know
I got a stolen Bombay here
kidnap
Do you have anything
The treatment is the answer, sir
What treatment?
Nothing, your trusted agent
He has a weak spot
Is it a weak spot?
what do you say! Sit down
Remember me
This weakness loves him
Can i take a picture?
Get caught
Yes sir?
what has happened?
Picture
Take it
Yes sir?
what has happened?-
Take a picture of Lulu
just a moment
Can you get it
Present?
What is your disadvantage?
She is a confidante
You know when filming Salman Khan from
Psychologically, one problem was found
I'm looking for my doctor
Salman Khan?
Salman Khan himself?
From Kay Salman Khan -
No, I mean, I mean
I heard a lot of complaints
You say, what's your problem
.... you know
Tell me, doctor, I can cure him
I can not say
Let's say
Is a confidante
Confidential
Sir, finish this game confidentially
Open it sir
Are you all here Is not it strange?
... The main cause of the illness was John Bridney
The woman is dead
The director has arrived sooner
If I knew, we wanted 3-4 additional craters
What do you say, I do not have the money
I'm hungry and dressed. Everything I get is here
The reason is that I can not make a movie now
what film?
It was a romance story
Couple story
A skeptic woman and an innocent husband
The woman wounds her and goes away
Eight years of marriage, the wind fades
What's the use now?
Seven months
Sapena went to me and gone
Did your wife and welton
You and my story are like you
What's next
That's what it should be
Sorry
Woman finds out her mistake
She goes to her husband
Crying, begging
He goes to spray and apologizes
An innocent husband also brings him
Happy Ending
This is a movie story
You will not be like that
No, you can not die
Ok do not accept
If I have your story
I'll show you a glimpse of it
The woman she had not seen before
He loves you that he has not felt so far
Do not show all this to you?
He finds out his mistake
Will or not
Sapena does not do this
Why does not she
Really?
Sure-
Well then I'll make a movie
How much budget do you want
Sixty one crore-
Sixty one crore
Excessive
What are you doing
Back to Sapna?
shame on you
We make films
Take these 11 crimes for consideration
Mubarak, my dad is the producer
I'm going to leave the rest of Mumbai
Is Sapna going?
The saws are sure to come
If I'm not directing you, I'll be directing you
You make the world next to you
OK
Your dad John Dadish John
You let Polar go back in my car a couple of more years
Hey
where are you going?
I'm going to be the author and the rest of the gameplay
You're not going anywhere
Where do you look Get it all here
Let's start early, when will my supporter get back?
Daddy dan
amazing
What is the title, Daddy, the wonderful name of the film, okay?
Do you like sapena
I'm so sorry for you
I fell in a hurry
Sapena is happy -
Aunt
Listen to her
Get acquainted with him, Mr. Paron listen
A hard work writer, who is trying to do it
Get out of here
I rebel -
But the part of this will change very soon
The quest for this will be much more
O God, there is a real scene
Like a real donkey house
Goliide is an idealist
Play the game
!Great! Who wants to know that you're not really a gangster?
Are you a character Great
Do you know who you are?
Do you know why i did this
Why why why?
Cut Cut -
What that is
This is Goldie Kapoor's movie, the Octa Kapoor series
Why You Why Why Why You Thrice
Oh, actress, feel it
Take it and tell me why you did it
If you do it again, I'll take your mother to death
Hey Baba, this movie feels very important
you got it? Show me now
!Bro
Who was talking
Medium
Look at this here, dad John Thoridy
The world's famous gangster from Utopia
Do not worry, he's the producer of our movie
Mr. Tridee is the author of ours, Mr. Paron
Very good writer
Sorry
How much do you not get?
No, what's your point
My daddy is a great writer
... wrote so much a big movie
Which movie did you write?
What can i say now
what do I say! What was the movie
The whole movie the actor tells me what to say
No, it's a lie
This is a lie, she was a good film, she liked it
The false tale of the truthful man, what he wrote
Okay, you're miles
You Miley, Hollywood movie, English as well
Now tell me your money, Dada
My brother is a family member, please give me one
... you know Dada Yeah
One crunch is so much, how are you?
Thirty percent discount
Seventy lacquer, finished
It is very worthwhile
Yeah, you just rub your lash, you're mine
DVD movie, I want to see
Do not do this, it will die
Sir
Oh God, where do I go from now on?
Elo
Paron, Baba-
Which daddy Sanjo Baba
Shut up, your brain flawed
Baba Amar, the literary width
Do this movie
Come here, I'll do something for you
No no, daddy, I do not need your work
I got a movie, with the famous director, Goldie Kapoor
Where did this sound of bullets come from?
Filming is taking place, Police besieged the mafia group
Come on, shoot more bullets, also a gangster
Should not stay alive
Okay, daddy, I'll go
O God, if you know Dad about Don and do not know about Dad
My guys are surrounded by me
Mr. on this side
I am on my behalf
Chief Badag Singh
Come on, ordering you from now on, you
With Gupta you have nothing to do
If from now on, you will deal badly with them
You're in this country, not you, not your group, not the réistone
I do not see you
That's the kind of person you've come to here
Then you sat down before them
I apologize for this
Your Name?
I'm called the boss
Bob did not remember you as a child, someone is yours
Say, give your full name
Things, Gajinder Singh
Who tells you the boss?
Okay, who sent you?
Something, my friend sent me
I'm sorry
His father's name is Da Vinzer Sinhe, his father is Mahnaj Komaray
From yuppies
What's up sir
Tell all the cities of Utopia
Yupi cities, oh, you
Campus, Mahadiou, Vince Parad
Pretium, sorry sir
Sir, you know, thank you sir, for your sight
I was happy, I became happy, I became glad
Geographic information saved
You are a very good person
Gupta, what should we do with you now?
You are a commercial com pany that makes up 10 of
Shops for dadash
No no
15? -
20? -
OK. Automatically
I do not have
Come on automatically
Thanks -
My heart is that I have nothing
You do not interfere
He is a helicopter partner
With the Minister of Political Affairs
This decision can only take it
The result of thinking and deciding you is not my essence
The result is in line with our decisions
How valuable is this palace?
Sir, at least 7 million crore
What do you say buddy
You see that part of the right, making it there
Baba, we need to write the script
Let's write the script that you can not write here
Look at the palace
Did you write a good scene?
Right now he defined a good scene -
Really?
There was a scene in your home -
What's up with the Hindus?
Home -
... you're at home in the morning
... birds are singing
... The sun is coming up
... the color of the whole orange ozonation
... think, my wife, Sapna
... His hair is thrown over his shoulders
... with an orange sari
His hand is coconut and he's walking
Coconut
... The coconut that you have in the tray of prayer
Going to your feet
My foot?
Daddy you are the Holy Prophet for your brother
God are you
Is Sapena doing that?
It does not matter
What a lovely scene
How much do you want?
Uncle
Come
! Sapna -
What do you do, you gave us all this?
Get it back
No, no, you get it, you guys do not mind this
What did you do
Lightweight
Daddy John, for a movie
... be real
I wanted to ask you how you and your wife were from
Separated?
It was a very bad day
Stephanie, you helped us
Caused Sapna's misconception
Sapena, you made a mistake
Sapnaaa
I do not wanna be widowed
For this very healthy year
I'm not mistaken
I'm still not a mother, I'm so good for you
Stephanie
You're wrong
... Stephanie's husband
That jeoparded me for my sake
Because of that, I am here now here
I am happy and happy
... think now
.... you and me
I understand these assumptions very well
Stephanie is friends
.... so much so that you
You wanted to make that foreigner out of this house
You wanted to do it to me
Repent repentance
What do you say, you fall asleep like that
I could not do it
Do you remember the early marriage of Sapna?
You always asked, I'm cumming?
Where do I go, when will I go?
What am I doing for you?
I defined you for my work
How much did you like me
Not
It was doubtful
I always doubted you
You're skeptical
...O God
What else? -
Now I'm sick?
That girl, what's up?
I can not stand it again
Everything is fine, you do not trust your husband
Do not you trust
Talk to me and what else you have
What's the good thing Han
Well then I'm not using it anyway
Sapena is coming
you got it?
I did not mean that-
!I did not mean that
.... sapnaaaaa
Sapena
Brother
She's gone, why are you crying? -
I felt sentimental
What is the emotion -
... Daddy ... My wife, Sapna
Stop daddy
Daddy John Wonderful
Mishra helicopter, you must have heard my name
Yeah i heard
You went too high upstairs
But what's up there, Yeah
Did you come to this day today?
What would I tell you if he wanted John a few years ago
Like you somebody
Now, I've become bigger than you
Today i am juluto
So big to see me here?
And you're new to bending and respecting me?
What do i say Son of a friend, respect
I learned the older from childhood
I was a simple man, I changed my life
Without medication, and in the hospital, I will get the name of God
Little by little, I learned a very important subject
... that if the world has something worthwhile
That pile
You know, John, I've got a rupee, too
I can bear it
Then you lost your life to 70 crore
... I'm for my money
I can bend and bend the rest
They need to be horizontal
Do not you wise
How many times have you told me, in the middle of the letter?
I'm talking, blond guy, he's getting it
Fool
... I know it's so shameful
... if that land that you named yourself
I can not get back to you
If you were so big a name
It was not necessary to go back to Gupta
If I am the head of this
I'm not going to leave you in two steps
... hahahaha
Try to understand
That you understand something to others
First you must be wise
Intagram Bollywood Van
@ Bolly1official
Remember Goddess
Give the name of your mind
Watch out for us
Remember the goddess, remember the name of the goddess
Take care, take care of us
If it's God's shank
Hey goddess
One and only one hundred and one
I want to know more about you
Someone who miracles you, you guys
When your blood is in your current vein
Adam will be like kings
The soul will reappear again
Like a king
When to quarrel
Out of the eyes comes out fire
You are attacked from the four sides
Ears are torn when you call her
Wait another day, do not go from here
You go, then stop him
I accepted that
Why do not you accept?
You are against the whole world
The day I got in the Ganga River
My whole body stretched out
The way things are done
The whole city knows me as a psychologist, but
They make a mistake
Sapna Dupe
Homecoming ghetto
Here and there, the road to fights, but when you go
The poor will change completely
It's the same for me
Look what happens to you, because of your husband
When you go, you think the camera is hidden
Suspicious talk, marble nights
Foreign hands around her hair
Namely, you got stuck at home
Hello Goddess
Why are you so tired?
what has happened?
It's all because of these hackers
I understand, I found a supplier for this
One that has a lot of money
That is a strange name, they have died
He has a lot of money, so if you give him two crates, tell him 6 crore
Later channeled, 25% down
Once again, you will get the money that we will divide
There is a little problem, he is
Do not you
I'm impressed by your story, you're a lover
You are real
Husband are very effective in returning a woman
You are making films, how romantic they are
Why do not you play the first role?
Very handsome, handsome
What better way to play this game
You are awesome
I like Sapna very much
I can not make love to her
Dada, you speak like God
I play this movie, I'm playing the movie
We found the actress
Okay Malice Let's talk about your wages
How much do you want for this movie?
Who was talking about money for you now?
I'll give you a special discount
Only 9 crore
What
Enough, it's just a little 9 crore-
Give her a pillow
Come on eat, everything is fine
In fact, it's the doctor's pill to make love to with his wife
... gave him
Lucky is wrong, he has already lost his pill
It's one, nine, three
Daddy John felt good
And that marmalican mosque used to do this
Come on and touch me
What does the car make, what does it do here? To
What have you come
what has happened?
If you come here, it will burn all over
Come and make your dreams come true
Come to my arms
Your wife is here! You did not tell me
Where is dupe
Scroll Lucknow-
When
Yesterday-
Did I send the paper that I sent, or not?
When not, how to read?
Come inside
How do you tell your dad inside? They swear they will not come home
What's inside the house?
The song is playing
Okay, I'll tell you a secret
What a secret
Uncle's Secret -
Uncle?
She promised to play actress Bojpuri, who plays her
She's talking to her uncle
Oof, this is my tribute to John Adam
Bride
You came my daughter! Very good, you're alive
My name is me
what has happened?
I never thought you'd be so posted
I?
You must be embarrassed
Embarrassing
What did I do?
With your disdain, your dignity was saved
But what did you say to the bride?
we do not know
Oof, with whom I will give you this
Uncle why do you look sick?
Mona is your life like a Chinese movie
What you see and see but nothing happens
what do you mean?
The bride came last night when you were having love and being
Is Sapena Coming?
So why did not anyone tell me anything?
Your dad was busy with love and now
Fun?
Let's take your car
go fast
We do not need your movie again, come back to Bombay, your wife
She has sent a divorce letter, and her case is going to dissuade her
what are you saying?
Take the car
If she returns to her, the movie closes me, from
Where do I make money then?
I have to do something
Come on car, wait for you
Why are you bothering me?
I want to get you Juventon
I'll throw you
I do not want to explain to you-
what do you mean?
The woman in charge wants you to do the same -
You were afraid to take a divorce letter to the foot of Zenton
Forgive me, tell me whatever I do
Do not be so big, your wife can be
I can not be a slave to anyone
I tell you what you should do
Call and tell me to get ready for divorce
Divorce I love him
I know, but as you wanted to
Look for it, it will be your side
simply
Call
Catch
Pinky, her sister's rang
You see, it was dismounted
Hello
Sapena
Are you divorced?
Ok send yours
Morsi was awesome
Pinky became miserable
Do not cry sister
Dupe, I can not do that
Somebody sends a dope from behind
There is one who is driving the rear seat
Abjehi, Malika Kapoor
Malika Kapoor, welcome
What happiness do you see right?
Salafi
Sure-
Malica John, what did you do in the movie
As you, your deceiver husband, have taught you
My heart was crazy
I love it
Are you in the boutique of Sapna, my suit and trousers?
Guy
Yes, Sure
Classical-
Yes, what's the size?
Height 180
Wide scoops
Chest 56
Malika Jan, there are only two people of this size
One of my babies, one is Mr. Dupe
Hey Pinky
Take two three to one coat with the size of your sister's husband
Honestly, my husband was the same
Was?
Just divorced my phone right now
Oh, I'm sorry
But you are so normal
You say sorry, she divorced me, I am
I gave her a divorce
Malica John, my name is Sapna Dupe, nobody dares
... do not get in touch with me, then you call the phone
What do you like?
Bright gray, packaged?
Yes, be sure to pack your pink, Yeah
Drink a cool drink
Did you survive the 3rd check of your dash?
I like it
my share
Prepare yourself for a lifelong contribution. Gouldy
Great how are you
Easily, Sapna Dupe from John A. Augustine's life
Malice arrived
You know what I say
This is Miss Malika
For her thief
OK
It is
For a beautiful night, a new friend's new life
with love
Uncle, who was he?
Who sent me
I do not know-
Sapena
I said no?
Do you call bk Sister husband
Phone rings
Listen, take it yourself
Hello
I am
I know
I know-
Sapena, you've done a lot of work that you did
Did you really want this?
Who does not want this foolish man?
Mr. Dupe, I sent a mistake
Wrong or true, at least you did the right thing
I'm so glad that I did not think
Where is the Divorce?
Divorce
I said about the flower
Flower?
What did you send with suit?
Which jacket are you? -
This gray coat
You swoon the dog for you, you do not understand
Dog?
shut
That's what I see
Professional translation and audio translation from the Bolivu Web site
Bollywood1.Co
Mona
Wowie is like me
who are you?
I'm acting
Pony Singh, it's quite like you
I was looking for a role, I heard that they made a new movie here
Sir, there are two more tragedies here
Kill her two
Bollywood Van Talking Telegram
@Bollywood1official
Turn on the car
Go
Uncle, strain your blood strain
Car out
Intagram Bollywood Van
@ Bolly1official
... who sent you to kill me
You did not tell me that I did not run away, I ran away
Tell him who killed you and your dear
Davy Diall Dupe known as Trydi
This time you can not understand the lamb
Say, speak for a few minutes
Death is not with anyone who owns the business itself
Long live the moon
This is not lost
Elo
Sapna-
are you well?
Saw I'm fine.
I wanted to know that it was not something
... no sapena, I am without you
I'm stopping another, bypass
Worry
Hey Mishra, you were saved by the phone of a woman
Otherwise, it was your corpse
Thank you woman!
What do you do Do you want to kill me
Good day, give you a little alms
Long live the moon
Well, sir, you're out, very eaten, and you're out of the way
Hey what's up
Drinking, he tells you the truth
When I'm upright, I'm not lying
Whatever you say, you tell it, apart from the truth
You say something
You are a nonsense writer
cheers
You saw right.
Do you all know
My dad John, hello
Hey, we're hard at work, all we have to say is silent
That gangster, whatever he says, silences him
why are you laughing? Fine, go
What did you die
When I'm upright, I'm not lying
Shut up
You hat all of you, I've hat on you
You know that you've lost 11 corners, now, each
Missing you in the 11th week
Sir sir
I'm looking for you
What was your dear director? Moody's Astonish
What did you drink in my drink?
This is the penny
I'm Pany, I'm proud
I saw the movie Darda Mona very much, I'm a director
I could not have thought that I was awaiting you
what's up here?
Mr. Director, it's now my movie hero-
Champion?
John's dad is superb
How are you?
Where is Trida?
If you tell her, she'll be very good
I'm sorry for you
where is it?
we do not know-
The world's best actor
Darmandra Jay, Sunny J.
Now Pony Jay
Just a few minutes later, he told Gaudy the actress
I'll be a star
I'm so sad about you
Malika Mrs.
Then I did not talk to you that night -
I sent flowers, suit, I called several times
I forgot you did not
I know you're so busy
Did you speak English, Punjabi?
How cute
For Sapena, you learned English, for the sake
Am I Punjabi
You know, Talibin says my couple are wonderful
... you know what I mean
Come
What are they doing?
I'm doing it
Why i do not want to
Because i'm doing
You kay hseni
This is Panic Singh, the film's hero
You were using me too
You came to me
Very few, I can not work with this little person
listen
English no, Punjabi, please-
You are so nice and attractive that everyone wants them to be with you
Can not you die
Charming charm
My suit
Do not coat, filmed, hurry-
Get out of the kids, light
I make this coconut?
Uncle, leave this scene okay, and then you break the coconut
You see me happy
!Sorry-
My dialogue
Do not fight
I'm practicing a dialogue
What is dialogue pony
You see me happy
Say goodbye, just say that
You do not understand
I'm the Actor
Hey, let's sit on the kids
The dialogue is very good for the same time
Hey, you can say goodbye, you do not get a good dialogue
Are you insulting
No, it's a good dialogue.
Punjabi Tap, Take Yupa
Goalie do something
Dear writer, the sun set, what's up here?
Your dad brought your life
You are directing, telling me, you made several films
Go tell her
Now tells him
I'm ready
!What's going on-
Let's go
One tells me where to break this coconut
I'll tell you whenever you need to break it-
So when?
Move-
You see me happy
O God
cut
Complete the dialogue Dada-
Sapena
you are good?
Spencer, you're so beautiful in Sari
But you're not good at all
This is an unlucky suit
Disloyalty?-
Yes, yes, suit, Ms. Gamegather's choice
Gift card
You gave me a gift -
You divorce me on my phone line, I'll send you a suit
Is this possible?
no it's not-
Listen to something else I did not come to see you
I did not come to see the filming
I've come to see you make your movie a hero once
I'm evil
Your wife is not evil, you are the goddess of God
Greeting
My name is Sapna Dupa.
Of course I know-
No one defines this poor, you tell us in our industry
the writer
I am the parony of the ear
I'm Goddie
Yes, Mr. Goldie Kapoor, I'm on my side
What sweet
I saw all your films-
You really make a very good movie
Okay, tell me what the scene is and Sapna DuPa
You want to do
The woman has a good dialogue
Look at her brother's wife here.
In the Ganges River you will drive two boats
You are one of us, and you are one of them, John, you tried
It gets you
No, no, no such thing happened at all
Dunbar Paron
My dun paron
It was not so
So how was that? -
It was such ... how was it?
... I do not know if he gave me a reminder or not
... how is it possible?
How can i forget
Do you remember Celebration of color
Hey Mona, the time you did not have a gun
I lit a cigar with a bullet
Looks like you do not like yourself
I love your daughter so much
Or give it to me, or take me off
Let me take you later, first tell me my daughter
Have you accepted
We did not think we would get your permission first, that's his lifetime
He intends to first of all take great pleasure
Later we will meet it
If that answer is rejected?
We force it-
He's going to get the bride
The first answer is yes and your good prayer
I just sneezed, I did not say anything
I really liked your confidence
... I'm so glad on my behalf
The answer is yes
Father, if your answer is yes, why do not you go with it?
I?-
Where do you look at your dad? Answer it
What this answer is
I answer
I do not want to marry you
Why you have a problem
Shut up, I have no trouble you have
... I am giving this to a wise guy
Ignorant ignorant
I do not marry the ignorant sailor
My husband and I have to come together, completely English
I get married with an educated person
Go away, do not go with you
Do not you? -
Hey, my daughter is completely right, go away
Hear it or not, spit it out
Little stars are flashing, I'm Terti
I love you
Great, who does not know the alphabet, because of his love
Learn a perfect song
How romantic your dad John is
Very romantic
bull sheet-
Tricked me
To learn English, to learn English
As soon as I got stuck, you remember English
Then all this, it must be a romantic song
Have
Come on, I got your color to myself
Come on and paint me as you want
I swear by God that your eyes are innocent
I want to live in my eyes
cut
Who is the director, who is the man who dreams this way?
That's wrong, this guy thought to be Dickish
Beautiful
What a beautiful thing Man must be
I'm gonna waste my time
I swear by God that you have a blind eye
I want to live in your eyes
I swear by God that you have infinite eyes
I want you to live in my eyes
My heart wants to stay here
I'm drowning the whole day
Your eyes make me crazy
Look, tonight tonight to Pasta
Think that it's Diwaliyah tonight
Without you I do not want to miss a moment
you are my world
Your color has astonished me
I'm drowning the whole day
Ok, it's over
We run the body scene, bring a corpse
The body wants
I murdered him
say
Daddy Jaysi, the director wants a body
What I killed the one just now
Afterwards
Okay, I'm going
Let's take it, people, when they are not filming
Then you were tormented by your death
In the last 10 minutes, this person has not changed his heart
What is a pledge, then cumulate the video
In the next movie, I give her a dead role, with a dialogue
I took that number a long time ago
The new director wants to get the number
Does not know
My daddy, my friend, is a penny
Is here now
what to do now?
I do not know-
Do not stop filming
Why shut down? -
Outside the police
Okay, we're letting the video go
... have permission, but that corpse
I know it is hana
It's the body of the corpse
His job is to make money, which is a corpse.
Shut your dad
What to shut up do not shut up--
You're crazy to say that you are mad. Actor, that's fine
He plays the role
Hey shut up
stand up
Look at him
I was impressed, you will play the next movie
With the dialogue
OK? Now finish the game
That fellow. is dead
Take it from here
We saved him. What did your body do?
I put it in an old car
I see
What what have you done? Have you thrown a car in the car of the commissar?
Elo
This time it was just water, next time it might be acid-
Who is talking
I do not know-
Lucky
Good luck you saved this time
... Daddy will give you John. Otherwise
Watch the movie or else you will find your body
I'm filming
He was talking like a chain killer. I'm terrified
Did you cut off the phone or I'll cut it off
O God, the phone is cut off or your neck
Dada was a beautiful dialog
! The woman is afraid of dry skin, you think of a dialogue
shame on you
you do not worry-
My dad is knowing, it's the job of someone
Will not be forgiven
The wife of Dadash Sapena. please come
Mrs. Malice is very upset, but she should come
Because Dupe has a lot of enemies
what do you mean?
Someone may attack him at any one time
It's always your knife in your pocket
Goldie
The right woman tells her that everyone is near her
At any moment, it may be gone forever
Max, Madan, Moan, Morley
Shut up Lucky-
!what has happened? Why are you afraid of Malice?
My name starts with M, Malika
Goldie
I was very stressed here
But now that's fine here
Mrs. Malice, do not worry, I've come to sit again
Hello
Do you know when he rang?
We are trying hard to stop the phone from answering.
We are afraid that someone will threaten the Dupean family
Okay
We'll solve it first, understand who it is who is us
Annoying
The renowned Utopian, his dad John Teredy
The movie is made
Now he's dying to give you a great gift,
Your name is a helicopter, that bitch is flying
Stop it! Your dad John Dadish John
My ear filled with his name
The bitch also has the name of the offender who is going forward
Going
I do not destroy it, I'm not a Mishra helicopter
Chowtha, go and kill his female actress and bring him here
who is it?
Bob says Tridy
Mishra, do you want to kill my actor?
Do you want to close my movie?
Catch the phone, my idiot is the head of your every single person
Separating
I will not live
Cut off
But heard the whole thing again?
He heard
Do not miss it, darling
Frightened
Who was who What is the phone?
Get your phone on
My dad is all over
I'm thinking of something, I've got John on that side
How do you know?
Do not be afraid, darling, there was no chance at all
Call
It was not the time for the call, the phone was all silent
Well then, where did I find out what I think of?
Relax.
... I mean, I think of something,
no no no
I do not think - you think
I do not think anymore
Hello my dad
Help our dad, we are the family of the soldier
We are the army
We all gave the martyr country
This is the son of this brother
!My husband
Everything the Earth gave us, Mishra helicopter force
Took us from
We tried hard to fight the enemies in the country
But we lost this battle
I respect the army more than anyone else
And an army will never fail
Hey Mishra, see who is here
I will not go anywhere without inviting you, if I go, it looks like you
Why did I come until I told her why
Can not breathe
Like you
Mishra breathe, sit down
Daddy John, you are our guest, what can I do?
To do you
I just want the plots of the widows
Why are your dad guilty of looking for these widows?
I heard that for the sake of a widow, the wife of her husband sent you
Now you are looking for this widow, think
! What does the woman do?
Oh, Miashra jokes
I did not say that
You do not know the woman you give Sapna
If my daddy suppena understands that you made me joke with me
You are every single bare alley you rotate
Oh, oh, do not be here, look
no it's not-
To say this is a joke
You're so funny
Give me the sanda
come and get it
One joke to be happy, sign up
Do you know the price of this land?
A project of seven hundred cores
Why do not you bother yourself?
See how much the widows land
Double it
You know, John, you and I can go to Varanasi
We rule
Take my hand and see for yourself
Mishra is very smart
What did you suggest?
But I have to ask you two questions
Ask ok, what's the fear for what?
Question 1: Who is the King of the Forest?
Lion
Adrian was very good
Second Question: What is the lowest of the world?
How are you?
Man-
A man like you
Is this your life? Insulting
Long live the moon
The camera comes out here, it's a good shot
Do you shoot me the shot?
Let's take one or two of my beautiful scene
A moment
Yes?
Director, shut this movie
Otherwise, I will tick and you will be in the alley of Varanasi
Do you think
Again, if I'm alive, I'm not bulletproof, with a bomb
Exploding
just a moment
Explode
Who is talking
Hello, my dear John-
Sorry
! Lucky-
Sorry my wife
The whole map was ruined
Lucky was not afraid to start filming
Lady Malice, you were in danger because of me
Purpose?
My wife, Sapena
Sapena wants Malice to go and the filming will be closed
Why not shut the video?
What do I do with movies? I want Sapena to come back
Now Darwak gets jealous
John Darwach's messenger, because the filming continues
... if the video is shut down
Who else is the one to decide on the scene?
You go, we have a new author
His dad is writing
A true story
What does his dad write, who is he?
No, no, my wife, I'm taking a fire from jealousy
I want to be more fun
I want to accept all the conditions
Promise that he never doubts me
Panning Singh, Dupe is playing with me
But he does not know that I'm the hero of this game
Do you have a wife, do not you? Why are you telling me?
You have to express your passion
So I burn the dope out of jealousy
I want to make me jealous
Goodbye, I'm going to make him afraid
You're coming along
Daddy dan
the light-
The camera has to be here, it's a great scene
Pinky, I'll break this neck
This is my dear actor
Your sister's husband?
Saw Saw, no, no, I'm Pany-
The wife of her dignified wisdom
Hello. Today you are helping me with great gratitude
My friend pani
I can do anything for you-
I swear to Goddess, I'm very angry now
There's a lot of fire now
It has come
Lets start
What are you doing, Go Onur!
Come on, Pany, talk with more emotions
Malika Mrs.
This blue squirrel looks very much for you
You are sorry
Today, you ... come on, sit next to me
Such situations are low
Pani
Poniot is calling, sir, where do you go?
Pony Go Onur
Look here, there's something back-
look
Come closer
Come close
Do not touch your hand
what happened?-
Look at Pony, what is she going to eat with her eyes
what's up here?
I do not know, I did not write it
I say so good
You can not trust anything in this world anymore
You see what it's like to do with your cheesecake
It's very obvious
... Now I do not dupe, I'll give her a lesson
Sapena
Tride, help Mrs. Tride
Do not wait, go away
I do not need anyone's help
What is this
Today my heart is shaky
How do you go where do you go? She is wounded, why are you?
Taken?
come here
Wissa here, I'm going to be working again
Today space is not suitable. Filming tomorrow
Space is not good! Filming tomorrow
Still, the movie does not come out to you, dialogue
You can not tell, you have the Punjabi dialect
You will work half an hour at 6 o'clock, tomorrow
Take pictures!
Let's understand it
Come on, actress, talk calmly with her -
I tell him you come in, calmly
What are you doing here? Because you're the producer
Come on, I can not keep my dialog
With a slip? Shut up
Malika come here
This is a very interesting scene, here for your first time here
You want to tell how much you like it
OK?
sister
Excellent
Feel free to cry -
First impression
Move-
Move
Vasya Sapena
If you go today, you will never know what your heart is doing
When you've gone, you're waiting for each moment
Sounds like you think
The phone rings, I think your phone
Sometimes I feel you did not go
Right now your sister's voice came and you were on
Daddy chose your name correctly
Really you're like a dream
Everywhere you see, my world is stopped there
Every time I get you, I'm laughing at you
You say, without me I can live?
Without you, Sapna I'm flawed
Cut was great
Elo
my child
What a great surprise to Baba John
Why did not you call I went to the airport for you
My daughter, who am I? Well, I remember tomorrow's anniversary of your marriage
So I came. Are you surprised?
Tomorrow is a great day. So I'm happy for you
I prayed for a ceremony
Where is your husband?
The woman is dead
Pony Singh, I got into trouble
Tomorrow, Baba Jun will be celebrating the anniversary of the wedding
I'm going to dope
Are you crazy Do you want to be my husband and come?
Okay, I'll tell her
Mr. Pany Singh, I am giving myself part
Be sure to bring the dope
I do not want to know the problem of our relationship with us
Okay, come
come and sit
Happy anniversary
Congratulations
Good luck to the kids, I promise you that
Remind me to be together
The foundation of the marriage is based on trust
Never question the trust of each other
Trust in the failure to bring it back
Intagram Bollywood Van
@ Bolly1official
Mona
Sapna Dupe, I'm so annoyed, now it's my turn
I've heard her follow the wife of her brother
You are looking
Did not you find it Thinking that you did not want the woman to give you
Kill herself
It fell for me
My wife, I'm alone
I will send you a degree
My wife is in front of me
If you're gonna kill me like a good husband
come here
I'm waiting for you
The Wisdom of God's Dad
Sapna-
Sign this a few tabs
After this, all of Umwalton will be for me
Sapena
Hey, daddy John is there, look
Dupe
Mishra
Let's take her wife-
Sapena
Honestly, what I saw was right?
... Otherwise, I am
Sapna I'm telling it right
They are all round
Swear to me
Sapna is sworn to you, it's all wrong.
I'm telling the truth
is anybody there? Save me
After the birth of the children, Mrs. Sapna Dupe head
Busy
The skepticism was over
The life of my lord, now, was going well
About Pony Singh, she is marvelous with Malika Kapoor
Dawsh's movie is a great soul to succeed
Translator: Sepideh and Yasin
The Best of Indian Cinema on the Bollywood Web Site
Bollywood1.Co
What do you want your dad
Dear Mishra, you are the name
Both went to the wind
At least a good spit
I'm very sad
I want to do it from you
I want to make my biography
People should be aware of what the danger was
Say my soul
Money, what's your budget?
One hundred crore
You say yes
Now let's face it
What's the name of the movie?
Let's take a biography of Mr. Mischa
This song was translated at the beginning of the film
Visit the Bollywood Wave site to order the movie