Sabarwal International school..
..is one of the top five schools in India.
Straight  and one..
Our teachers are not just from India..
..they come from abroad too.
Very good  now put your hands down.
The motto of our school is..
Education is the Birth Right of every Child.
Very nice. - But..
I cannot help you with your nephew's admission.
I mean...
Look at this.
You can forget about fifth grade.
According to our school standards..
..we cannot admit him in second grade either.
Look at him.
He's only interested in playing video-games.
Sorry  sir.
Whenever Bittoo's nervous  he starts playing.
Since his parents demise  he's got only two supports.
Rimpi  and that PSP.
He's completely addicted to it.
But  don't worry.
I'll personally do his homework and projects.
Like all other parents.
Just.. admit him in your school  Mr. Principal.
What's this?
Gift for sister-in-law. - What nonsense!
Get out! Get out!
Not out  look in. In!
There's more.
Rascal!
You dare try to do a Sting operation on me.
You think you're some kind of a hero.
Who sent you?
You will be the star tomorrow  sir.
When you'll have more media people running after you..
..than Aamir Khan.
'Kabootar'! - 'Kabootar?'
Hey  what are you doing?
Good morning  sir.
Good morning.
Why do you follow me? Why do you pull me back?
Why are you after me?
Come face me  and I'll slap you hard.
Everyone say with me.
Play on.
You'll face the music.
Yes  you'll face the music.
You eat my bread and snap at me!
You look like a dog.
If you come back  I'll slap you again.
Everyone say with me.
Play on.
Girlfriend tells her boyfriend to quickly remove her top.
Boyfriend says okay.
Play on. - And then girlfriend tells her boyfriend..
..to now remove her skirt.
Boyfriend says okay.
Girlfriend scolds and says... Dare you wear my clothes again!
It's either this guy or that.. just play on.
Play on.
Here or there  just play on.
It's either this guy or that.. just play on.
Play on.
Sukhi!
Did you get admission? When are the exams?
Sooner than you expect
The principal's right behind us with the exam sheets.
Let him come.
Balloo. Gun!
Is he a principal or a shooter?
Balloo!
Sukhi  are you having fun?
It's just like when we used to..
..flee from Agarwal's house with the noodles.
But  Agarwal never fired at us.
This way. - Stop.
Stop  you rascals.
There you go  mom.
Our local cable's ready to broadcast breaking news.
Shall I press the button? - No  'Kabootar'.
This game's all about 'timing'.
This goes on air only when I get the message from Ballu.
Wait.
Rascals! Come out!
You think you can make breaking news out of me.
Rascals!
You don't know who I am.
Mr. Sethi  we're your true admirers.
And  we want to make you famous.
If you don't believe us  call your wife. - Wife?
What did you two did with my wife?
Lover-boy. When you don't do anything with your wife..
..what do you expect us to do? Dance?
Stop firing. It'll just make things worse.
Call your wife.
Hello. - Hello. Pammi.
How are you? - What's wrong with me?
Nothing. I was worried.
Okay  I'll call you later. - Okay.
Listen. - Yeah.
I love you. - I love you too  baby.
Lover-boy. Ask your wife to switch on the local news.
Pammi  switch on the television. - Okay.
Just a minute.
Sabarwal International school..
Oh  my God!
You never told me..
..that your interview's coming on television.
Oh  so exciting.
I've to tell my friends  okay.
Okay  bye.
Rascals. What's this nonsense?
Come out. I'm throwing down my gun.
Fine  we'll stop this nonsense.
You can ask your wife to check again.
What do you want? - 500 million.
500 million? - In cash.
I don't have that kind of money.
You rob the parents in the name of education.
And now you say you don't have the money.
You guys must have made around 700-800 million..
..with admissions and donations alone.
We're only asking for 500.
Please believe me.
I might have around 150 to 200 million  in cash.
300 million  final. - Look..
That's a small price for Sabarwal's reputation.
Yeah.
And  the admissions are still going on now.
This scandal can cost you dearly.
What's the guarantee that you won't make copies?
Mister. You think we're selling you water-pump..
..that you're demanding guarantee.
We aren't putting a bullet through your head.
Consider that a guarantee.
Fine. When and where do you want the money delivered?
Come to Hyder Kholi  Chandni Chowk by 1 pm.
And wait for our call.
You think Rs.2000 is a measly amount.
Tell me.
Forgive me  sir.
It was a mistake.
Your existence is the biggest mistake.
Fool!
Take a look  Mr. Sethi.
He's apologising after losing Rs.2000.
You know what it's worth when you try to earn it.
So  what brought you here?
I..
Actually  I...
You didn't visit the school for a long time.
So  I just wanted to make sure everything's fine.
What's wrong with me?
The Yoga teacher in school..
..has made me fit.
Everything's okay.
Hello.
Not a rupee less  understand?
Who are you  madam.. - I'll do the talking.
And  listen carefully  I am not going to repeat it. - Yes.
Keep the bag of money at Bashir Miya's shop..
..which is exactly opposite Nandu bread-maker.
Yes.
Then go to Nandu's shop and say..
..Three radish stuffed bread  with extra butter.
That's your codeword.
Say that  and he'll give you the PSP.
What's my account?
The total's 460.
Give me another box and a betel leaf.
The total then comes to 500.
Yes  mister. What do you want? - Nothing.
Nandu Bread-maker.. - That's the one. Right there.
That one? - Yes.
Come one  come all.
'Aalu Paratha  Gobi Paratha  Paneer Paratha'.
Pour me some more gravy  son.
Aunt  do you want to bathe in the gravy?
There you go  aunt. - That's not your problem  son.
'Aalu Paratha  Gobi Paratha.
Yes  mister 'Aalu Paratha  Gobi Paratha  Paneer Paratha'.
Three Muli Paratha's with extra butter. - Okay.
Three Muli Paratha's...and extra butter..
Smeared or poured?
Smeared. - Okay.
Smeared with extra butter. - Some more gravy  son.
Here you go  aunt.
What's this?
Rascal. What's this nonsense? - Quiet.
What's going on? - Quiet.
Where's my tape?
Let go my collar.
I was told whoever orders three Muli Parathas..
..smeared with extra butter  give this calculator to him.
That's what I did.
Oh no!
Move back! Move back! Move back!
Move back!
What's your name? - Bashir Miya.
What's wrong  sir?
Bomb! Bomb! Bomb! Bomb!
Did you find the bag? -We've found the bag.
Where?
Next to Bashir Miya Paan Centre at Chandni Chowk.
Yes  it's a black bag.
Move back!
Bomb! Bomb! Bomb! Bomb!
Bomb!
Who are you?
I am the principal.
School? - Yes.
Principal sir  please move back.
Let the police do their job.
Move back.
Two more bags found in the middle of the road.
Please repeat the location.
Mid chowki  we've found two more bags here.
It's a serial bombing matter.
We'll be right there  over.
Harbat.
Move.
Bomb! Bomb!
Take the car at the back.
Hello. - Hello.
Are you Jasveer Baweja.
Yes.
Where's your son Sukhwinder.
He's gone out for some important work.
Please  come in.
What are you two doing here?
Did you diffuse the bomb on the road?
The bomb's exploding in here.
This suit's hot like an oven.
My leg's completely cooked.
Take a look.
Food's the only thing on your mind.
Take a look yourself.
You should've seen the look on the principal's face.
He couldn't understand..
..why the police's taking his 300 million?
Whose plan was it after all?
Ballu the great  with my aunt's blessings.
By the way  did you take a course in acting as well?
You see  when your life's on the line..
..the worst actor can give the best performance.
Don't worry  brother. I am there.
The 'Biryani's' ready. Please taste it.
The one for tonight? - Yes.
The rice is not completely cooked. - Okay.
Let it steam for another 15 minutes. - Okay.
Leave that here  I'll finish it.
Let it be  you don't need to take the trouble.
Look.. - My son  Sukhi.
And they are his friends. - Hello.
Hello  sir. - Hello. Hello.
I'm getting a call.
Jeet.
Here's your treasure.
You see  aunt.
He installs the connections..
..and makes us hold the set-top boxes.
Hold it.
Goodbye. - Bye.
See you again. - Okay.
Sukhi.
Mintu  what a twist.
We're in a big mess.
70 people have filed a case against us.
If we don't return them their money..
..our house will be auctioned.
They can't auction our house.
Who do they think they are?
Sukhi.
It was an order for a grand wedding.
The food was so delicious  I brought it for you.
The mince-meat's really tasty. - Yeah.
Kailash kept stirring it for two hours.
You know. It's still a little uncooked.
Should've let it cook some more.
Nonsense.
Thank God! We were successful in our plan.
And it was a big victory too.
We got the money  and video evidence against Sethi.
After all  who made the film? - The film's yet to be made  son.
We just managed to sum-up 300 million.
We need 1.2billion more.
Think.
I know you don't like this.
If you were alive  you wouldn't have let us do this.
Remember  you would always catch me cheating in rummy.
But  Mr. Baweja..
..some mess can be cleaned only by crooked ways.
We don't have another choice.
Ravinder Baweja's an asset for our bank.
He's our pride.
Mr. Baweja.
On this occasion  I would like to say that..
..I want this bank to be for the middle-class  and common man.
Where they can keep their money safe..
..and earn good profit.
Thank you.
Sir  according to this scheme..
..how can we give 15% for three months of cash deposit?
Don't worry about the interest.
Try to lock as many people you can in this scheme.
What if someone wants to pay by cheque?
No  Saira. This scheme's for the lower-income group.
And  most of their income's in cash.
This is why Mr. Sabharwal's opened..
..a separate title account for this scheme.
And  you two are the signing authorities.
Here you go  Mr. Baweja.
I had a small flat in Dwarka.
I sold that and brought 900 000 for you
These are some of my savings.
Take these.
The scheme certificate.
Saira Madam. What can be a bigger assurance..
..than Mr. Baweja himself.
The scheme's doing really well.
Mr. Gupta  these are the investor's money.
Tally them and keep them safely.
So  what were you up to till 4 am in the morning?
Nothing. I've nothing to do.
Is this the time to come home?
If only you had approved my loan..
..I would've come home on time.
You're drunk. Go on.
Get some sleep. - No  I want to say this.
If he had approved my loan..
..I wouldn't be installing cable-connections in Dariyaganj
I'll hang you by those cables wires. Useless.
Drunkard.
I will. I will drink every day.
I don't want to do this job anymore.
You can do anything you like.
But don't ever come back to this house drunk again.
Fine  I'm leaving Delhi. - Stop  son.
Don't go. Sukhi.
You had to say it.
Sukhi. My son.
He'll be back soon.
She's pampered him too much.
Hello  uncle. Hello  aunty
Diwali's here.
Come. - Happy Diwali.
Don't eat all of them.
Happy Diwali. - Happy Diwali.
Come  sit
Aunt.
Happy Diwali. - Bless you.
She's made my Diwali sad.
She's been upset since Sukhi left.
Sukhi will be back soon.
He's not left home for the first time.
Where is our money?
Will we get our money or not?
We want to know.
Mr. Baweja  what should I do with this?
It's been five months.
When will we get our money?
Mr. Chadda  please calm down. - Why?
The bank will return everyone's money  with interest.
Interest? No  no  no..
We don't want any interest.
We just want our money back.
Has the cat got your tongue?
Just tell us..
Sir  you're handing us over to the police.
We deposited 1.5 billion of the investors..
..in the title account  on your orders.
What money? What title account?
What are you saying  Mr. Baweja?
Mr. Gupta  why don't you say something?
You know I gave you the money.
Yes  Mr. Gupta. Go on.
Sir  he didn't give me any money.
Sir  they are lying. - What?
Baweja. Fraud  cheating with the bank.
I've been serving this bank for 30 years
You know my honesty.. - Shut up!
You can say whatever you want at the police station.
Take them away.
Come on. - Listen to us  sir.. - Come on.
What's going on here?
Why are you making a racket?
Mr. Sabharwal. Hello  sir
My employees Baweja and Saira swindled your money.
You won't get them back..
..by making a racket in the bank.
I want you to go and lodge an FIR against them at the station.
But  still.. - Our money..
Quiet!
Come on. - Leave.
Who's going to return our money now? - Yeah  Who?
The bank has washed their hands from this matter. - Right.
Where's our money?
They can't just disappear.
My name's Chadda. - We will not let take our money. Look. There he is.
Here comes the thief's son.
Okay. - Let him come.
We'll make him pay. - Right.
We gave him our hard earned money.
They can't take our money.
I am sure  Mr. Baweja.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Mom  I want to say something.
I never said this before..
..how much I loved him.
I know he always yelled at me.
But  I always respected his principals.
By God  we'll clear his reputation.
Cheers for marriage  health and wealth. - Cheers.
I've made the best arrangements for the wedding.
Mr. Sabharwal  I feel that's expected.
You see  today's television star..
..and the future film star  that's my son Aman. Right?
Mr. Sabharwal  I feel like you've found a gem.
Do you see the ethics I imbibed in him?
I asked him to get married  and he said yes instantly.
You see  he has 2000 friend requests pending on Facebook.
And  from girls.
But you see  brother.
I will fulfill my promise.
Reception  in Taj Mumbai.
Honeymoon in Europe.
And  1.5 billion  they're all ready.
You've just one daughter.
You're bound to do that much  right?
Yes.
You're right.
Once daughter's married..
..then  I've a few more responsibilities.
Once they're dealt with..
..life will be really peaceful.
Sabharwal  don't worry.
We still have a long way to go?
Which way? Shall I get the car?
Why don't you explain him?
Try to understand what I am saying.
You didn't hear what I said.
You see  I am trying to say..
..once my sister becomes the cabinet minister..
..then  just watch.
I'll get that bank case dismissed completely.
As far as your files are concerned.
I'll get them cleared in a snap.
You.. made me so happy by saying that.
Really..
On that note  he'll tell you a joke.
Go on.
Sir  which one?
Just tell him a joke. - Yes.
Message..
Boyfriend to his girlfriend.
Sweety  come home in the evening
There'll be no one.
Sweety comes home in the evening.
And  there's no one there.
There's..
That's the joke.
What a joke..
Yes  it's true. That's nothing.
There's more. - Stop it  Aman.
I am going to die laughing
You will really get along with papa. - I see.
You've got a wicked sense of humour.
But  you had this innocent look on the reality show.
You see  baby.
That was Aman's strategies to win the reality show.
It's called 'Mind Games' sweetheart.
'Mind Games.' -'Mind Games!'
You smoke? - Of course.
When Aman's happy  he smokes.
But  aren't you doing an anti-smoking campaign on television?
Image  baby. Image.
One has to do it.
And anyway  I charge for it.
You charge for it? - Of course. I'm a celebrity.
Wow! Now  that is hot.
Stop leaching. - I am not leaching..
I'm just admiring the beauty.
What's the time? - Are you getting late?
Yeah! It's time to hit the gym.
Come.
What? - The cable rent.
You charge full rent  but always show half movie.
The rest of it is wasted in ads.
So  we don't make them at home. - Yes  you do.
Do you see her attitude? - Always complaining.
Here you go. Get lost.
No need to come next month.
They think they own us along with the connection.
Sukhi. - Hello.
Hello.
You don't show English movies at night.
Okay  we'll show one at the weekend. - Okay.
You've really grown up.
These beggars don't have a connection. - Hold on  Sukhi.
They're watching C.I.D. mom's favourite serial.
What the.. They're stealing our connection.
Wait.
Who are you? - No need to get personal.
Sukhi  from Jasbeer Cable.
We don't want a connection.
Don't you see that doorbell?
Why were you pounding on the door? - This is just the beginning.
What's going on inside?
'Chikni Chameli's dancing.'
Do you have a problem?
I know you're watching CID.
I can have you jailed for illegal cable connection.
Where are you going?
Stop. Stop.
You don't own it.
Let's settle it over something
Corruption's in your blood.
We're decent people. - We're no thieves either.
So  you are watching CID. - Yes.
Preeto  move aside. Let me watch CID.
Who are you? - Sukhi  from Jasbeer Cable.
Preeto. Move aside. The criminal's about to be caught.
You can watch the repeat.
They've a lot of those.
First  how long have you been watching cable for free?
Since they tried to kill Daya for the first time. You calculate. Move aside.
Attack on Daya.. - Five months.
Sorry. We've been watching since five months.
Since five months. Rs. 1000 for the connection..
..and 250 a month  adds up to Rs.2250.
Are you going to pay here or at the police station?
How about a concession?
We can't give you any concession.
You will have to pay 2250.
We make an honest living.
We still have honest people amongst us.
I've only 150.
I'll adjust the 100 in next month's rent.
Sukhi from Jasbeer Cable.
Tomorrow if you close shop  we'll lose 100 rupees.
Fine  I'll have it sent tomorrow.
We won't close down business for 100 rupees.
Send the rest tomorrow.
What else do you want?
Let's go. What are you looking at?
You haven't finished your second drink yet.
I already finished my third.
What's wrong with you? - Make me another.
By the way..
You know that milk factory job?
I've stationed Kabootar there.
Its done?
You're the best 'Make-shifter' in this world.
No! I've told you many times.
Come after 10 am. - It's Sukhwinder Baweja.
Cable-guy.
Did you stand out here all night? - No.
I couldn't sleep all night.
I had to refund your 100 rupees.
And  my mom says loan is the biggest burden.
Fine. Then  lighten your burden. - Yeah.
Sorry. I've only 50.
I think I lost the remaining 50.
Can I pay you later?
Yes. Of course.
But  don't stay up all night.
What now? - I found 20 more.
It was in the secret pocket.
What's this about? - I've got 10 more.
My beloved.
This time.. I've 500.
Can we go watch the morning show in Saket?
It's the age of love.
Girl  you're soft like butter.
I'm bound to lose my heart.
It's the age of love.
Girl  you're soft like butter.
I'm bound to lose my heart.
My eyes clicked when I saw you.
Your image's posted on my heart.
My heart's.. filled with only your images.
Dance with me.
Give me a dose of your love.
It's the age of love.
Girl  you're soft like butter.
I'm bound to lose my heart.
My eyes clicked when I saw you.
Your image's posted on my heart.
Your eyes spell black magic.
You've made me lose control.
Come  let me take you around the world.
Say yes  and we'll fly away on a holiday.
It's the age of love.
Girl  you're soft like butter.
I'm bound to lose my heart.
My eyes clicked when I saw you.
Your image's posted on my heart.
One  two  three  four.. five.. six.. seven.. eight and again
Oye! Hey Shilpi! - One  two
Three. - Hi. - Hi.
Guys  give me a moment?
How are you? - I'm fine.
I wanted a favour from you  meet sukhi.
Nice to meet you. - Heard a lot about you.
Do you teach here? - No. I am a student.
Sir  the lights have been installed.
The stage is set.
And  I've put up five huge generators.
And  the dancer.
Let's talk to her right now. - One.. Two.. Three..
Hello. - Hello  Ms. Shilpi.
This is..
Sudhir Bagga. - Yes  Mr. Bagga.
You are coming  to teach dancing in the wedding.
I am so sorry  but it's not possible for me at all.
But you said you will. - Right  I did say I will.
But  a personal problem has come up. - What?
But  don't worry I'll send you a replacement. - I see
She's a very good dancer..
..and  her charges are lower than mine. - Thank you.
Bye. Bye.
It's done. - You did one good thing  Bagga.
And one  two  three  four..
One  two  three  four..
One  two..
Hi  dad. - My doll.
Hi  dad. - What's going on?
Meet Manpreet  our new choreographer.
By the way  she's fantastic.
Hello. - Hi  sir.
Ms. Shilpi's sent you  right? - Yes.
You've to really do your best.
After all  it's my daughter's wedding.
Definitely  sir.
Sir  if you don't mind  can I say something? - Of course.
You don't look like Gudiya's dad.
You've maintained yourself so well. - You don't know  dad.
He does power Yoga every morning one hour. - Wow.
Thank you.
You two can continue  we'll leave. - See you  sir.
Bye. - Bye.
Okay  again? - Yes.
So and yes..
Bye. - Bye.
Preet.
Thanks.
Without you.. - No need to say anything.
But  without you.. - I did this for myself  not you.
What? - You won't get it.
But really  if you ever have a problem..
Why are you getting sentimental?
Do one thing  get my granny free life-time cable TV.
Then we're even.
What?
Do you want to get me emotional and get a kiss?
Get lost? - Bye.
Thanks.
That Manpreet's a great girl. - Why?
We couldn't come up with an idea..
..and she managed to get in Sabharwal's home.
Wait and watch  she'll set things right.
Then ask her to do everything.
What are you doing here?
Why? Jealous?
Brother-in-law?
Tell us which is real? - Rascals.
You're drinking beer  and offering me milk.
Brother-in-law  just taste it. Please.
Oh  God! That's too much.
Brother-in-law  drink the milk.
Bagga. Is it 'Naag Panchami' today?
Sir. Milk is good for health.
I see. Good for health?
So  get healthy. Come on. - No  no  no.
Milk doesn't suit me. - Bagga.
Pick up the glass.
Try the first one.
This is real.
No! - No!
The third one.
This is real. - Absolutely not.
Brother-in-law  all of them are fake.
Amazing. The cream's absolutely real.
We've stumbled upon an amazing chemical.
Not just cream  but milk  butter  butter-milk  all A-1.
We'll produce the milk  and you can take the cream.
And  the real one.
Now  we don't have to mix fake products with the real ones.
We'll now supply them completely fake products.
We need to make the first delivery in three days.
After that  we'll be rolling in money.
And  swimming in cash.
And you know  they keep their money in the fridge.
What the..
If they keep the money in the fridge..
..where do they keep the curd?
So  let's make things sour for them..
..with cream on top.
Play on.
Sir  come. Madam. - Who is it?
Ministry of Health and Food..
Our madam.
We'll have to seal your dairy. - You..
We've information that you make adulterated milk here.
And  you're drinking liquor here as well.
No shame at all.
Get up. Get up. - Get up.
Where's the processing unit? - Come on.
Inspector Chaudhary  start the proceedings..
..and seize their licence. - Ok  madam.
Madam  listen.. - Let's go..
Madam.. - Open the door.
Where are you going? - So  Milkmaid  show me your licence.
Adulteration with milk. - Milk  without a cow.
Rascal.
Take a picture.
Sir. Can I make a call?
I see.
'Praise be to Lord Shiva!'
Yes. - Brother-in-law  there's a problem.
There's been a raid at the dairy.
Don't know  some lady officer.
Handle the situation at any cost.
If Gudiya's father-in-law finds out  he'll cancel the wedding.
Get the cash out of the dairy.
And  send that dairy to Jenny.
Tell her that I sent her a gift.
But  ask her not to open it as long as I don't get there.
Tell her I'll be at her place tonight.
Are you Mr. Sabharwal's brother-in-law?
First cousin from mother's side.
Oh Mother.. - What happened?
Don't complain about this to your brother-in-law. - I see.
It won't affect this madam.
But  your brother will have me sacked.
Look  please help me out. - Ok.
You can take this out  if you want.
If you want to save your job..
..then  you'll have to save us from your madam.
My madam? - Yes.
Shall I get rid of her?
I'll have to bribe everyone. - Just do it.
Just get our fridge out of this factory. - I see.
Let's see.
You'll get the job done?
Sure?
Yes  sir. Jai Hind!
Inspector Chaudhary  the commissioner's..
..summoned me urgently.
Continue your proceedings here  and keep reporting to me.
Raman  what's wrong with you?
Is this filled with milk or alcohol?
Here you go  sir. That's one million.
Listen to me carefully. - Yes.
Only one of you will go with the fridge. - Fine.
And  he'll go along with you.
No problem.
Jenny must feel it's a gift  that's what brother-in-law said.
When will we send a gift to Jenny?
Only when brother-in-law let's go.
Here. Give this to Jenny on my behalf. - Fine.
Let's go.
Come on.
Careful. Don't worry. - Okay.
All the best.
Jenny. - Raman?
Hi  Jenny.
This is brother-in-law's gift for you.
This is from my side.
Oops. Sorry.
Thank you.
Fridge? But  I already have a fridge.
No  no  there's a big surprise. - Surprise?
Brother-in-law will tell you later.
He'll come at night.
Please don't open.
Hello  lady. Myself Jogi.
How's your day? - Hi. I am okay.
Shall we go  sir?
Hello  lady. Jogi again.
Remember.
Actually  we gave you the wrong fridge.
So  we've got you the new fridge. Look.
This has more features.
Colour. Wonderful.
Hi. - Who are you?
I.. am Jogi.
Aren't you Mr. Sabharwal? - Yes.
Mr. Sabharwal! You've two factories. I know it.
You've many other factories.
You have schools  bungalows. Right?
Hold on  I am getting a call.
I get nervous.
Hello. I'm with Mr. Sabharwal.
I'll be right there. Okay?
Of course. We'll definitely meet.
Who was he? - Raman came with the fridge  so he was with him.
And  those two guys are exchanging the fridge right now.
I never ordered any replacement.
Who is it? - They're there in the kitchen?
Where?
Who is it?
Hey!
Close the door.
Open the door.
Thank God!
Brother-in-law!
Yes.
Rascals. I would've lost 500 million because of you.
I've delivered your fridge  with balloon.
Shut up! Balloons!
The raid on the dairy was a fake. - What? Fake?
Find out who they were?
No wonder Sood left so soon.
What's happening?
Yes.
But.. the money's safe.
But  what's happening with me?
You're going through a bad phase.
The planets are not in your favour.
Do something  please.
Stay quiet until Gudiya's marriage.
The wedding day's auspicious.
Arrange for a feast and donation to 101 Brahmins before the marriage.
You'll be rid of all problem's  Sabharwal.
Okay.
Mom  I did tell him that..
..you trust that Manpreet too much.
Mintu was right there. Ask him.
Ballu  shut up.
I wonder how Sabharwal turned up there.
Otherwise  we would've finished the job.
What do you mean how?
Whose job was it to keep an eye on him?
She was given just one job.
But  she couldn't do that either.
Let's forget what happened?
At least we got our hands on 1.5 million.
You can use that to buy stuff for your catering business.
That's what it's good for.
And him  lover boy.
She'll set things right.
Do you see now?
I say chuck Manpreet out of this plan.
Why chuck her out?
Calm down! Calm down!
We need to think what next?
What else? I'll round up some boys.
We'll rob the rascal at gunpoint. - No abusing here.
Are you crazy? - Why?
Because  we aren't professional dacoits.
Taking our own money is not stealing.
Like this?
And  what if we're jailed after this.
Who is going to explain him that?
Okay  then you can do whatever you think is right.
I am going.
Ballu. Stop  son. - Bye!
Ballu.
Inspector Valli called today.
The investors are after our lives.
If we don't return them our money..
..then we'll all be out on the streets.
Nonsense!
Look.
Don't worry.
Everything will be fine.
I'm only worried about aunt.
Look after her  please.
And..
..you too.
Saira.
I'll get you out of here soon.
You two only find faults with me.
What about Sukhi  who's ruining the entire plan..
..for the sake of love?
No point in fighting amongst ourselves  Ballu.
We'll be on the losing end.
The court has issued orders.
If we don't repay them in two weeks..
..aunt loses everything.
We're in a big mess.
Don't worry  mom.
Mintu will show me how to crack the safes.
You don't understand. Ballu has to be with you.
He won't take a second to crack Sabharwal's safe.
Yeah  we did have an argument.
Stop fighting. Bow down.
Ballu's calling.
Hello. - Hello  aunt. Balwant speaking.
Hello  son.
Pardon me  I walked out in a fit of rage that day.
But  don't worry.
We will win in the end.
Ballu. I was just talking to Sukhi about you.
Look  you two shouldn't argue amongst yourselves.
After all you're brothers.
I just prayed for everyone at the 'Gurdwara'.
Why don't you ask the Lord to join our team as well?
All our problems will be cleared.
Right  son.
Listen. - Yes.
Come home in the evening. - Okay  see you.
Bye  son. - Bye.
Ballu's agreed. He's coming home in the evening.
Let's go  son.
Okay  everyone.
Five  six  seven  eight start..
He's hiding.. behind her glares.
Sometimes peers from above.
Or spies from below.
He's hiding.. behind her glares.
Sometimes peers from above.
Or spies from below.
Steals my heart.
With an arrogant style.
Your mischievous eyes.
Your mischievous eyes. - Papa.
Look at papa.
Your mischievous eyes. - Papa  you're looking so funny.
Uncle  try to feel the words and beats of the song.
That's what I'm trying to do.
Am I doing it fine? - You're better than Malaika.
I was talking about uncle.
It's very simple.
Give me your hands. Okay.
Back  back  now come ahead.
Yes. Right. - Papa. This looks like gym class.
Manpreet  can you give papa some simple steps?
You shut up  dear.
Manpreet's popular in Delhi. she is fantastic - I know.
Just watch  she'll turn me into Hrithik before the cocktail party.
Hrithik.
Gudiya  I think you're making him conscious.
You just go  I'll help him practise. - Please.
Alright. I'll go. I'm famished anyways.
Thank you. - Let's go.
Ma'am  shall we stay here. - No  take them outside.
Help them rehearse. - Yes.
You know  uncle. You're too stiff.
Just loosen up.
Loosen up.
You need to practise hard to dance like Hrithik.
I can dance all night if you like?
Do you have the stamina  uncle? - Try.
But  don't call me uncle.
Call me  Mohan. - Okay  Mohan.
Shall I play the music? - Yes.
Sir.
The food's served.
Gudiya's saying if you could join her..
No?
Manpreet  let's eat.
Carry on  Mohan. I'll join you.
Waiting. - Yes.
Don't.. you understand I'm rehearsing.
Bagga. The kebabs.. superb.
Superb. - They are world famous.
Hello  ma'am.
Hello.
The dress really suits you.
You're looking nice.
Amazing  our tastes are so similar.
You're having salad  so am I.
I believe in eating light.. - Mohan.
I believe you can eat all you want.
But exercise double.
That's what Salman says as well.
Oh  Salman says that. - Yes.
Then  we must have soup and starters along with it.
Hey.. - Mohan.
I don't want to sound rude.
But your arrangements are so classy..
..but  the food's so middle-class.
So  the salad.
I think.. you should arrange for something better.
I hope you didn't make the same arrangements..
..for the marriage and reception.
Bagga. - Sir.
Yes  sir. - With whose permission did you make this arrangement?
Were the caterers your relatives?
Who did you ask?
Sir  you approved ten items.. after that it was a go ahead.
I.. - So..
Don't argue  Bagga.
Manpreet says the food's rubbish.
Rubbish. - Mohan.
According to your class and style..
..I think you should try Modern Caterers and Decorators.
Remember the wedding  of the Diwan's? - Yes.
They handled the catering there.
I was the main choreographer there.
The food was so tasty  and so expensive  oh God.
I see. Bagga. Call Modern Caterers.
Sir  what about the commitment you made to them.
Manpreet's saying it. So  it's final Bagga.
Address? - Find it  Bagga..
Dictionary? - Yes  go.
Do you need salt in the salad? - Do I need salt?
Hold on  I'll find out.
Sir  it's the Agriculture Minister on line.
Yes.
No  no  we're heavily packed.
Not a chance.
We can't cancel our prior commitments for the Minister.
Yes?
I am Bagga.
On behalf of Mr. Sabharwal's..
His daughter's getting married.
So  I need to discuss the catering order.
Who's the boss?
Obviously  me.
Good.
So  Mr. Sabharwal's a renowned industrialist.
Her daughter's getting married to that boy..
..serial superstar  Aman Kapoor.
The boy's family demands..
..they want only Modern Caterers.
I said  it'll be done.
And  here I am.
Was I right?
What's he saying?
Seems like a genuine client.
And  he's got a strong reference as well.
I think we should do it.
Thank you very much.
If it wasn't for you  things would've gotten difficult for me.
That's okay. You're a genuine guy.
And  you're paying double. - Right.
We've to look after you as well.
I had a question.
That small boy looks after your business.
He's our younger brother.
10 years ago  mom found him crying outside the bungalow.
She brought him home.
He's very lucky for the business. - Oh my God.
You made an orphan your brother.
He's no orphan  he means more than a brother.
Sorry for hurting your feelings.
Very few people respect others.
Play on.
Modern Caterers and Decorators.
Quality and Quantity.
We offer the best. - Since summer of '69.
Good.
Bagga. That's called class.
Five star service right at home. - Yes.
Thanks  Bagga. - My pleasure  sir.
Tell Manpreet about this. - Yes.
Wonderful  teacher..
You're making Sabharwal dance to your tunes.
Right  Ballu.
Yeah. She's a dance teacher after all.
You would know better.
But  I shouldn't have been on the team  right Sukhi.
No. You see  Ballu's always short-tempered.
Forgive and forget. - Hey. Don't ruin things for me.
If Sabharwal gets a whiff  it'll spoil our plan.
Stay away from each other.
Stay away.
He's hiding.. behind her glares.
Sometimes peers from above. Or spies from below.
Don't worry  Mr. Bagga.
Ballu's made arrangements for the dais..
..decoration and conveyance.
I see. - Yes.
There's nothing other than that  right?
I was really worried.
But  with you around I've nothing to worry.
You can forget all your worries. - No..
Get up. - Oh no.. - No  son..
Sorry  sir. - It's okay.
Everyone makes mistakes.
And anyway  the kebabs are cold.
You should always serve hot fresh kebabs to the guest.
I'm sorry  sir. - Get fresh kebabs from the oven.
I will just get them. Sorry  sir.
Wow! That's amazing  brother.
You treat your staff so nicely.
Mr. Bagga  the staff is the foundation of our business.
Not the boss.
And  if we don't respect them  they'll spoil our business. - Great.
And  there's something called humanity.
Great.
Really  great.
She's hot-headed  and she's having a tiff with me.
She's insane  and in a bad mood.
Loves to have an affair.
Tries to convince me.
Teases me slowly-slowly.
Your mischievous eyes.
Wow  Mohan. What a performance.
I am impressed. - All because of you.
First of all  your suggestion Modern Caterers..
..saved my reputation  their food was simply delicious.
And  the way you made me dance.
I mean  the entire party.. - Anything for you.
I think you're getting late.
Bagga. Bagga. - Sir.
Sir. - Drop madam home.
Of course. Madam  just two minutes.
There's chaos at the parking space.
I'll just deal with that and be right back.
Are you mad?
Will you decide what you're going to do?
Who's your boss?
It's my order.
Say yes. - Yes.
You will drop her.
Say yes. - Yes. Yes.
What happened  papa? - Nothing.
Okay.
Yes  madam. Please.
He's in a bad mood.
Bro  what can a poor servant do when the boss yells at him?
Don't worry  I'll drop her.
I'll drop her. - I.. I..
Just relax. I'll drop her.
Come. Come with me. - Thank you.
Bagga. Bagga. - Yes.
Don't mind but  such small things often happen in a party.
Come on.
How about a lovely-lovely.. for a change of mood?
Bagga. Have one more.
Okay.
Sukhi.
You're like my brother.
You know how to give respect.
And then there's that..
Sabharwal.
I've been with him since 20 years.
Forget about respect.
He keeps abusing..
..and humiliating me all day.
Relax  bro. You're drunk.
Sabharwal's the one who's high.
I said..
Please admit my daughter in your school.
He says..
Your daughter won't become a doctor or engineer?
Get her admitted in a public school.
And be grateful.
And I was so hurt hearing this..
I just can't tell you.
And  then there's you.
You're showering that orphan with love.
Raising him like family.
God gives everyone a chance.
You too.
Out with it.
This farm house is more like a fortress.
I'm tired  but couldn't find the stash anywhere.
There's just one place left now.
His bedroom. - You didn't check his bedroom yet.
He doesn't allow anyone in there.
What now?
Tomorrow's 'Mata Ki Chowki' (prayer ceremony).
That's when I'll get the opportunity.
Fine. Careful.
Hail the Goddess.
Glory to the Mother Goddess.
Wow. It's so amazing.
See I told you. - And  I told you.
Don't drink too much.
If brother-in-law finds out we're drunk..
..he won't spare us.
We can't even walk.
How can we run?
I..
Why did you bring her here? - Brother-in-law!
She wanted to see Indian culture.
So we said we'll take you to 'Mata's Chowki'.
This way  we can do two things at one time.
We're the Goddess's super fans.
The One with the red veil and black eyes.
We're dear to the Goddess.
We'll serve you day and night.
I love You.
I sing your praises.
O Goddess. - Glory to You.
Bless us with Your grace.
Give us Your blessings. - Glory to You.
Alleviate our pain.
O Goddess.
Bless us with Your grace. - Glory to You.
Don't let the night pass away. Don't let this bond break.
We'll sit all night at your feet.
O Goddess.
Hurry up  we don't have time.
Yea. Open it.
Shower us with wealth.
Solve our problems.
O Goddess. - Glory to You.
Come here  take a look.
Look there.
Make this plan perfect.
O Goddess. We request you.
Don't let the night pass away. Don't let this bond break.
We'll sit all night at your feet.
O Goddess.
Come here. Here.
It's empty. - Nothing here.
Look there. Come on.
How much?
I said it once..
I'm disconnecting.
Mohan. - You?
Actually  I had a request. - Yes. Tell.
Not here. - Let's go in the room.
No  let's go in the balcony.
Come on. - Yes. - Come on.
You are great.
We sing Your praises  You're truly amazing.
We come to Your threshold  for Your blessings.
Your grace is true  we're your children.
Every Saturday  is an auspicious day for us.
Everyone sing with me..
Don't let the night pass away. Don't let this bond break.
You sing very well.
We'll sit all night at your feet.
Don't let the night pass away. Don't let this bond break.
Remember my friend Shilpi.
The one who recommended me.
Yes.
We're inaugurating our dance academy day after tomorrow.
In Kalkaji.
And  I want you to be the chief guest.
Me  chief guest? - Please. Don't say no.
If you say so.. - Thank you.
By the way  Manpreet..
..this dress really suits you. - Oh.
Sir!
Come quickly.
Raman and Pawan are troubling the lady singer.
If you don't come Goddess will get angry.
It's nothing. They're just children  playing along..
Wait  I am coming. - Come.
I'll be right.. - Yes.
Don't you have any manners?
How could you say that in front of Manpreet?
They're troubling the lady openly  and I can't say it.
Look.
Get lost.
O Goddess.
Please do something.
I know something can be done.
Look  I know Mr. Baweja was an honest man.
But  I cannot do anything now.
The orders are from the court.
You have only 5 days left.
Try to convince the investors to withdraw the case.
Otherwise  I'll have to do my duty.
Just a minute.
Hello. - Aunt. Balwant here.
There's no money anywhere.
I don't thing Goddess is supporting us.
Now you do something. - Fine.
Play on.
Excuse me. - Sir.
Sir. - Who's your senior manager? Call him right now.
Tell me  sir. I am here for you.
I ordered for soya sauce 15 minutes back.
How do you expect me to eat my sushi?
Sir  we're expecting a special guest.. - So?
There she is.
Hello  ma'am. So pleased to see you.
As usual  we've booked the top three floors..
..of our hotel especially for you. Please  come. - Come.
Hello. Hello  Mrs. Mehta. Good to see you.
After a long time.
Where were you? - I was off to Milan  for the power project.
And  how's your party doing?
It's running on your funds.
Don't embarrass me  I trust your party.
Thank you  ma'am. - Thank you.
Allow me.
Thank you.
Excuse me  sir.
That's the limit.
I ordered for soya sauce  what's this?
Sir  this is a bottle of rare wine from Mrs. Hansal Mehta.
Especially for you.
Mrs. Hansal Mehta. If you don't mind  can I ask a question?
What do you do?
Hansal Constructions. Hansal Finance. Hansal Shipping.
Hansal chemicals. Hansal Fisheries. Hansal Farms. - You mean.
Hansal Plaza  Hansal Mall  Hansal Arcade.
You're well known from Gurgaon to Delhi to Noida.
It's my pleasure to meet you  madam.
Likewise  my pleasure.
It's great meeting Aman Kapoor  the big star.
I wish Sailja was here. - Who?
My daughter  Sailja. - I see.
She's a big fan of yours.
In fact  both my children are big fan of yours.
They don't miss a single episode.
Sailja even records all your episodes.
I see.
So  you're here on a shoot. - No  no.
Actually  Aman's getting married.
Mr. Sabharwal's daughter.
What was her name? - Gudiya.
Gudiya.
I'm sure you know him.
Actually  Mr. Sabharwal bought the land..
..for his bank and school from Hansal Real Estate.
But  the payment's still due.
Shut up. Let's not talk about it. - Sorry.
Congrats in advance  son. - Thank you so much.
Excuse me  ma'am.
This is the limited edition watch..
..the one you ordered for your son.
It's come.
Wow. That is classy.
Fabulous. - You like it?
Keep it.
Your wedding gift. - No.
What no?
You shouldn't say no to your elders.
Take it. She's giving it with love. Keep it.
Take it. - Thanks.
Instead of Mrs. Hansal Mehta  can I call you aunt.. - Stupid.
She's like your aunt.
And she has to attend your wedding.
Otherwise  we won't take this gift. Give it back.
Are you coming  or not?
Check that.
Excuse me. I'll be right back from the restroom.
Okay. Come back soon.
Hello!
No  no. No  Mr. Sabharwal.
I've told you so many times stop calling madam.
We're not interested in doing any business with you.
Ok. And  please don't call again.
Son  what are you doing?
So many brownies? Tell me what's bothering you. - You know it  dad.
When Aman's stressed  Aman eats brownies.
Yeah  but what's the problem.
That Sabharwal  he's a big time fraud.
And  you brought this proposal. - Yes  I did.
You needed 1.5 billion to launch your future film.
But  what's wrong?
Once the marriage is done with. - Yes.
And refuses to give the money at the reception? - No.
That's not possible. - I'm telling you  dad.
Don't take a risk.
And anyway  I've decided.
Decided what?
First the money  then the marriage.
Listen to this. - Go ahead.
Boyfriend: If I kiss you what will you think of me?
Girlfriend: Stupid.
Why?
Girlfriend:
If you taste only pickle  instead of the entire plate..
..then you're stupid.
Your phone.. - Hello. - Mr. Sabharwal.
Yes.
I had to say something important. - Go ahead.
The dowry amount  that was decided between us..
..we want them before the marriage. - What's wrong?
Nothing  it's a personal requirement.
I'll tell you later. - But  Mr. Kapoor  we had agreed that..
..the money will be given in Mumbai during the reception.
No  we want it before the wedding.
Just make the arrangements. Yes.
Listen..
Okay?
Now you acted more like Aman's dad.
I'm your father after all.
Fool.
There's a problem. - Go ahead.
I had an agreement with Tej Kapoor..
..that the dowry money will be given at the reception  in Mumbai.
But  he's gone back on his words.
He wants the money first  only then..
..will he go ahead with the marriage.
So.. please arrange the bank money that I kept with you..
..I'm coming to get them.
Stay there. - Why? What happened?
Saturn's fury is at its last stage.
I don't want any obstructions in Gudiya's marriage.
Make preparations for the steps I told you to take..
..to escape Saturn's fury.
I'll get the money personally.
Bagga. Have you arranged for 100 Brahmins..
..before the wedding? - Yes.
All the arrangements have been done.
What's wrong?
The money's reached the farmhouse.
I'll return you every penny.
With interest.
Just have faith.
Why the long face?
Make a happy face. You're getting married today.
So what if I'm getting married.
That cheat Sabharwal said..
..the groom will descend in a helicopter. Where's the helicopter?
Superstar Aman's riding on a peacock shaped chariot.
I won't step inside without seeing the money.
Tell me this. When I didn't get married without seeing the money..
..I won't let you either. Don't worry.
Once you get the money  buy yourself a helicopter. Okay?
Now  smile.
Come on. Start playing.
I think I've seen them before.
I just..
Sabharwal. Congratulations.
Congratulations. - Congratulations to you too.
Let me introduce you.
She's Mrs. Hansal Mehta from Hansal Group of Companies.
She's like family.
Special guest.
Come in. Come. - Come on.
Dad.
Sabharwal  I forgot to say something. - Yes.
Aman wanted to see the bride once.
Son  you can't before the marriage.. - No!
Sabharwal  you didn't get it.
Bride.. - Okay  come in.
Come. Come. - Come in.
Come on.
There you go  bro.
You see  Sabharwal.
I want to tell you something personal.
If it wasn't an emergency  I wouldn't have troubled you.
Sir  this is no trouble at all. - Yes.
Whether you slit the hen at the shop or the jungle.
But  its fate decided.
Sorry  sorry.
Son-in-law. The money isn't going anywhere.
The money's safe here.
Not to worry. - Yes.
Bagga. Tell him a new joke.
He's a good man.
You've trained him well.
You just snap your fingers 'Bagga.. Bagga..'
Kapoor  he's the dog that never barks.
Only cracks jokes.
Tell us.
Come on.
Stop. Stop.
You start instantly.
You see  Sabharwal.
It's my son's wedding  you think we're here to listen to jokes.
Not at all.
Bro  I've arranged a wonderful program for you.
You'll be amazed.
You're going to have fun. Let's go. - Come on.
Bagga  wait here.
Night of bliss.
Beloved's hot-hot.
I'm capturing my beloved's image through my eyes.
I'll sway  play hard to get.
Beware my beloved.
Sukhi..
I'll do the serpent.. serpent dance.
The shiny nose-ring pin.
The danglers in my ears.
Are only for you  they stole your heart.
Beloved  my plan is.
I won't let go of you so easily.
I'll do the serpent.. serpent dance.
Gulp down that drink.
And groove on the floor.
Dance with me  darling.
Now get up from that seat.
Or I won't spare you  I'll bite you.
I won't step back.
I'll do the serpent.. serpent dance.
..serpent dance.
Thank you.
Do give your blessings.
Come on. Please.
Keep moving.
Mr. Aman Kapoor. Call for you.
Who is it? - Don't know.
But he says it's important. It's urgent.
Hello. - Praise the Divine Mother!
You're being fooled. - What?
What nonsense.
And  who are you? - I am Obama. Listen to me carefully.
You've been duped big time.
The money  for which you're getting married..
..has disappeared from the bag.
Forget the movie.
You can't even make an ad film now.
Check the bag before the nuptials.
Otherwise  you'll be the loser.
Hello.
What's wrong? - What happened?
What happened? - What happened?
It's nothing. I'll be right back. Wait here.
What did he say? - What?
Listen to me  son.
What happened? Who was it? - Don't know.
Dad. Stop this sham.
They take us for fools.
What's this  uncle?
What is all this?
See. The money has disappeared from the bag.
And.. these papers..
What do you want me to do with them?
I warned you. They're frauds. - Hey!
Mr. Sabharwal  what's this?
Where's the money?
Where's the money  Sabharwal?
Hold on. Hold on  Mr. Kapoor.
Even I would like to know where my money is.
Let's go inside and talk.
Sabharwal  let's talk here.
In front of everyone.
And  where's the money? - The money..
You saw the money yourself  and..
Bagga!
Bagga! Where's he?
He was supposed to look after the money. Where is he?
What's happening with me?
Don't act innocent  Sabharwal.
You wanted to trick us into the marriage..
With your average daughter.. - Hey!
Shut up!
Don't you dare say a word about my daughter.
Or I won't spare you. - Brother-in-law's right.
We've seen many TV stars like you.
No need to endure anymore humiliation  brother-in-law.
Hey you  TV Star.
You and your guests just get the hell out of here!
Stop this nonsense.
Enough of this sham.
Dad  the wedding's cancelled.
Get out of here. - Wait. The wedding's definitely cancelled.
Let me talk to him.
Sabharwal. Hansal Mehta had already told me..
..that you're a big fraud.
But  I cannot believe you can stoop so low..
..and cheat in your own daughter's wedding.. - Shut up!
Rascal! Shut up  you rascal!
Shut up!
Do you know who you're talking to?
Sabharwal! This is my empire!
Who's this Mrs. Hansal?
Tell me. Who knows me better? Who is it?
Tell me.
I am not Mrs. Hansal Mehta.
Who are you? - Jasbeer Baweja.
Ravinder Baweja's wife.
Oh? Can't understand  Sabharwal?
Wait a minute  aunt.
We'll explain him with little jolts.
We tricked the principal of your school Sethi..
..and robbed you of 300 million.
'What brings you here?'
'You didn't visit the school for a long time..'
'..so  I just wanted to see if you're okay.'
And then  we raided your dairy as well.
'Brother-in-law  there's a problem.'
'There's been a raid at the dairy.'
The video-recording has already been delivered to the police.
And then  we made you dance to our tunes..
..to take your money.
Manpreet!
Rascals. You don't know who I am.
We know who you are.
My father lost his life because of you.
And sister-in-law Saira's still in jail.
I am Sukhwinder Baweja  Ravinder Baweja's son.
I swore to restore my father's reputation.
Just like you robbed the investors..
..and put the blame on Mr. Baweja.
Similarly  we robbed you of your money.
Robbed my money.
Just try to take that money out of Sabharwal's house.
The money's already left the farm house.
And  you've personally returned..
..the investors their money with interest.
Fool.
'Come on. Please.'
'Keep moving.'
Sir.
How about a joke?
Forget it.
Today  you're the joke.
Bagga  you..
You betrayed your own employer.
And yes  Sabharwal's killed many Bawejas  and now..
Papa. - Gudiya  move.
Move aside. Move!
That's enough.
I could never imagine..
..you could do such a thing.
After mom's death  you were everything for me.
My hero.
But you hurt me.
Go away from here.
Please go away.
This had to happen  Sabharwal.
You can't get a bigger punishment.
Mr. Baweja's soul is finally at peace now.
In view of all the statements and witnesses..
..the court sentences Mohan Sabharwal..
..to 7 years of rigorous imprisonment.
'Life didn't stop with Sabharwal's punishment.
Sukhi and Manpreet got married.
Granny got her free cable TV connection.
Mintu's seen less cooking and more in religious parties.
Ballu was always a fixer  and he still is.
Kabootar got admission  without the donation.
And  Bagga found a big family to tell his jokes.
But  our mom's truly amazing.
We've seen many super-heroes..
..but  not a super-heroine like our mom.
Play on.
So you think you're smart.
Whenever someone cheats you  troubles you.
Locks horns with you all the time.
Snatches your rights  tries to scare you.
Just teach him a lesson  buddy.
Whenever someone cheats you  troubles you.
Locks horns with you all the time.
Snatches your rights  tries to scare you.
Just teach him a lesson  buddy.
Play on.
They've a good report.
They've the support of God.
They're always after those with wrong intentions.
And a bad heart.
When someone pollutes the world  we calm him down.
When someone picks a fight with us  we teach him a lesson.
No point in sitting down  give a tit for tat Make that your rule.
Play on.
Whenever someone cheats you  troubles you.
Locks horns with you all the time.
Snatches your rights  tries to scare you.
Just teach him a lesson  buddy.
Whenever someone cheats you  troubles you.
Locks horns with you all the time.
Snatches your rights  tries to scare you.
Just teach him a lesson  buddy.
Play on.
Be the king  stop being afraid.
Help the needy.
Don't spare those who act smart.
Just do as I say.
Whenever someone creates a problem for you.
And troubles you.
Whenever someone ditches you and avoids you.
No point in sitting down.
''Give a tit for tat Make that your rule.
Play on.
Whenever someone cheats you  troubles you.
Locks horns with you all the time.
Snatches your rights  tries to scare you.
Just teach him a lesson  buddy.
Whenever someone cheats you  troubles you.
Locks horns with you all the time.
Snatches your rights  tries to scare you.
Just teach him a lesson  buddy.
Play on.