Hello and welcome to the TC Show.
No, we are not talking
about Railway TC's here.
This is 'TC', Tele-Shopping Channel.
I would like to show an AV..
..to our heavy audience.
And don't mistake
him for anyone ordinary.
..he's quite a heavy personality.
Our very own Mumbai
boy Akhil Lokhande.
I am quite distressed.
I always wanted to
excel in every field.
Thats why these days..
...I'm living my life in
4 XL, 5 XL, 6 XL sizes.
I always wanted to do
work equal of six people.
Now when I enter any lift..
...I realize I am
equivalent to six people.
I always thought life could
never tread on a single wheel.
When there is a will,
there is no way.
I always thought how
will I pacify my kid.
I am really disturbed.
Friends, this depressing
AV was shot two months ago.
Well, let's wel	come..
Farhad, Sajid, is the stage firm?
Yes, absolutely.
Please welcome Akhil Lokhande.
Akhil Lokhande. Wow!
You showed up alone.
I don't see the rest
of Akhil Lokhande's anywhere.
Sir, now no more “I'm disturbed“.
But I am surprised.
How did this happen?
Hold on.
JC!
Jagtap Capsules!
A unique invention
made of Ayurvedic herbs.
A bottle of JC...and you're all set.
JC means...
- Jagtap Capsules.
Come on.
Turn this Laurel into Hardy.
- Yes, sir.
And he should look
like Akhil Lokhande.
Sir..
- Stick it properly.
You're not concentrating.
- Sir.
The deal was 4000,
this is just 2500.
So, you didn't put on
any weight for it either.
Keep this, a bottle of JC.
Go and build 16 abs.
World record.
Be happy.
You've got your head in the air.
I will kill you.
Why? Are you a villain?
Villain?
Don't create a scene here.
- Why, are you a jester?
Jester.
Don't test me, my hands are not tied.
- Why? Are you a widow?
Widow?
Why you..
Phone's ringing.
Hold him.
Hello.
Yes, I am coming.
I said I am coming.
If I wasn't in such a hurry..
...I would've exacted my money.
Get lost. - It's important,
or I wouldn't have spared you.
He pretends as if the entire
world dances to his tune.
One more.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Stop it. Stop it.
Stop the rehearsals.
Music cut. Music cut.
Remove all the male dancers..
..keep the female dancers.
Boys, pack-up.
Girls, come in the front.
What do you mean by
"Girls come in the front" Remo sir?
You think you can throw
us out whenever you like?
I know, I'll break your teeth?
Why, are you a dentist?
Dentist?
I'll crush you.
- Why, are you tobacco?
Tobacco?
I'll will gut you.
- Why, are you Hajmola?
Hajmola, why you..
Let go.
Let me go.
Hold him.
Hello? Coming.
Let me go.
- Ifl didn't have to leave urgently.
...I would've exacted my money.
Understand.
Get lost.
It's important
or I wouldn't have spared you.
Let go.
Important?
He pretends as
if he'll build a big empire.
Lord...
So Borivali team has set a target.
..of 120 runs for Dombiva
i's team.
And Dombivali team's opening batsman.
..has arrived on the crease.
One.. Two.
Howzat!
What?
Where did you get him from?
It touched my bat.
He'll even give a cripple LBW out.
Now go.
- Sir, it hit the bat.
Be quiet,
or I'll give you out as well.
Howzat!
Here's your money.
Akhil, you really
stirred up things today.
Really!
What can I do?
I have to get to my other job..
But this is not done.
Your days of raising
fingers are over, boy.
Now I will lift my hand.
- Why? Are you a beggar?
I will send you back on a stretcher?
Why? Are you a compounder?
I am going to malign you.
Why? Are you a rag-picker?
— Rag..
Let's take care of him!
Now say. Come on.
Here. Keep one note.
Hey...
- Hey!
Don't hit.
- Let's go.
Now get to your other job.
Other work.
Feels like you've married to
your work, not me.
Each day I would kindle my desires..
..on the threshold of hopes.
And today's ‘Kanrvachauth’.
The biggest day in your wife's life.
Most important.
And you came late even today.
Why?
You made me your wife.
So why did you do this with me?
Why?
Parvati , actually...
...work is just an excuse.
There's someone else in my life.
Kavyanjali.
Dear, please try to..
- Enough!
Enough! Enough!
“Virtuous bonds“,
Made for Each Other“..
...all these are just
too good to be true.
But the truth is...
I am just your discard.
All I wanted was one smile of joy“.
..in my own beautiful world of dreams.
But you've proved..
..our union is no Iongerjustified.
Cut it. Very good shot.
Bunch of freeloaders.
Hi.
Our date was fixed before my shoot.
And I am sorry.
What are you doing?
Well, I feel like taking
you to an expensive place today.
Where?
Petrol Station.
Because there's nothing
more expensive than that.
Uncle, ball.
Thank you.
You know,
my life's like this football.
Whoever comes,
kicks me and gets ahead.
You'll achieve your goal
through these kicks, Akhil.
And I know what your goal is.
To help your father get better.
Poor guy's been in
the hospital for a year.
You work day and night
to cover his expenses.
But just watch.
Someday he'll be absolutely fine.
Really?
I swear.
Thanks.
Hey.
Forget it. Thief.
Are you hitting on me?
Do I look like a ruler to hit on you.
Will you stick to me?
- Do I look like Fevicol to stick to you?
Kiss me?
- Am I Emraan Hashmi to kiss you?
"Someone dwells in me all day."
"My days and nights are lost in her."
“Someone feels so close.“
"As if my head beats in him."
"There's no cure to...
what I've been struck with."
"Someone touched my head."
"Whose sights do I owe it to?"
"
f anyone asks, I'll say it's you."
“I'll tell everyone
that it's your effect.“
"
f anyone asks, I'll say it's you."
"Someone knocks on my heart."
"..comes in and stays there."
"What's this sin that has no atone?"
"Someone touched my head."
"Whose prayers do I owe it to?"
"
f anyone asks, I'll say it's you."
"Wrapped in satin clothes."
"Filled with abundant of colors."
"What's this gift I've been
bestowed with?"
“Don't let it slip through your lips.“
"My patience's melting for you."
"
f anyone asks, I'll say it's you."
So...what do you want to say?
Have you planned for
a candle light Dinner?
Papa's trying to save electricity.
Quiet.
For your kind information.
I like my conversation.
..in the isolation of darkness.
Miser!
What happened?
There's no arm-rest on this side.
You get only half the
sofa in half the amount.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Papa, let me switch on one light.
Sir, I'm here to ask for
your daughter's hand for marriage.
And do you have
irritation or objection..
..with the rest of her body?
Meaning?
I mean..
..your relation with my
daughter is out of question.
Cancellation, rejection!
Why, sir?
What lacks in me?
You've something even
the rich can't have. - What?
Poverty.
You're poor.
- Sir, your..
You're a hapless.
There's no strength
in this relationship.
Papa!
Your daughter's necessities are few..
..that's why this
relationship is the best.
What do I want?
Three cotton clothes,
two pieces of bread..
...and a single courtyard.
I don't want a palace of sorrows..
..just a hut filled with joy.
Get lost.
Stop reciting your TV serial dialogues.
Hey...
What's your name?
Yeah Akhil Lokhande.
Lokhande!
Listen carefully.
I want a husband for my daughter...
..who's wealthy, and not the person
who wants sympathy.
Wealthy.
Now do you understand?
Come back when you're rich.
Out!
What if I don't go?
I'll kick you?
- Why, are you a donkey?
I'll break your milk-teeth?
- Why, are you the milkman?
I'll bash you so hard.
- Why, are you a maid?
He's so audacious.
Fine, if you like
being such a loud-mouth..
..then...swear on this fire..
You won't decide
to marry my daughter..
..until you become a millionaire.
Come on, swear.
Akhil..
- Don't say anything.
I swear.
First millionaire,
then Sakshi's husband.
Papa's trying to trap you.
You are trapped.
Laugh all you want, sir.
But listen to my
mathematics carefully.
I am going to multiply money..
..and soon it will subtract
the smile on your face.
Your mind will get divided..
..and your daughter
will get added in my life.
Are you a mathematics teacher?
Addition.
Papa, electricity's back.
I am ruined.
Who's going to pay the bill?
I will kill you.
Who will pay my bills?
O Bollywood...who do I pray..
..so that business is never slow..
..and my shop makes me popular.
Jugnu, give me 'Honeymoon Dvd“.
Son, first take ‘Dosti’,
then ‘Mohabbatein’.
Then 'Shaadi No.1'
and then 'Honeymoon'.
And then..
That's 400 for 4 CDs.
Get out.
What do you want?
- 'Darr'.
Only 'Darr'.
- Yes.
Take Jeet as well.
- Why?
Because beyond 'Darr'
there's ‘Jeet’ (Victory).
Show off..
Akhil.
My friend,
where are you going in such a humble way?
On my way to the hospital.
And after that to work.
I must admit, buddy.
Hold on.
Look, this is 'Baghbaan'.
Four sons couldn't look
after their only father.
And you alone do four
jobs a day for your father.
That's not a big thing.
I'm sweating for my own blood.
That's called love.
You've always fulfilled
every desire of your father.
I'll come with you
to the hospital now.
And how would uncle be living“.
..in the hospital all these clays?
“Don't try to stop me.“
“Don't object if I follow you.“
“I've a right on you.
You're my delight.“
"Don't be shocked if
I obstruct your way."
"You're right beside me.
I am right next to you."
Akhil?
Oh, God. I am exhausted.
Don't you have chest-pain anymore?
What chest-pain?
It's just another excuse.
..to spend another year
in this luxurious hospital.
And to get acquainted
to nurses like you.
But...is it a good thing
to squander your son's money?
It's bad. It's very bad.
But he's not my son.
He's my ticket to comfort and luxury.
He's my walking ATM counter for me.
Who's this?
Where are you going?
Son, you've arrived.
Am I a fax, to arrive?
Look, you're turning red.
Am I a traffic light to turn red?
Look, son, you're over-doing it.
Am I a bowler to do an over?
I treated you like God.
Tell me who my father is.
I've no clue.
But 30 years ago..
...I met your mother
during a rail journey.
You were just a 3-4 years old kid.
You were playing
in your mother's arms.
And during our conversation.
“Your mother narrated
her sad story to me.
How your father made
your mother pregnant.
..but not his wife, because..
..there was another
mistress in his life.
When your mother heard this..
..she left your conniving father..
..and was returning in that train.
But just then...
...the train met with accident.
And your mother passed away.
But you survived.
It's the grace of God, Akhil.
You survived.
If I hadn't survived that day,
would I be..
I've yet to get to the point.
The interesting pan comes now.
The Rail Minister arrived
at the accident spot.
And he announced that.
..any family with
even on deceased member..
...will get 1 lakh as compensation.
Sol picked up his trunk, and him..
..and pretended as he was my son and..
Beat him.
- I am dead!
- Oh, God!
More.
Old man..
You really gave him a sound beating.
Very good.
Old man.
As you sow...so shall you reap.
I can't believe this.
Your bachelor father's
shown us such a dirty picture.
The question is Akhil,
what is your origin?
Because this is reality.
Real life.
This isn't 'Gol maal' where
you'll find an old trunk..
..in the house like Ajay Devgan did.
Well, let's imagine
that you do find a trunk.
You do.
But it's not necessary
that you'll open it up..
...and just like in Manisha's
film 'Love Letter'..
..it would have your
mother's love letters.
..and you'll find those too.
Well, we're filmy people.
Let's take some Iibeﬂy.
Let's assume that you
found the love letters as well.
It's not necessary that
you'll also find a locket.
...like Jeetendra did
in this film 'Locket'.
Since I took Jeetendra's name,
let's take some more liberty.
Even if you find the locket.
You won't find your parent's
photo in the locket.
Even if you find
your father's picture..
..your father won't turn
out to be a millionaire.
Pannalal Johri.
Yes, Pannalal Johri.
Bangkok's diamond king.
He can't be your father.
My father's Pannalal Johri.
What?
- Yes.
Akhil, you're a millionaire.
Jugnu.
I am a millionaire.
- Yes.
Jugnu. I am a millionaire.
What did I just press?
- What's this?
Bangkok's diamond merchant.
...multi-millionaire Pannalal Johri
passed away today.
Pannalal Johri was a renowned
personality in Bangkok.
Akhil.
Your father wasn't even born yet..
..and he Died.
You're so unlucky.
You're doomed.
Akhil.
I'll get water for you.
I hope my friend doesn't die.
Akhil.
Akhil, the shock's made you mad.
Jugnu, it's not the shock,
I am mad with joy.
You heard the bad news,
not the complete news.
Listen. Listen.
So what about his property
worth 3000 crores.
Because he has no heir,
or wife and kids.
If any of his relative turns up..
..then he'll be the owner
of 3000 crores overnight.
Now you drink the water.
Some more.
Jugnu, my father's dead..
..and I am not happy about it.
In fact, I am very happy.
Why?
Because he betrayed my mother.
That's why Lord took away my father..
...and served me justice.
He gave me all these evidence..
..so that I can prove to the world..
..that I am Pannalal Johri's son.
Jugnu, now this
Slumdog's a millionaire.
'Johnny Johnny. .
- Yes.“
“Are you drinking?
- NO JI.
"Open your mouth.
- Aww."
“Telling lies.
- No Ji.
'Johnny Johnny. .
- Yes.“
“Have you been drinking?
- No Ji.
“Open your mouth.
“Telling lies.
- No Ji.
"No, no, no."
“I've not been drinking.“
“I've been forced to drink.“
"It's all okay."
“I'm having fun.“
"in the bar, in the car."
"She's got thousands of problems."
"She keeps drinking
all the while and says.."
"This is my first."
"In the bar, in the car."
"He sways like he's drunk."
"He keeps drinking
all the while and says.."
“I'll stop drinking at dawn.“
"Never listens to anyone."
"Bad habits all the while."
"On every bottle he says.."
"This is the last one for the day."
"Never listens to anyone."
"Bad habits all the while."
"On every bottle she says.."
"This is the last one for the day."
"Johnny Johnny."
"Chug it Chug it."
"This is the last one for today."
"Johnny Johnny."
"Chug it Chug it."
"This is the last one for today."
"Johnny Johnny."
"Yes--
“Do you see two?
- No Ji.
"Open your eyes..
- Avvvvvv."
“Telling lies..
- No Ji.
“Either birthday or wedding.“
“Either full or half.“
"My buddies ganged up on me."
"Either happiness or tension."
“Every day it's a new reason.“
“All you want is attention.“
"No, no, no."
“I've not been drinking.“
“I've been forced to drink.“
“I'm full now!“
“No more partying from tomorrow.“
"In the bar, in the car."
"She's got thousands of problems."
"She keeps drinking
all the while and says.."
"This is my first."
"
n the bar, in the car."
"He sways like he's drunk."
"She keeps drinking
all the while and says.."
“I'll stop drinking at dawn.“
"Never listens to anyone."
"Bad habits all the while."
"On every bottle he says.."
"This is the last one for the day."
"Johnny Johnny."
"Chug it Chug it."
"This is the last one for today."
WOW, Akhil.
From "l am really troubled"
to "l am really rich".
Crazy boy.
He's trying to stop the king..
..from entering his own palace.
Papa.
Papa, it's your son..
This is terrible.
I've been orphaned again.
What's this guy blabbering about?
Please.
You look like an Indian.
- I am Habibullah Sheikh.
Pannalal's right-hand.
His lawyer.
Mister, how did this happen?
The diamond from Johri sir's
ring fell in his potato wedges.
And he swallowed the diamond instead.
And...he died in 2 minutes.
He's not a noodles to die instantly.
Address him with respect.
Do you know who he was?
He was my father.
He's my papa.
My dad.
Now give me the money.
Hanky.
What did you hear?
Money.
Corrupt mind!
Papa, you can't speak properly.
This man can't hear properly.
Life without you is no fun.
Because I've turned into an orphan.
Your memories are still
in this bungalow, isn't it?
So...now I will live in this bungalow.
..with your memories.
The car you took to the office,
that huge car..
..now I'll drive to the office in it.
I'll find your company
while handling your company papa.
What is it?
I would like to talk
to you on an important issue.
What?
- Talk.
Talk?
Akhil, I don't need to investigate.
I mean question you.
What?
Why can't you be Pannalal Johri's son?
Have some tea.
Every year,
when India can produce children..
“Equivalent to
population of Australia..
..then why can't
Pannalal sir produce you?
Is that logic enough for you?
- Yes.
He's from Bangkok, I'm from Borivali.
Is that okay?
I've another logic for that.
- Go ahead.
If India's Sania Mirza,
Pakistan's Shoaib Malik..
..can be husband and wife.
Then why can't Bangkok's
Pannalal Johri and..
Hold on. Have you studied LAW?
Yes?
No, because...this concerns 3000 crores,
Lulla sir.
Hey! That's Habibullah.
Look, my father's given me this name..
..with great love and affection.
So please..
- I mean, you're a lawyer.
Won't you ask for any evidence?
Like these...love-letters
written by my father.
This locket.
Family album.
But these days any
fraud can forge all this..
..with the help of computer graphics.
So here's my blood.
This will prove that I am his blood.
D.N.A.
'Daddy's Najayaz Aulad'
(Daddy's illegitimate son).
These things aren't needed, son.
I recognized you at first sight.
Your mother's name
was Shanti Devi, right?
Yes.
Sometimes,
my boss would feel embarrassed..
..and mention about her to me.
Fine.
So tell me,
Habibullah sir, when can I take over.
You can't take over..
..because someone's
already over-taken you.
What do you mean?
Pannalal made a Will before he died.
And he transferred his
entire property to someone else.
Who is it?
Does he have another illegitimate son?
Any son?
More than a son?
This is a conspiracy.
A big game-plan.
Hold on.
Did he show you any proof?
Letter. . .locket. . father's picture.
Did the DNA matched?
Then damn it.
How can he be my father's heir?
How dare he try to assert
his right on my property?
No!
I won't let this happen.
Who's that rascal?
Where's that rascal?
Rascal!
Pannalal Johri's was
cremated only a while ago..
..and you've already usurped his seat.
It's about 3000 crores.
Everyone's conscience is for sale.
But I am the real heir
of Pannalal Johri, not you.
All this belongs to me.
This property is only mine.
Did you hear?
Turn the chair around.
Look at me.
Look into my eyes.
Turn the chair around!
He's Pannalal Johri's heir.
His sweet, adorable and only...
..and more than a son.
But he's a dog.
For God's sake, don't call him a dog.
- Why?
Because his name's Entertainment.
Why Entertainment?
Why? Why not?
If pigeons can be called 'Masakali'.
Horse can be called 'Badal' (Cloud).
If Mahila Jaywardhane
can be a male's name.
Then why can't his
name be Entertainment?
Look, Akhil.
Pannalal Johri was really sad..
..after your mother's accident.
He started repenting .
He was living like a live monument.
For years he attempted
to find you two..
..in many continents.
But then he got disappointed.
...and after getting
disconnected from everyone“.
..tried to kill himself
on his pavement.
That's when he...he saved his life.
Hello, sir.
Since then he dwelled
in the basement of his heart
He became the 'Pepsodent
of his brush'.
The peppermint in his life.
The instrument of his music.
And his name..
- I know.
Became Entenainment.
Now tell me...if Pannalal
hadn't given his property.
...to Entertainment,
then who else would he give it to.
My millionaire father
gave his property to a dog.
To a dog!
I am ruined.
My father made my
life worse than a dog.
I am ruined.
I am poor again.
Hello.
- Akhil, this is Jugnu speaking.
Shocked to hear my voice, aren't you?
I am in Bangkok.
Jugnu.
A Slumdog DID became the billionaire.
What do you mean?
What are you saying?
Your buddy's been
orphaned again. - No.
I am ruined.
- No.
I've lost the 3000 crores.
- No, this isn't possible.
Akhil. Hello, Akhil.
I really can't believe this again.
A dog's name 'Entertainment'.
The dog's name is shocking for you.
But he usurped my 3000 crore..
..that isn't shocking for you.
Sorry! yaar
That dog.
By the way, is he a male or a female?
I've an idea.
Take a stone and hurl it at him.
If HE runs, he is male.
Or if SHE runs, she is female.
Whether he's a male or a female,
but he stole my bone.
Sorry, sorry.
I can understand what I am asking you.
Look, Akhil. Don't be sad.
You please divert
your mind from this dog.
Forget the dog.
Look, I'm sure you haven't
eaten anything since yesterday.
Eat something.
Will you..
Would you like a Hot Dog?
Don't beat me like a dog.
Save me kids.
Jugnu.
What now?
I'll go crazy if I stay here.
Come on, let's go back to India.
Are you crazy, Akhil?
You want to go back to India.
How will you face Saakshi?
Akhil, you are going
to let a dog live your life..
..and live like a dog yourself.
Akhil, you're the hero of this story.
And that dog's the villain.
And the hero always kills the villain.
Take the history of
Bollywood for example.
Gabbar, Shaakal, Mogambo.
They all died a dog's death.
And he's already a dog.
Easy job!
He has to die, and like a dog.
Do anything you want.
Shoot him, stab him,
slam him on the ground.. - No!
But kill him.
- No! No!
I can't kill anyone.
Not just anyone but the
one who's taken your wealth.
The one who has ruined your destiny.
The one who has brought
you on the street.
Akhil, I say for your right,
you have to kill the dog.
Akhil, you have to kill the dog.
Akhil, for the sake of your right,
just kill the dog.
You should kill the dog.
Kill the dog.
Kill that dog.
Kill the dog...Akshay Kumar.
You mutt...I'll kill you.
Entertainment,
it's time for your exercise.
Come. Climb on.
All the mills in the
world have closed down.
There's just one working mill,
that's the Treadmill.
Please climb up.
Climb up
This is not a local
train that he'll climb up.
Hello, Akhil.
- Hello.
Hello.
Bone from underpants.
I'll help you.
Wonderful.
You were really amazing.
So please make me
Entertainment's caretaker.
I see.
He served papa till his last breath.
- Yes.
And in return,
I'll serve him till his last.
Please.
Please. Please, sir.
Please don't say, Zardullah.
- Hey.
That's Habibullah!
Are you crazy?
Habibullah! Habibullah!
Sorry!
Fine.
From now on you will
always look after him. - Yes.
Habibullah!
- Yes.
Let the war begin.
When the dog comes and holds this,
he will..
...he'll get electrocuted and he'll die.
Come on.
Come on, everything's in place.
- Come on.
Switch it on.
The dog's coming.
Hurry up. HUT"! UP-
Let's get out of here.
He's here.
The dog didn't get electrocuted?
Check it.
- I did fix it properly.
Akhil!
Save me.
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
How much more are
you going to beat me?
Are you fine?
I am okay.
How's he going to die?
Help! Help!
Jugnu, save me.
I'll save you.
Akhil, my friend.
Stop it. Stop it. Stop hitting me.
You dog!
"Traitor, your heart is a traitor."
For you, it doesn't listen to me."
"Let's see who wins, head or me."
"Head has become mischeivous."
“I've been habituated to you.“
"World say, this is a bad habit."
He's addicted too.
He's gone.
Either he'll be lost in the jungle.
Or he'll be some wild animal's toast.
Let's watch it live.
- Forget it.
Come on.
- Forget it, let him die.
It'll be fun.
Careful Akhil, it's really high
Careful. Careful.
- Careful.
Akhil if we fall from here,
we'll get broken into pieces.
Akhil.
Stop.
Slop!
Akhil.
Where did my Akhil go?
Get rid of this problem from the root.
Why did you hit me?
We'll first make him
smell the chloroform.
..and then tie him up.
Or tie him up first and
then dope him with chloroform?
Is he gone?
He's done for,
Tie him up.
He'll fall now.
3000 crores is now all ours.
Pick him up.
Jugnu, let's leave him on the terrace.
Once he falls down,
there's no surviving.
Oh no...
No!
I won't spare you.
Oh no...
Akhil.
- Jugnu!
The dog is hungry.
Pour it.
Pour the entire thing.
He's dead for sure today.
Come on.
- Let's go.
He's dead for sure today.
Drink it sir.
Entertainment.
Drink it.
I am so hungry.
I've to get to the court as well.
I am getting late.
Zehreela (poisoned).
- Hey! That's Habibullah!
No. No.
Look, you should never interfere.
His head isn't beating.
Do something.
We'll be hanged for it.
What do I do? Yes.
Get up.
- Here, Akhil.
Wake him up.
Bravo.
Save him somehow.
This is an iron.
Close the door. Close the door.
Rascal, you handed me irons.
Water!
Give me water!
My chest is burning.
That mutt Entertainment
has made our life hell.
Pannalal you scoundrel.
Who gave you the idea to raise a dog?
Give that here.
- You rascals.
Who are those two with him?
- Open the door.
They look like villains.
Look.
He looks like the
villain from Dabbang 1..
..and he is from Dabbang 2. Isn't it?
But...how are they connected
with this family?
Hey what are you doing?
Get up.
Very good, brother Karan.
Come on, Arjun.
- Yes.
My Lace is open.
Brother, give me a minute.
I told you,
Arjun, I don't want any goof up.
You did.
But mother always said..
..if your shoe-laces are open,
don't run.
Don't be so mad, brother.
I am your own blood.
- Yes.
But because of your actions
I feel like murdering you.
You're a criminal mind, after all..
..it's bound to have such thoughts.
You'll really go far, Arjun.
Wherever you go,
people will say "Keep moving".
You won't be able to
sell yourself if you want to.
I'm sure you were born
after 1000 dogs died.
But you're still alive.
You mean...l am a dog?
Are you asking or telling,
brother Karan?
Arjun.
Mother was right you don't love me.
After all, I'm your step-brother.
"When has the sun been
away from the sky.."
"..when has the moon been
away from the rays."
"When has aroma been
away from breeze..
..when has spring being
away from the garden"
“This is the bond of love.“
"Its confluence of many centuries."
I love you a lot.
You see, were supposed
to be released in 2 days.
But since it was your birthday.
...I planned this escape.
You won't find a brother like me.
I can give it in writing.
And if there is, then...
You eat.
What happened, brother?
Why did your eyes widen?
Pannalal Johri is dead.
This means, brother..
...the one we've trying to kill
all these years, is finally dead.
The old man.
Every time we tried to kill him..
..his pet dog would
interfere and save him.
Brother, now we're the
heir to his 3000 crore..
..because we're his first cousins?
Second!
But what's important is...
..we're his only relatives.
Then we should prepare to
get out of here, brother Karan.
Arjun, stop being so brazen.
We'll be released in 2 days.
And next day we'll
enter the Johri Mansion.
WOW, Akhil.
I'll have to mention
that it's a fabulous mansion.
So awesome.
It's an exquisite place.
I bet you spent quite a lot on it.
There's an antique fan as well.
Is this male or female?
Male or female?
I mean is it Bajaj or Usha?
By the way...the owner of this house..
..has gone to his favorite
place Snow white Arena..
..which is 3 hours away from here.
Because that's the
only place where it snow falls.
I see.
By the way,
what would you like to have?
I will drink. That too neat.
You should've added water.
No, no. This is my
daughter's in-laws home.
Water is forbidden for me here.
I would like to get my daughter..
...married to the heir of this house.
The heir of this house?
Yes.
With your daughter?
- Yes.
He's Enter..
Yes, he has already entered...
in her heart
Curses!
He's.. - Exactly,
they are crazy about each other.
Say something.
She keeps barking in the serials.
She barks?
- Yes.
Do something.
Ready?
Now see.
Action.
Uncle. I swear on God..
..we're two bodies, one soul.
- Wonderful.
He's my mornings and my dawn.
- Very good.
His feet...is where my pilgrimages lie.
- Wonderful.
He has four legs as well.
But how is this possible?
You barked.
Not me, maybe it came from there..
See...
...they're eyeing each
other like Romeo-Juliet.
Uncle, this is the effect
of love at first sight.
You mean it's about
love at first bite.
Fine, it's done.
Okay.
Come on.
Pay respects to your
future father-in-law.
Come on.
Pay respects to your
future father-in-law.
Come, son-in-law.
Why are you standing there?
Come on.
What's this?
What's what?
Not what, what.
What's this?
He's your son-in-law.
Son...
My..
The heir to 3000 crore.
Pannalal Johri's heir,
Entertainment.
You mean...Pannalal Johri..
..gave 3000 crore
to this dog and died.
Yes.
Papa.
Papa, please listen..
- Uncle, please listen.
Please, listen.
Give me one more chance.
I'll keep your daughter happy.
Just one chance.
I'll be rich.
I promise you.
Please listen to me.
My fate will change.
Your fate will never change.
Papa, please.
- Get in.
You'll always be poor.
What's the point of
being Pannalal Johri's son?
You turned out to be
a disappointment.
And that dog Entertainment..
..turned out to be the
real heir to the wealth.
Dog?
Uncle, listen to me.
Akhil Lokhande,
forget Saakshi forever.
“I want to ask God what has he done.“
"Why did he take back the gift
he had bestowed me upon?"
The heir to 3000 crore...a dog.
Stop the car!
What happened?
Dear...
...do you admit that, post marriage..
...every man becomes a dog.
I suggest that...
...you marry the dog.
Papa!
That rascal Pannalal gave
all his wealth to that dog.
But that dog...separated
me from Saakshi forever, Jugnu.
That's why, Akhil..
...we'll have to think
of a full-proof plan..
..to kill the dog.
What's to think?
Let's shoot him.
We won't get the wealth
if we kill the dog.
It will go to that son of his.
So what do we do?
Expiry date.
How long do dogs live?
Maximum 12-13 years.
That Entertainment
will conk out in few years.
For now we've just one target.
Akhil.
And we'll have to
find a special place..
..to take care of him.
And that special place is...
Snow White Arena.
I will kill that dog
in his favorite place.
Akhil, you're done for.
Entertainment, you're done for!
I see.
So tomorrow he's
going to kill the dog.
And we wolves. .
.. Will kill him.
One arrow...we kill two sparrows.
But, brother,
why will we kill sparrows?
Go...fetch!
Yes.
Die you rascal!
Akhil!
Entertainment!
- Akhil.
Akhil, what are you doing?
Have you gone crazy?
We got what we wanted.
He's dead.
He saved my life.
Entertainment!
Akhil.
Today...
...an animal taught me
a lesson on humanity.
Akhil.
Today...
...an animal taught me
a lesson on humanity.
"What is loyalty and what is trust."
Entertainment!
“..I have learnt it from you.“
"What is head and what is love.."
“I have learnt it from you.“
I must admit, he's two-in-one.
He was Royal.
But the dog's loyal as well.
Dog?
No Entenainment.
Entertainment.
Earlier, when we tried
to bump-off Pannalal..
..the dog interfered.
And even this time,
he interfered in our plans.
We'll have to do something, Arjun.
Or that dog will
always taint our face.
By the way,
brother, your face looks tainted.
Johri sir..
Mr. Johri..
Father.
I forgive you for whatever
you did with your this son.
And for whatever I did with your son..
...I apologies for it.
I must admit.
You turned out to be
a true diamond merchant.
You're a good assessor.
Entertainment!
Only a real assessor
can recognize a true gem.
Pannalal Johri.
Your son deserves all this.
Not this son.
See you, father.
Entertainment...
...do you know why the truth hurts.
Because truth has a point.
And that point is...
...that you're right and I am wrong.
Sorry...for trying to kill you.
Thank you...
..for showing me the way.
Goodbye.
And yes...
...if anyone calls me a dog..
...I'll consider it an honor.
Sanjay Leela Bhansali.
- What?
The names of my three lawyers.
Mr. Sanjay.
Ms. Leela and Mr. Bhansali.
Poor chaps have been doing
rounds of the court for us.
Court?
- Yes.
Films succeed
because of three things.
And these days our case
is also thriving on three things.
Entertainment!
What?
- Well, you're forgetting..
..that many years ago,
Pannalal Johri..
...had started a Private Ltd Company.
...called The Entertainment Company.
You're right.
But for his dear Entertainment.
But, Pannalal Johri made
his second cousins, which is us..
..the major shareholders.
But what did you do under
the pretext of that relation.
Forging!
Pannalal Johri caught
you two red-handed..
..and also fired you two.
I see.
Arjun, we didn't receive
any termination order.
Not at all.
What do you want to prove?
Just that we're still
the existing owners..
...of that Entertainment Company.
And according to
Mr. Pannalal Johri's Will...
By the way, why am I talking to you?
Ms. Leela,
I'm sure you've a copy of that Will.
Please read it out.
I, Pannalal Johri,
in my right state of mind..
...bequeath my entire property.
...and bank balance to Entertainment.
Yes!
Entertainment Company belongs to us..
...and this property's
in the name of Entertainment.
So, the heir to 3000 crore
is not this dog, but..
...it's the owners of the
company called Entertainment!
Entertainment!
But in Will, doesn't mention company..
..instead it's loyal dog.
...of the word 'Dog' in the will.
The reason is that he
never considered him a dog.
Court doesn't believe in emotions..
..it believes n facts, Mr. Dracula.
That's Habibullah!
And listen.
If there's no 'Dog'
mentioned in the Will..
...then there's no
'Company' mentioned either.
Very smart.
And now..
Not you.
In the company of our lawyers,
the court will decide..
..and also prove who's the rascal..
..and who's a mangy cur.
After all the views..
...Court is passing the
judgment in the favour of...
Karan and Arjun, They are the
rightful owner Of the Johri Empire.
Pannalal Johri's wealth...
goes to these two rascals!
How?
We'll tell you.
You see...a good lawyer knows the law.
And the best lawyer knows the judge.
1500 for me..
- And 1500 for me.
You dog,
I know you understand everything.
Now listen to me carefully.
Actually,
you're no more than a street-mutt.
So stay there.
If you need to pee,
then find a lamp-post.
If you feel hungry.
..then feed on the left-over
from the waste-dump.
You're a dog, so live like one.
Right, brother.
Yes, but before that.
Let's take back what's ours.
What are you doing?
Along with this property,
this leash belongs to us too.
And stopping us means
breaking the law.
Time flies by when you're with a kin.
But with time you
know who your kin is.
'Look what I brought for you.'
'Look'
'Just for you.'
'Since you entered my life..'
' . .there's only entertainment.'
'No sorrows.'
'You're not my son,
but you're no less either.'
Get out!
- Get lost!
Get lost!
Johri's dog.
- Got nowhere to go.
Lord, even in your presence..
Loyalty has lost.
And betrayal won!
Why are you looking that way?
You think someone
will come to help us..
..from that direction.
Surprised.
How I came back?
I was about to board
the flight to India..
..when I read this news.
I had to come.
You see, father's last wish was..
..that you be the heir to this wealth.
And...a son will have
to do something.
..to fulfill his father's last wish.
After all, I am his blood.
DNA.
Daddy's Najayaz Aulad
(Daddy's illegitimate son).
But...his son.
Earlier I formed a bond
with father for the wealth.
Now, for the sake of that same bond..
...I will get you your wealth back.
And yes, Entenainment.
We're with you.
Just wait and watch.
We'll first have to break
Karan and Arjun's unity.
And then their strength will be over.
And then we'll make them
confess to their crimes..
..and have them thrown
out in the streets.
What do you say, Akhil?
Wonderful. Amazing. I'm speechless.
But it's very difficult
to separate these two brothers.
Don't worry about that,
Ab...dulah, sir.
We'll do what the British did with us!
Divide...and Rule!
Now we dogs...
...will teach those rascals a lesson.
Careful, brother.
Entertainment.
I guess he's here for revenge.
Revenge?
You want revenge?
How will you do it?
Like Rajnikanth.
Or like Spiderman.
What can one dog do?
What can he do?
I'll show him...by running
over him with my car. Come on.
Brother, I'll run-over him.
No, I'll do it, I'm the elder one.
I am the younger one.
Why don't you understand?
It's just one dog.
You won't look good
running over one dog.
I want to run over him.
Brother, do you love me or not?
What's brotherhood
got to do with our love?
Listen to me..
- But..
With this car,
we'll send him off on his final..
Wait!
Stay!
Sit!
Roadside Entenainment.
At first even I thought
they were wrong.
But the court of
Bangkok opened my eyes.
..and proved that
my father's 3000 crore..
...belongs to them, and not you.
If anyone has anything to say,
then speak now.
You Bulldog.
You behave like a dog..
..but got the name
of a different animal.
Bull.
Stop growling...Pug!
I'll make you dance like Shakira,
get that.
And you....German Shepherd.
Has your father ever been to Germany?
And you...Boxer!
Did your dad ever
put on boxing gloves?
And St. Bernard.
If I had a face like yours.
...I would've sued my parents.
Now...if anyone has the guts,
then come and face me.
What are you doing?
Go away. Leave.
Leave!
I called for a mobile-tower.
..where did this sim-card come from?
Look, I don't like jokes.
This shorty is no match for me.
Who's got the guts to face me?
Sir, move back.
They're about to attack, sir.
You're a real player.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Sir, take my advice.
And get out of here in your car.
Go on.
- Yes.
Let's go.
Akhil.
Sir, you two hide in the jungle.
I'll deal with them.
- Run!
"Who let the dogs out?"
Akhil.
- What?
Down there.
Oh my Dog!
Sir, your death's between his jaws.
What do I do?
Reverse psychology.
He wants you to worry.
But you laugh instead.
Laugh.
Before he blows your fuse,
confuse the dog.
The ball is in his court
Help!
Akhil.
Oh my Dog!
Help! Save me.
Save us both.
Save you both.
Idea, sir.
Where are you going?
Sir...don't worry.
I have in my clutches,
the leader of these dogs.
Call your friends back.
Tell them to get out of here.
- Akhil.
Say it aloud.
Yes!
Bite me. Pretend to bite me.
He bit me.
Amazing.
You almost killed that dog.
Sir, am I cigarette to kill him.
I mean you scattered them like leaves.
Am I a leaf-blower?
We mean you stole our hearts.
Am I the government who will steal?
I see. Fire with satire.
Brave man. Brave man.
Please look after yourself.
Especially from those dogs.
Today they were a 100...
..tomorrow they can come back as 200.
He bit me really hard.
- Show.
Show.
- Forget it.
Show it.
- What can you do?
See you.
Arjun, he's right.
Brother, shall we hire him.
Let's do.
It will be fun.
The heir to 3000 crore..
...will be our servant
and do our bidding.
And he'll also protect us.
We'll have our cakes
and get to eat it too.
Don't remind me of that.
Sorry!
Where did he go?
Are they back?
No, no, no, listen.
Will you work for us?
Driver... - Cum Bodyguard..
- Cum Watchman.
Cum..
Since you're insisting so much...
I'll come.
Made in Thailand.
Sell in thairon
Why did you stop?
Sir...the castor oil's over.
I'll go get it.
- Quickly.
Hello.
- Akhil.
Saakshi.
Where are you?
- In Bangkok.
Whose Kok?
- I am in Bangkok.
Oh, you're in Bangkok.
Akhil, father's trying
to find me a NRI husband.
He still has 2 months
left on his tourist visa.
What kind of Dad, you gave birth to?
You..
- Saakshi.
Saakshi. Saakshi.
- Yes, papa.
Saakshi. listen.
I've found an NRI husband for you.
He only doesn't have hand and limbs.
Sometimes you'll have to
take him to the mall in this bag.
Papa!
Where are you getting
the castor oil from?
Where are you, Akhil?
I am back.
Don't get bored,
I'll switch on the television.
WOW!
Indian woman!
Virtues on her mind, sari on her body.
Don't bore me.
This is what you call beauty.
One piece item in two piece bikini.
"Looks amazing."
Bikinis don't have the etiquette..
...that a 'Sari' and
'Salwar Kameez' have.
Have you heard that song?
Have you?
- Which one?
"She looked amazing..
"..covered in the veil."
Sir's right. He's right.
She looked amazing..
..because she was
covered only in a viel.
Sir, the young sir's right as well.
Bindi on the forehead,
kohl in the eyes..
..that's what you call a girl.
A girl is someone
who has no cover or slip.
Just long legs.
Shut up!
'Sanskrit', 'Sabhyata', 'Sanskaar'.
(Cultured, Civilized, Virtue).
Sexy, seductive, sensuality.
The girl should be
reflection of your mother.
I've the perfect idea
for 'Divide and Rule'.
I'll have to bring
Saakshi in the picture.
And for that I'll have to find..
...a millionaire
son-in-law for his father.
Dear, finally I found
a millionaire son-in-law.
Your education.
- B.Com.
I'm B.Com.
- Who cares what ‘Com’ (religion) you are.
Are you educated?
- Yes.
Saakshi, what's your favorite color?
Yellow.
Yellow! Yellow!
Dear, then you'll
definitely like his teeth.
Son, show her your teeth.
Papa, he's got three
negative qualities.
He smokes, drinks and gambles.
Excuse me.
I've something positive as well.
Tell her. Tell her.
I am HIV+
Papa, not here. Papa, not here.
Papa, not here.
"Johnny Johnny.."
'Johnny Johnny. .
“I've not been drinking.“
“I've been forced to drink.“
I had sworn, first millionaire..
..then Saakshi's husband.
You? Millionaire?
It's the dog who's rich.
How did you get rich?
You see...Entertainment
transferred all his wealth..
to Akhil Johri...
Sorry, sir.
And made him rich.
How?
- BY Putting his paw
Habibullah sir, please show him.
Show him.
Take a look.
The paw is right here.
Show me as well.
Papa, it's true.
My beloved's here to hold my hand..
..in his hi-fi boat.
- Star Plus, stop.
Hey, Jamila.
- Hey! That's Habibullah.
Fine, fine.
Tell me something.
What overcame this dog..
..that he gave his wealth to him.
Entenainment says..
..how can the master's
son be a servant.
I see.
Him...this dog...said that to you.
Like this.
I mean he spoke from his mouth.
Where do you speak from?
I knew it, you won't believe all this.
This dog speaks.
Watch.
Entertainment, tell them
what rose up in stock market today.
See the prices rose up.
Tell us one city of Gujarat.
See. Bhavnagar.
What should we never
differentiate between?
Differences
See.
Hey stop your nonsense.
Do you think he's crazy?
You think you'll take my Saakshi..
...I mean his Saakshi
by doing this antics.
And he'll agree.
Why wouldn't I?
I'll give him a hug.
This dog has made him rich.
Akhil, Saakshi's all yours.
And you get lost.
Get lost!
Son.
- Yes.
Here's the engagement ring.
Diamond.
You get the diamond.
Congratulations.
Give me a hug, son.
The king's finally got his queen.
I got my Saakshi.
Karan-Arjun.
Your idea isn't bad.
But..
- No ifs or buts, sister-in-law.
We just need your dates.
Please don't refuse us.
Because you're only hope.
You see, you'll have
to work your charm in a humble way.
Otherwise we'll be...
- Jugnu!
In a big mess.
Listen to me.
I'll help all of you to create
a rift between Karan and Arjun.
Wonderful.
And also get Entertainment his right.
Do you know why?
This man here...
...is my life.
And you saved his life.
Thank you.
Just wait and watch..
..how I will fulfill your desires.
Now I'll separate those two..
..posing as Savitri for
Karan and Sonia for Arjun.
Swear on Balaji.
- My baby.
"Why do you wander here and there?"
"O little buddy!"
“I'll hypnotize your heart.“
“I like your synchronized moves.“
"O little buddy!"
"Baby I got my eyes on you."
"From the tip to the toes
To the lip to the nose."
“Make it wiggle.. wiggle.“
"Don't give me the dose of love,
it's daily squabble."
“Make it jiggle.- jiggle?'
“I am getting a little naughty.“
“I want you to get mischievous too.“
"O little buddy!"
“I am getting a little naughty.“
“I want you to get mischievous.“
"And if something untoward happens."
"It'll be so much fun."
"Do you or do you not?"
"Do you trust me or not?"
“Your benevolence's is beyond par.“
"How I wonder you are."
"O little buddy!"
"The garland around
my neck is meant for you."
“I've hidden your photo in my wallet.“
"The garland around
my neck is meant for you."
“I've hidden your photo in my wallet.“
“I understand that you do.“
“I understand that you love me.“
“Your benevolence's is beyond par.“
"How I wonder you are."
“Every book of love is about
sin and merit.“
"Minus 1, 2, 3
ain't no lunches for free."
“Every book of love is about
sin and merit.“
"So beg, borrow and run,
ain't no lunches for free."
"How long am I going
to just watch and yearn?"
“I've played the semi-final.“
"When are we going
to play the finals?"
"How long am I going
to just watch and yearn?"
“I've played the semi-final.“
"When are we going
to play the finals?"
“I am also waiting for it.“
“Your benevolence's. . .“
“Your benevolence's is beyond par.“
"How I wonder you are."
"O little buddy!"
"Your benevolence .."
Love's making me fly.
Trapped..
What?
In love.
Sir's in love.
Who's the fonunate?
I am the fortunate boy.
You know,
I am in love with my 36-24-36.
I love you Sonia.
- No!
Really? You swear.
And she's on her way here.
Tell her about your feelings, sir.
You're right.
- Yes.
Today I will tell
her about my feelings,
I..
- Hey, Villain!
"Why do you wander here and there?"
Sir...
Sir, what just happened?
She has stripped all her clothes.
The virtuous saga has
become a vulgar story.
She's wearing a new-born
baby's outfit, sir.
Take a look, sir.
Sir, for my sake take a look.
Sir, take a look.
I knew it, you'll be
stupefied to see me like this.
Close your mouth.
Sir, she's completely covered.
Such snowfall on the bare mountain.
I love someone else.
And he's the one who's
given me this fashion.
And he's someone who
knew we had a connection.
..but still he gave
me a new definition of love.
Who is he?
Your brother.
Sir.
Brother has betrayed his brother.
Karen!
Arjun!
What will you say now?
What will you say to me?
- Correct.
I was the one who talked,
you always cheated. Cheat.
Insulting your elder brother.
Don't forget...
...when you were in
your mother's womb..
...I was in 1st grade.
Hold on.
When I was in 5th grade,
you were still in 1st.
So what?
But I was the one who
looked after you the most.
Remember...
...when mother used to
tell us ghost stories.
..you used to get scared.
And who used to hold your hands?
You.
Because you were scared of ghosts.
That's why you used to hold my hands.
You're an expert
in humiliating people.
Now you tried to tarnish my honor.
Right now you're stealing my dialogue.
You're the one who tarnished my honor.
Arjun.
I've two minds to hit you.
Rubbish, you don't
even have a single mind.
Arjun!
Hit him. Hit him.
- Hit him!
Hit him!
Divide and rule. Hit him!
Mother was right.
You don't love me.
After all I'm your step-brother.
"When has the sun been
away from the sky.."
"..when has the moon been
away from the rays."
"When has aroma been
away from breeze..
From where is this playing?
“This is the bond of love.“
"Its confluence of many centuries."
You keep the girl.
No, brother. You're the elder one.
You keep her.
To hell with the cheap
girl who tries to separate us.
They both turned out to be over-smart
Because they know, if they separate..
..they will have to divide the wealth.
Earlier they were separate,
but now they are one.
One!
Akhil, our plan's flopped.
Why don't you find a new solution?
Am I a scientist to find a solution?
I mean find a way.
I am a traffic constable
to find the way?
We'll have to find a mode.
- Am I a farmer to find a mode?
No!
These Karan Arjun are really unique.
Sometimes their mother's
song starts playing.
Sometimes their
mother's ghost stories..
Hold on!
'It's a ghost film.
I am scared .'
Ghost.
- Ghost?
Yes, I've seen and heard myself.
Karan and Arjun are scared of ghosts.
Really?
- Yes.
Now we'll bring a ghost in their life.
But we need a ghost or spirit
or dead body to scare them.
We have a dead body.
Whose?
Arjun, when I drink a peg,
I don't listen to anyone.
Brother, when I drink two pegs..
...I don't listen to myself.
I see!
When I drink three pegs...
no one listens to me.
Rascal, entertaining yourself.
My Entertainment died
of hunger and thirst.
Congratulations.
Make another peg.
How about a drink, Gorilla.
That's Habibullah.
My Karan-Arjun will come.
My Karan-Arjun will surely come.
Huh, My Entertainment will come.
You made him worry,
his soul won't spare you.
His spirit will come after you.
Let go.
Sir.
Sir, it's me.
Me.
Tell him it's me.
It's him.
- Your servant.
Right.
They say as soon as
you kill a pet animal..
...their spirit starts
wandering around.
That's exactly
what I used to say.
Get lost!
But, no sir.
After what happened
with my friend Billa..
That's it.
What happened with Billa?
- Nothing.
Tell us.
No, no.
- Say it.
No, no..
- Forget it, brother.
Listen.
Once my friend Billa..
...killed a cat on a moonless night.
Billa killed a cat.
- Yes.
The same night,
when she was murdered..
..Billa was sitting
on his rocking chair.
And the chair..
Why's the chair squeaking so much?
It was second-hand, sir.
On that dark night,
a dark crow sitting on a dark branch..
..Started squawking loudly.
And the door to Billa's
room started opening.
Why's the door opening for so long?
It's opening in slow motion.
As soon as the door opened..
..Billa was facing the cat.
The cat's head was in her paw.
And she was sweetly saying..
What did she say?
Say it loudly.
Meow!
Me-ow!
What did Billa say?
- Billa screamed.
What?
I had killed the cat.
But the cat said...
Is it your wedding night
that you killed the cat?
Hearing this Billa was stunned.
..just like you two are.
The cat jumped in Billa's mouth..
..and came out the
same way you're scared
...came out the same way
you're scared.
You're ruined.
You're two ruined.
Help.
"Johnny Johnny.."
Who switched on the television?
Hello.
Ghost!
Entertainment!
Sir.
Here I am.
- Where?
Look. Here.
Back here.
Why did you climb up on the deer?
- Ghost.
Sir, there's no ghost.
This is a conspiracy to scare you.
So that you suffer
a head-attack and die.
What are you saying?
Didn't you hear?
I'll say it again.
This is a conspiracy to scare you.
So that you suffer
a head-attack and die.
Who wants to kill me?
- Who?
Your own brother.
Step-brother.
You don't believe me, do you?
- No.
I was cleaning your brother's room..
..and you know what I found.
This. Vacuum cleaner.
They were trying to scare
you using this on the dog.
On the ceiling.
This CD player.
It's a recording of scary voices.
By showing you a
DVD of duplicate dog..
..and putting a wig on him.
By scaring you to death
or driving you crazy..
..he wants to be the
heir to the entire 3000 crore.
Meaning?
Time flies by when you're with a kin.
But with time you
know who your kin is.
Karan!
- Arjun!
You'll have to pay dearly
for locking horns with me.
Right.
As if I'm offering discount
on locking horns with me.
I respected you equal to god,
but you turned out to be a Godzilla.
I thought we were of same blood,
but you turned out to be a Blood Cancer.
What if their mother's
song starts playing again?
Akhil, our plan will flop.
Do something.
I will have to raise my hand today.
I'm not a coward.
Will you hit me?
Yes, I will.
Will you hit your elder brother?
- Yes, I will.
Enough, Arjun.
- Get lost.
Enough, Arjun..
- I am your step brother.
“This is the bond of love.“
How dare you hit your elder brother?
And you..
- Don't say a word.
Get lost!
Shoot it. Shoot it.
- I am.
I bribed the judge
to make you a millionaire.
Stop barking.
That dog's the real heir.
You cheated everyone, me too.
Come on. Our job's done.
DVD?
Brother, DVD?
DVD from above.
That means someone's
recording our conversation.
Show me.
Hey!
Entenainment is alive.
He was never dead, sir.
I may not be God-gifted,
but I'm definitely dog-gifted.
And she's..
I am not your Savitri or your Sonia.
I am just his Saakshi.
And thanks to this CD..
...this wealth will
be once be Entertainment's.
Greetings.
In shonmyour days are over.
And you'll pay for your deeds in jail.
Absolutely wrong.
I'll crush you, Akhil.
Are you flour?
Say something.
I will wash you down.
- Are you a bucket.
We will finish you?
- Are you climax?
BOYS!
Snatch the DVD from this dog.
Entertainment...run!
Sunny Deol has turned
into Sunny Leone.
Akhil.
- Yes.
Run. I'll teach her a lesson.
Take care.
Only a woman can
understand another woman.
Rascals ran away.
Sorry! Sorry!
Attack!
He's not a dog, he's my brother.
I've got emotions for him here.
And for people like you,
I've got action right here.
Attack!
Brother. Brother.
My friend's life is in danger.
We'll have to do something.
Do something please.
Do what.
Yes, yes.
Ready Steady go.
Go.
Allah!
Chaku-Ia (hand me the knife).
No, Habibullah!
Hand me the knife!
Sorry!
Rascal. Scoundrel.
Were you born upside down?
Forgive me.
Last chance.
Sorry! Sorry!
Before he stabs me
with the fourth knife..
...please kill me God.
Kill me.
- Sorry.
Buy a knife.
Knife-seller.
Buy knives for cheap.
15 Rs. a piece.
- Habibullah!
Cheating. Cheating.
“This is the bond of love.“
"Its confluence of many centuries."
Stay on the side, Entertainment.
Akhil.
Entertainment!
He's still alive.
We've removed the bullet.
But I am sorry,
his heart is not responding.
He's fine.
Akhil.
Careful.
Just blink and I'll understand.
Is it paining a lot?
Do you know what that
crazy doctor's saying?
He's lost his mind.
He's uttering nonsense.
What was he saying outside?
Yes.
Your heart isn't responding.
You..
He's talking rubbish.
He's crazy.
He doesn't know that you're a fighter.
Right?
That's more like it.
You've to dance at my wedding as well.
I've to get you married as well.
That female dog from the jungle,
the one you ran after.
I never saw you run so fast.
You'll marry her, won't you?
That's more like it.
You won't leave me, will you?
Open your eyes!
Open your eyes.
Who do you think you are?
First you saved my father's life.
Then you saved my life so many times.
Do you have the right to saving lives?
Will you show all the loyalty?
Can't we humans do anything for you?
But you're not loyal.
You're leaving me.
You're a traitor.
His head is responding.
Quick, nurse.
"What is loyalty and what is trust."
“..l have learnt it from you.“
"What is head and what is
ove.."
“..l have learnt it from you.“
Akhil.
He saved your life.
And anyone who has his love.
..is richer than any millionaire.
Sir, you're absolutely right.
No matter how hard you try..
..you won't find someone like him.
Let it be.
Sorry, sir.
You're right.
Akhil, didn't the police..
- Saakshi.
He showed his humanity again.
He said,
give them a chance to reform.
..drop all the charges against them.
After all we four are cousins.
Yes, we're all cousins.
I say this from my heart
We're sorry.
Brother Akhil, I had a small doubt.
He said we're cousins.
Him. From his mouth.
Yes, he can speak.
Brother in English,
'Bhai in Hindi and in Marathi.
See. "Bhau" (Brother)
What should we always have in life?
Bhow.
See. Good nature.
And even after everything he did..
..what is he not showing?
See.
He isn't showing off.
Now I pronounce you husband and wife.
And you too.
"My brother chocolate boy."
"He was the women's joy."
"He swapped all girls
with his sweet-talks."
"Brother was like Vanilla."
"When he got a chance."
"He took away all the kisses."
"Your youth's come to an end."
“All your lovers became my friends.“
“Call the DJ ."
"It's my brother's wedding."
"Uncork the bottles."
"It's trending on Twitter."
"It's my brother's wedding."
"Pending for a longtime."
"My brother asked me
the meaning of marriage."
“I said, rest of your life
has become a punishment.“
"My brother asked me
what about my independence."
“I said you'll face the
same plight as your daddy.“
“I hope no one jinxes your pair.“
“I pray you're never scared
of your wife.“
“Someone wish him good luck.“
"It's my brother's wedding."
"Uncork the bottles."
Basanti, you won't dance
in front of these dogs.
Why won't she?
We dogs have paid for the ticket.
Dance!
"My brother."
“Soon our weddin recession
will come down the lane.“
“Every dog has his day,
my day will come too.“
"It's the season of weddings,
the priest's ready."
"Brother will perform the rites,
don't be so rude."
"The guests will be busy
doing their thing."
"And two dreams will fit
in a single budget."
"Some play the band."
“I've been hooked too.“
"Uncork the bottles."
"It's trending on Twitter."
"It's my brother's wedding."
"Pending for a longtime."
He's fallen.
Oh, the shoe hit her face.
Hey! Catch him.
They're still working on my makeup.
As you pay...so shall you reap.
“Seems like he has sliced
both sides of every capsule.“
What do you mean?
Because we don't see any side-effect.