'Children are humans too.'
'They are innocent and truthful
than elders.'
'They don't have a wall of cunningness
around them.'
'For their betterment we need...
...to educate them in school...
...they should get such a world...
...where's there's love and affection.'
'Guru Ravindranath Tagore.'
"Beloved is in every color of heart."
"He is very stone hearted."
"The color of henna."
"Beloved has gone abroad."
"He hasn't sent any letter."
"How can I live without you?"
(Horn blares)
Come here... Come on. Come here...
Where is Dulari Devi School?
Take a left turn and then a right turn...
...you'll find a well...
...the Dulari Devi School is
just opposite to it.
Do you belong to the same village?
-We belong to the same school.
Is it? Will you take me there?
In your car?
-Yes.
Sit inside. Come on.
Tell me your names.
Avdesh.
-Hari.
Gorak.
My name is Neha.
Don't you have school today?
I have, but I don't go.
-Why?
The master is very shrew.
He thrashes us badly.
Hereafter, you have to
go to school every day.
I have come to build
a big school in your village.
Is it?
Will you drink water?
Here.
It is fun to sit your car.
Where's the cool breeze coming from?
From here.
(Laughs)
Stop the car... drop us here...
drop us here.
You'll find the school ahead.
We're going.
How does it open? Tell me.
It opened. Let's go.
-Hey, stop.
Let's go. Let's go.
-Hey, come on out.
Avdesh.
Do you want chocolates?
Wait, I'll come.
Come.
Is it for me?
-Yes, it is for you.
Give me one.
-Okay, I'll give you.
This is for you and this for you.
Chocolates.
-Yes.
You also have one.
Here are some books for you.
Take a left and you'll find the school.
-Let's go.
Hey?
Hey, look... the car is so nice.
2 x 2 = 4!
-It is so nice.
I think someone has come.
-2 x 3 = 6.
Where's the headmaster? Let's go.
(Indistinct chatter)
She is going in.
2 x 7 = 14.
Greetings.
-Greetings.
Who do you want to meet?
-I want to meet the headmaster.
He is having bath. Look there.
Hail Goddess Ganges!
Come, let's go.
Hey children, go to your classrooms!
-Let's go.
They are children of this village...
come on.
Come, please have a seat.
You sit here and I'll
call the headmaster.
Have a seat. I'll be back.
2 x 6=12
2 x 7 =14
Headmaster!
Hiralal, what's the matter?
-There's a woman to meet you.
Yes, I spoke to the collector.
Is she here?
Yes.
-Hurry up, give me the towel.
Here.
Madam, he's the headmaster.
Mr. Ramnarayan Jha.
-Greetings.
Greetings, my name is Neha Malini.
Neha Malini?
I've heard about Hema Malini.
You are Neha Malini.
Wonderful. Great. Great.
Have a seat. (Chuckles)
So, you've come from Delhi.
-Yes.
I was in US two months ago,
then I came to Delhi...
...then here.
-US?
America.
-America?
Oh, the same America,
where it is night and here it is day?
Hiralal, get two teas.
I've ordered for it.
Special? Okay.
-Yes.
What is this? School map?
Wonderful. It is nice.
It is very big too.
Like King Akbar built Taj Mahal...
...you've come to build a school.
Taj Mahal was not built by Akbar,
but by Shah Jahan.
(Laughs)
Yes, but King Akbar thought about it.
What say?
King Akbar thought about it, right?
Yes...
-Absolutely.
What are you doing here?
Go and teach the children.
(Clears throat)
King Akbar thought about it.
Tea...
Here...
Don't you study?
-No.
I make tea for the teachers.
Yes. He makes nice tea.
You have it... Here, have tea.
Hey! Hey! Go away!
(Chuckles)
Master, after toiling very hard
and taking help from many people...
...I have arranged for this fund.
-Okay.
You have to make a trust
of local people here.
The school building
will be built in their supervision.
Yes, I had spoken the collector.
He said the trust must
consist of five members.
I've spoken to the village chief,
there's an old minister of our village...
...Mr. Kailash... he's very educated.
Moreover, I am present here.
And two masters...
Okay, if you feel,
call the others tomorrow.
I'll come tomorrow.
Okay, as you wish.
-Okay.
I shall leave.
-Please, come.
Ganga!
What is going on there?
Move them from here. -Hey, go away!
Hey, get down!
Master, I am getting down.
-Do you think it belongs to you?
Hey, how dare you hit a stone!
I will thrash you to pulp.
I will teach you a lesson.
You scoundrel.
I will debar you from the school.
Scoundrel, escaped.
Ms. Neha, you don't worry.
I'll catch hold of him at home.
He will fall on your feet and apologize.
-No need.
Master, I think some children
don't come to school at all.
I met three children from the school...
...they came till here
showing me the way...
...but didn't come inside the school.
Ms. Neha Malini,
children don't come to study here.
They come here to play.
You tell me their names,
I'll get them from their homes.
They said their names were
Hari, Gorak, and Avdesh.
Hari, Gorak, and Avdesh?
Where did you find those three guys?
Why?
-Are you alright?
Yes.
Hope those guys didn't harm you.
-No.
Those three guys are criminals.
What are you saying, Master?
-I'm telling the truth.
They were children aged 12-14 years.
Ms. Neha, they've created chaos
in the entire area.
They've murdered four people.
-Murder?
Yes...
-Ms. Neha, forget it.
We'll concentrate on the school.
(Phone ringing)
Dad?
(Dad)-How are you, my dear?
Have you reached the village?
-Yes, I've arrived.
What is the name of the village?
-Birva.
I know you are very excited
as this was your dream.
Dad, I want to celebrate my birthday
with you and mom this year.
Dear, you know, it is not possible.
I am sorry, dear. You didn't get our
love together, but got it separately.
But fulfill your dream for
which you went to that village.
You are happy, I am happy.
Take care.
I am happy, dad.
I love you.
(Neha) DM sir, this school is my dream.
And I need your help.
-You are doing a great job.
I met three children on the way.
-Okay.
They must be aged 12-13 years.
They were innocent.
Then I learnt that they were criminals.
Our police is trying very hard
to nab those three children.
You don't worry.
Sir, I am not worried about myself.
I am worried for those children.
I was a software engineer in America.
I left everything and have come here.
I will finish my work and leave.
(Indistinct chatter)
Greetings, madam. Please, come.
Look there. They've killed someone.
Please, come.
-Who did they kill?
Please come, madam.
Take him out. Come on.
Please, come.
If you get any news about
those three guys, let us know.
Tell their parents to come
and meet me in the police station.
Once if I get hold of them.
Listen...
Who is this madam?
-She's here to build a school.
Really?
Pick up the dead body.
Pick up the dead body!
Careful...
-Come on, pick it up.
Move aside... Move aside.
Can't you hear me?
-Brother, move.
Who killed them?
-Those three guys killed him.
They met you yesterday.
He was constable Mahadev.
They killed him too. Let's go, headmaster
must be waiting for you. Come on.
Ms. Neha, come.
-Greetings, Ms. Neha.
Those three guys killed the constable.
-I heard the news.
I am waiting for you since morning.
I have summoned
the village chief and Mr. Kailash.
Please, come.
-Let's go.
Mr. Kailash.
Greetings.
-He is educated.
I told you about him, didn't I?
-Yes.
He is the chief.
Greetings.
-Greetings.
I help as much as possible.
But this village is in darkness.
There's darkness in this village.
You build the school...
...then children will get educated.
We are ready to support you.
-Yes.
Ms. Neha,
the trustees are in front of you.
(Chuckles)
This file contains all the details.
You read it and sign it.
Since when those three are doing crime?
-Who?
The one who murdered
the constable today.
From four to five months.
You tell me,
where do we have to sign?
Master, I am talking
about those three guys.
I wanted to ask you something.
What is the estimate of this project?
Two crores.
Two crores?
Two...
I am going to Patna
to meet the minister.
Until then you prepare the tender.
We've elected the contractor.
Paras... he is very honest,
respectable, and intelligent contractor.
You are Hariya's mother, right?
What was his enmity with the constable?
No sir, I don't know anything.
-You don't know.
Your child commits a murder
and you don't know anything.
You are Gorak's father, right?
-Yes.
What was his enmity with him?
No one will speak up.
You scoundrels.
You?
Everyone has joined hands in it.
You have begot a goon in the village?
Will you scare us?
Good night, madam.
Good evening.
I am Neha Malini from NGO.
I am Bansi.
I take care of the police station.
I have to the school
for school building.
Oh.
Please come.
(Clears throat)
Sir, is the tea ready?
Salute madam.
-Greetings, madam.
Get tea for her.
I'll get it right away.
-Give it to her.
Sir, I've washed it.
-Then go and dry it.
Yes.
Get it... Keep it.
-Here, madam.
Madam, have it.
I heard you met those
three guys on the way.
Yes, they dropped me till the school.
People who are sitting outside
are their parents.
Mother, father of criminals.
Nonsense people.
Hey, tell madam how many
murderers they've committed.
Four...
-Four.
Today was the fifth.
He was our constable. They
killed him by drowning him in a well.
You were there.
This area is such.
It is not life...
everyone is living in fear.
Madam, what do you do?
-I opened a NGO.
And this... family?
Father is a scientist
and my mother is a professor.
And I... Madam, I am...
Inspector Balkishan.
But sir, for how long will these
three guys keep murdering people?
You have to arrest them.
I have to do... but how? What?
You tell me...
...the entire police department
will help you building the school...
Department, will you help her or not?
Sir, we'll help her...
-Madam, we'll help you whenever you want.
I shall leave now. I need to go to Patna.
-Okay, madam.
Hey, salute madam.
-Greetings, madam.
Please come...
You go peacefully and return.
Look, I'm investigating them.
Be seated, I'll be back.
We'll surely nab those guys.
You go peacefully and until you return,
I'll finish my enquiry.
Okay... I shall leave.
-Please, sit.
(Bird chirping)
(Door closed sound)
(Engine start)
I think, Paras has done some setting
with the village chief.
But boss, it is your right.
The fund is of 2 crores.
Is Paras capable enough to do this work?
Yes, he is.
That's the reason the village
chief didn't call me.
Boss, what do we do?
(Scoffs)
What do we do?
There's only one solution.
Those three little guys.
Find those three little guys.
Talk to them.
They are looking for Ranjan's address.
Give them Ranjan's address
and Rs. 2000.
Tell them to kill Paras today.
Boss, isn't here any other solution?
Do you have any other solution?
Tell me... he's talking too much.
"Boss, isn't here any other solution?"
Lakhan used to join hands...
...with the superiors and take
every contract in the village. -Yes.
I joined hands with the school
people and took the contract.
I bribed the trustees saying,
I'll give them a house.
(Gunshot)
(Groans)
-Hey...
Lallan?
What happened to you? What?
What happened to you, Lallan?
Hey, who shot him?
Hey! Hey! Who is it?
Who is it? Hey!
Hey, who's firing? Hey...
Hey! Hey!
Come out!
(Gunshot)
-(Groans)
Greetings. Wow...
all the trustees are present here.
I heard that those
three guys killed Paras.
Those three guys are very mischievous,
dangerous, and crazy guys.
Look, you gave the contract
of the school to Paras.
Three guys killed him.
This village cannot progress without me.
The responsibility of building
a school is on me.
(Chuckles)
Headmaster, give me the map of
your house. Give me.
I'll make a good one.
Give me. Give me.
(Scoffs)
You also give it to me.
You show me yours.
You don't have one?
Give it to me.
Uncle, don't you have one?
Have faith. I'll make a good one.
-I know.
I'll give you a good one.
Let's go.
-Let's go, boss.
(Sighs)
(Horn blares)
(Indistinct chatter)
I've read that cold drinks
are unhealthy.
Everything is harmful
if you do it excess.
I do everything in excess.
Do you know when I am thirsty...
...I drink cold drink instead of water?
It is a very bad habit.
I need an approval for
the school building.
I have given you the approval.
Look at this.
Look at this. The file is ready.
Thank you, sir.
Shall I tell you the truth?
I failed in eighth grade.
But by Lord's blessings,
I am the education minister.
But I have something lacking.
A lacking that keeps pinching me within.
Do you know what it is?
I am an illiterate.
I am uneducated... but I wish that...
...the children of our state should study
well and become IAS and IPS officers.
They should serve the society
like you are doing. Am I right?
Look, you've already
taken a step towards it.
Master, I've bought chocolates.
Distribute it to the children.
-Give him.
Headmaster, they were writing on
the wall with a charcoal.
I caught them red-handed
and brought them here.
Okay, you go... I will handle them.
You come here. Come here.
What were you doing, idiots?
What were you doing?
Will you write with charcoal on the wall?
You've become mischievous.
(Wailing)
-Will you write with charcoal on the wall?
Will you do so much mischief?
Fools, will you do it again? -Master...
It is wrong to punish
children like this.
Ms. Neha, you tell me... he was
writing on the wall with charcoal.
Is it a good thing to write on the walls
with charcoal?
No, you tell me.
Ms. Neha, these two guys should be
rusticated from the school. -Why?
Ms. Neha, those three criminals...
...he is Avdesh's brother
and he is Gorak's brother.
Do you want them to become criminals like
them after being rusticated from school?
Master, minister has given approval
for the school building.
This is good news. Wow.
We'll do the paperwork with
the contractor that you've approved.
I'll call Lakhan today.
Lakhan?
But last time you said it was Paras.
Paras was murdered.
-Murdered?
Yes, those three guys killed him.
Their brothers.
What is your name?
Mahesh.
-Manikant.
Do they three meet you?
They meet us sometimes.
They are going to Patna today.
Why Patna?
-To look for Poonam.
Who is Poonam?
-Avdesh's bride.
(Emotional music)
Are you Avdesh's mother?
Greetings. My name is Neha.
I want to talk to you about Avdesh.
You know that police is
looking for them, don't you?
If they nab them,
they'll thrash them brutally.
They'll send them to jail forever.
I've heard lot of threats till now.
Your threats make no difference
to my son.
(Bird chirping)
Believe me,
I'm not here to threaten you.
I want to save those children.
If possible,
I want to give them a good life.
Don't you wish your son to get
educated and become a good man?
(Bird chirping)
Sit here.
(Indistinct chatter)
(Bird chirping)
Five months ago, Avdesh ran away
from home after fighting with me.
He never returned home.
Mahesh told me that
he meets him sometimes.
We didn't beget nasty children.
They have become goons.
(Sniffles)
Everything was alright.
It was during Avdesh's wedding.
"In tender age, she got married."
"I was innocent and beloved was naive."
"What trouble I've landed into?
He doesn't understand anything."
"Beloved is very mischievous,
what do I do?"
what do I do? What do I do?"
"I'm 12 years old and I got married."
"Beloved, I'm 12 years
old and I got married."
"Beloved."
"Beloved went ahead me.
What do I do?"
"Beloved is very mischievous.
What do I do? What do I do?"
"When I was 15 years old,
they bid farewell to me."
"Beloved, when I was 15 years old,
"Beloved."
"Beloved calls out for his mother.
What do I do?"
What do I do?" -Let's go.
"Beloved is very mischievous.
What do I do?" -Come on, hurry up.
What do I do?" -Hey, come on. Come on!
"What do I do?"
-Come on!
Take this.
It is more than Rs. 10,000.
Give back Poonam.
(Spitting)
You delayed.
We sold Poonam and took the money.
What are you watching?
We've already sold her.
You can't do anything now.
-How could you sell her!
How could you sell her!
How dare you!
-You argue with me!
(Wailing)
Your father has taken loan from us.
Tell him to repay
the loan at the earliest.
If not, we'll sell you too.
(Spitting)
Rama Shankar is strange man.
He has to pay loan and...
...he fixed his daughter's marriage
with our son.
This means, can he abduct Poonam?
Will he sell her anywhere?
Even you have to repay him loan.
Do you know,
Raghuveer is eyeing your son now?
Yes, these days, Raghuveer's men
are roaming near our crops. -Yes.
After we harvest lentil crops,
we'll sow potatoes.
There's lot of advantage in potatoes.
We'll repay the loan.
We'll repay the loan...
Eat food.
(Horse neighing)
Hey, get it down... careful.
(Indistinct chatter)
(Cycle bell ringing)
Raghuveer has sent me to you.
He has asked me to get the money.
The lentil crops are going
to be harvested.
Give us one more month's time.
Your boy keeps roaming here and there.
Shall I talk about him?
He will get a job.
He'll get Rs. 10,000.
He'll get Rs. 500 monthly as tips.
Raghuveer sold his fiancée.
Now he is eyeing on him.
Then I'll take your cattle.
If you take cattle,
how will we live?
Hey... Do anything you feel like.
You've made our life miserable.
The capital amount is Rs. 5000.
Interest money is Rs. 4000.
You have to pay Rs. 9000.
Tie the cattle...
I'll come with you tomorrow.
You'll get Rs. 10,000.
Mr. Raghuveer will wave off
your interest money.
Understood?
He'll give Rs. 5000 to your father.
(Chuckles)
I'm going with Dhooman today.
Where are you going?
I don't know. I have to
go if I have to save the cattle.
My parents will die
if the cattle are not here.
We both will die without you.
We will not let you go.
Let me go... who knows,
I may find Poonam there.
I may even get a chance to free her.
We'll find Poonam for you.
Let's go, we'll talk to Dhooman.
(Goat bleats)
Come, I've been waiting for you.
Hey Dhooman, go away...
Avdesh will not go with you.
You are talking too much?
You!
-Move... why did you hit him?
Hey, hit him...
-I am telling you.
How dare you!
-Why are you hitting me?
Wait...
-I'll teach you a lesson.
Get out!
-Hit him.
Get going!
-He'll teach you a lesson.
I'll not spare you.
He got saved or we would've
thrashed him to pulp. (Laughs)
Avdesh, Raghuveer and his men
are hitting your dad in the farm.
(Indistinct chatter)
Father!
-Uncle? Uncle?
Father...
-We'll not spare you, scoundrels!
Uncle!
-He killed my father.
Father! Father!
Scoundrels killed my father.
Contractor, how much is it?
It is Rs. 25,000.
We killed Manohar.
I've committed 2-3 murders for you.
I've abducted many children.
But I never told
your name to the police.
Contractor, it would've been nice
if you would give me more Rs. 25,000.
Contractor, don't feel bad...
...I am in need of money.
-Why will I feel bad?
Goodbye.
Boss, Raghuveer is becoming greedy.
Let he be greedy...
...he has been calculating things
these days.
Get those three guys to me.
You don't worry.
Boss is calling you. Come on.
(Barks)
Come on... don't get scared.
Come on.
(Sighs)
Bhola...
-Yes, boss?
Where will we find Raghuveer?
He is constructing his shop.
He has got Rs. 50,000.
So, he is doing it.
Come...
-Come, sit. Sit.
(Sighs)
Come...
-Yes.
Sit here.
Sit.
(Sighs)
Have you killed an ant?
You would've killed a rat too?
You would've killed a snake too.
Did you kill it or not? Then?
-Yes, we've killed it.
It is not difficult to kill
a human being.
Come here...
-Go... Boss is calling you. Go to him.
Come, come.
Come, sit here.
Killing a human is not a big deal.
You just need to have guts.
Bhola.
-Yes, boss?
Give the things to them.
Here.
You also take...
-Practice in the jungle.
You'll get Raghuveer in his shop.
If you are in need of money...
...then don't ask anyone.
Come to me.
Your father died...
...hereafter, I am your father.
We'll get your bride back.
Understood?
Go.
(Laughs)
Let's go.
(Singing)
(Gunshot)
(Barks)
Where's your son?
Have you hidden him inside?
He's not at home.
-He murdered.
Do you know that?
How about your husband?
How about your son?
You are alone.
What all will you endure?
If you need me...
...meet me... at my quarters.
"I spoke to my darling at night."
(Bike engine starts)
(Bike passing sound)
(Muslim prayer)
What all I am going through
because of you...
Why? Why did you kill him?
Tell me! Tell me!
I will thrash you. Tell me!
Will you tell me or not?
Why did you kill him? -Mother? Mother?
You've made my life miserable.
Why did you...?
He killed my father...
so I killed him.
I am going... I am leaving the house.
I'll never return.
Avdesh! Avdesh!
Avdesh!
Where are they three?
They are going to Patna.
To look for Poonam.
There's somebody named
Ranjan in Ameethapur.
Mahesh told me.
Lakhan is a big criminal.
He made three innocent children
as criminal.
He is using them.
You gave him the contract.
Neha dear,
you are doing a good deed.
We want that good deed
to get completed.
What do we have to do
with Lakhan's past?
He is working... we just need
the work to be done. That's it.
Mr. Kailash,
touch your heart and tell me...
...is it okay if a hooligan
does this good deed?
Ms. Neha...
...talk softly, somebody may hear you.
Hiralal says that
Lakhan is a bad man.
We shouldn't take risk
by talking against him.
We'll all do the work...
what's wrong in it?
A criminal can't build
a school building.
Criminal?
He's not a criminal, but a shrew.
He hasn't started working on
my house yet.
Your house?
I'm going to Patna.
Tell Lakhan to stay away from this job.
I'll return and talk to you.
-No.
Goodbye...
-Listen...
(Sighs)
Hit him!
-It slipped out of my mouth.
You should've kept your mouth shut!
How could you...
Shut up!
-He ruined our plans.
Oh no.
Open... open the window.
Cool breeze.
-It is cool breeze.
Increase the speed.
Yes, increase the speed.
Water...
Play a song...
-Come on, play it.
"Which place is this?
It is a four feet wall."
"O sir, we got sold cheaper
than the cattle."
"Which place is this?
It is a four feet wall."
"O sir, we got sold cheaper
than the cattle."
"O sir, our tears are
flowing non-stop."
Children aged 12-13 years
have become criminals.
They are committing murders.
Child trafficking is also
a big problem in that village.
Boys are sold and bought for
Rs. 5000 to Rs. 10,000.
There's someone named Ranjan in
Ameethapur here... he's behind everything.
Find him out.
-Ameethapur? That's a red-light area.
We can put NGO pressure
on Ameethapur police station...
...we can take their help.
Hey, does Ranjan stay here?
Yes, upstairs. Go.
-Okay.
Here... see if it contains
Poonam's photo in it.
Is she Poonam?
You'll get her tomorrow morning.
You've come from far.
You must be tired. So, take rest.
I will send food for you all.
I respect Mr. Lakhan very much.
You are fortunate that
you got Poonam so easily.
I'll be back.
You don't go anywhere.
Stay here.
(Door closed sounds)
(Door locked)
(Laughs)
Uncle, I've locked those
three guys in the room.
Take care of them.
-Who are they three?
They are birds.
They came flying to me.
Take care.
(Police siren)
We were looking for an opportunity.
There's something wrong going on
in this mansion.
Ranjan was on
our radar from long time.
Your NGO has given us
this opportunity...
...by putting pressure on
our Department.
Shall we?
-Yes.
"Your silky tresses."
Hey, you didn't find anyone?
-Why are you standing here?
Go away...
-Come on.
Police! Police! Flee!
Do you know Ranjan?
Do you know him?
Where is Ranjan?
-I don't know.
Hey, who is Ranjan? Where is he?
-He's there.
Ranjan!
Who is it? -I am your father!
Scoundrel, open the door!
Open the door! Open it!
-(Door knocking)
Are you Ranjan!
-No.
Tell me...
Sir, there are children here.
"You hurt me so much that
my dreams shattered."
"Oh sir, no one should be born as girl."
Where is Poonam?
Speak up!
Who is Poonam amongst you?
From Birwa village.
It is her.
"The house is on the river bank
of Ganges in the east."
"Oh sir, I am three miles away
from the home now."
(Police siren)
You go and look there.
-Okay, sir.
Let's go.
Who is inside? Hey!
Is anyone inside?
Hey, open the door.
-(Door knocking)
Where's Ranjan's house?
-Sir, this is the one.
Constable!
-Yes, sir?
Get something to break the lock.
-Okay.
(Door knocking)
Avdesh, are you alright?
Sir, take this.
-Yes.
(Door knocking)
Hey, move back...
-Move back.
Avdesh...
-Move back...
Avdesh, listen to me.
Move back...
Hey.
-Run!
Avdesh!
-Constable, nab him!
Hey, surround them!
-I'm telling you to stop! Stop!
Hari!
-Run!
Stop!
Hey, stop!
They escaped in the dark.
It is hard to find them.
I know them.
Thank you, Ms. Neha.
Because of your information, we've
caught hold of human trafficking gang.
We have sent all the children
to child refuge.
You got your Poonam back.
You please have a seat. Sit.
By the way,
where are those guys from?
There's a village named Birwa near
Betiya, they belong to that place.
Ranjan has revealed everything.
A man named Lakhan...
...he is the chief of child abduction.
Lakhan is a hardcore criminal.
He makes criminals.
He is involved in child trafficking too.
No one is doing anything against him.
Lakhan should be removed from this job...
...and this contract should be
handed over to someone else.
Ms. Neha, do we need Vibhishan
to win over Lanka or not? Tell me.
Lakhan is a bad man.
He'll have work...
...then everything will go on smoothly.
Your school will get
completed on time, right?
Look, you must be mistaken.
I know Lakhan personally.
He's a nice man.
(Chuckles)
I'm seeing love in your eyes
since the first day.
What?
-For the village.
I am seeing love in your eyes...
...for the children of the village.
Shall I suggest you something?
Why don't you join politics?
I give you the guarantee of
getting a ticket.
When a beautiful girl like you will
stand on the stage for a speech...
then we need not toil to get the crowd...
-I am not interested in joining politics.
I will expose Lakhan.
But I think, many more people
will be exposed with Lakhan.
Ms. Neha, you got angry.
You want to remove Lakhan, right?
Yes.
-Okay, I'll remove him.
Give me... where do I have to sign?
Give it to me.
(Crickets creaking)
Hey, get it. Hurry up.
-Yes, I'll get it.
"By cleaning the house and courtyard...
...and after washing the dishes...
...I became like the branch of
the tree, Oh sir."
"By cleaning the house and courtyard
and after washing the dishes...
...I became like the branch of
the tree, Oh sir." -Poonam?
"You took the money
and chopped me off."
"Oh sir, you made a
daughter as an animal."
"Oh sir, you made a daughter
as an animal."
"Oh sir, my tears are flowing non-stop."
-Madam...
What are you watching?
Go and inform her parents.
Go and inform her parents, son.
Your parents will be so happy.
My child is back...
May god bless you.
"It is a four feet wall."
"Oh sir, I got sold cheaper
than the cattle."
"Which place is this?
It is a four feet wall."
"Oh sir, I got sold cheaper
than the cattle."
(Indistinct chatter)
Hey, give it to me...
come on, throw it down.
Hey, careful...
-Give it to me.
Take this... Take this.
Bhola...
-Yes, sir?
I heard, you get such
goggles in the city...
...in which you can see
under the clothes.
Boss, you are right.
Even I heard that.
Madam, please come. Look, the
construction of the school has begun.
Lakhan, what is this?
These are bricks.
I am not talking about bricks.
I'm talking about children.
Yes, they are children.
I think you don't know that
making children work...
...who are under 18 years, is a crime.
Is it?
Give it to me...
-What is this?
Children, stop it. Come down.
-Hey...
Stop it...
-Come down.
Get down.
-Let's go.
Go...
-Go to your house.
You go now. Come after you
have crossed 18 years.
He's doing crime.
-Yes.
Take this.
-What is this?
It is minister's letter.
You've been removed
from this contract.
What?
Your work is done.
Enough, you may leave now.
(Engine starts)
Ms. Neha, what have you done?
You sacked Lakhan.
I didn't sack Lakhan,
but Mr. Baldev did.
Baldev is incarnation of God here.
Lakhan is the owner.
We are just pawns.
Even we'll resign from the trust.
If we are alive, we'll built a house.
Ms. Neha, you look for another
village to build your school.
Go away. Immediately.
You don't worry.
My NGO will handle the trust.
She is very adamant.
Let's go to Mr. Lakhan.
-Come.
Before he avenges us...
-Let's go.
We can't trust him.
He can do anything.
Everyone is here?
Brother Lakhan...
Brother Lakhan, forgive us.
-What's the matter?
Leave my legs.
-No, until you don't forgive us...
...we will not leave your legs.
Okay, I forgive you.
He forgave us.
-My three lions are here.
You get up and go home.
Look, I will build the school.
You just support me.
Goodbye... Go, go.
-Goodbye.
Thank you.
-Go, please go.
Come here, my lion. Come on!
Come on, well done! Come, come.
I heard that...
...school teacher followed you to Patna.
To nab you.
She has sworn to get you caught.
She's your enemy.
If she gets us caught, she'll die.
She has to die.
You three are lions.
She is after you.
(Laughs)
Don't waste time.
Shoot her on sight.
Before she gets to your neck, kill her.
Go... very good. Go.
The trust has become fund.
I'll meet the minister
after the teacher dies.
I will take back the school contract.
Understood?
I don't give money simply
for minister's elections.
Contract is of no use
if there's no murders.
An animal costs more than
a child in our village.
Sir, 15 children have been sold
from our village.
All this is because of
Raghuveer and Lakhan.
We had taken some loan
from Raghuveer.
He snatched our cattle
and land in return.
He killed my husband too.
I will see.
Avdesh, what are you doing?
Are you supporting Lakhan?
The same Lakhan who killed your father?
This girl, she saved your Poonam.
Will you shoot her?
Come on... kill me... Kill her!
Come on, kill her! Kill me.
Kill everyone in the village.
Come on, shoot.
What are you watching! Come on!
Avdesh, Lakhan is using you.
Surrender yourself to the police.
Nothing will happen to you,
I'll be with you... -Stay back.
If the teacher wasn't there...
...Poonam wouldn't have returned.
Scoundrel Lakhan is manipulating us.
He killed my father,
now he's become my father.
Lakhan must be bad man of this area.
We have killed an ant.
We've killed a rat.
We have killed a snake.
We have killed human too.
Now we'll kill Lakhan.
-How will we kill him?
He comes to the furnace every morning.
Find out whose place is this.
I have to buy it. Understood?
-Okay, boss.
There'll be a highway here...
railway track here.
The value will increase.
(Gunshot)
Did you hear a gunshot?
-There, boss.
Boss, where are you?
-Hey!
Why is he shouting so much?
-Boss!
Boss, where are you?
Boss!
-What's the matter? Who shot?
Those three guys.
Boss, those three guys killed Ravi.
Run, boss!
-Hey, start the car!
Hey, start the car!
-We'll not spare him.
Hey, stop! Stop!
-(Gunshot)
Come on, move, move!
(Gunshot)
Stop! Where are you running? Stop!
Scoundrel!
Balkishan!
-Why did this idiot come here?
Hey Balkishan!
-Oh.
Why are you panting so much?
(Panting)
What's the matter?
-(Panting)
Why are you so tensed?
I got saved. (Panting)
Balkishan, I got saved.
He shot at me.
-You? Who shot at you?
Those... (Panting)
those three guys fired bullet at me.
Those guys fired bullet at you?
-Yes. (Panting)
They were my servants,
but they betrayed me.
Now I have to escape from them
in my own village.
I have to fear them.
Balkishan, do something.
Kill them.
-No, I can't.
SP has ordered us to arrest them.
Is SP superior than me?
Brother, SP is superior.
-Balkishan!
I mean, even you are superior.
Now... this police job is such.
I will find a way.
-No, no.
You don't find a way.
I will find a way myself.
That teacher is acting very smart.
Now I will act smart.
You just sit and watch. Understood?
You'll just watch.
-Okay.
Hey... have something cold at least.
Oh no!
(Bird chirping)
Did you admit Ravi in the hospital?
Boss, Ravi died.
(Grunts)
This is that teacher's doing.
All this happened because of her.
Bhola...
-Yes, boss?
Bhola!
Find her...
find her and get her here.
I will show her who I am.
Until you don't get her, I'll sit here.
I will not move from here. Get her!
-Let's go.
I will not spare that teacher.
"Touch the gem of education
with knowledge."
"Make our lives worth living."
Move...
-Hey, move!
Hey, what are you doing?
-Come on!
Leave me! Leave me!
-Hey, move back children!
What are you doing?
-Hey, come on!
Move back! Come on!
-Come on!
Hey Lallan, you get teacher's car.
-Leave me!
Hey...
Where are you taking me?
-Hey!
(Screaming)
Hold her tightly.
Shut up...
-Sit quietly.
Shut up, don't make any noise.
You are acting very smart.
-Shut up!
Will you mess with us?
Just sit quietly.
Hold her tightly.
-Hey, hold her.
Don't make any noise.
Greetings... teacher.
-Come on, get down.
Get her here.
-Come on, move.
Hey, come on.
-Boss, here's the teacher.
(Stretching)
Oh city girl...
have you heard that old proverb?
You shouldn't lock horns with
someone living in the same area.
You've come to our area
and sacked me from the job.
Those three guys...
who used to listen to me blindly...
...you turned them against me.
You made them attack me?
Police may be working
for the public in your city.
The law may be working for the public.
But here...
...police works to protect me...
...and law also works to protect me.
Understood?
Look, no matter
what I do with you here...
...neither law nor the police
will harm me.
I will harm you.
(Slaps)
This is the punishment
for sacking me from the job.
(Slaps)
(Laughs)
This is the punishment for manipulating
those three guys against me.
(Slaps)
This is the punishment for getting
those three guys attack me.
But the real punishment begins now.
Bhola...
-Yes, boss?
Remove her clothes.
-Okay, boss.
Let me see, how salty this city girl is.
-Leave me.
Come on, remove it.
-Look, don't do anything with me.
It will be bad...
-What bad?
Tell us.
-Hey, come on.
Bhola... -Yes, boss?
-Yes, boss?
Will you undress her
when she falls unconscious?
Hey, remove it!
-Okay, boss.
I want to see.
Boss... hey!
No!
-We'll not spare you today.
(Screaming)
She is not letting us undress her.
-Hey!
No!
Pull it...
-Hey...
(Panting)
Hey...
-Tell your men to drop their guns.
(Panting)
Hey, throw the guns.
Come this side, all of you.
Come on, even you too.
-Hey, come on.
Contractor, come out with us.
You scoundrel.
What are you watching? Come on.
Teacher, you leave.
Hey, no one will come forward.
Move back. -Move back.
Move back...
-Move back.
Come on, you both go and sit.
Come on.
Hands up...
-Move back.
Move back... You both sit inside,
hurry up, come on.
Hands up... Come on.
Scoundrel! Idiot!
-He just slipped out of our hands.
Wear this.
Thank you.
Why thank us. It is your jacket,
we're returning it to you.
You are looking good wearing the jacket.
You are really looking very pretty.
Really?
Okay, we shall leave.
What happened?
Will you leave me alone and go?
Further is our area.
No one goes there other than us.
I will come along with you.
-Okay, let's go.
We are having fun sitting in your car.
Do this... drive faster.
It will be fun.
-Really?
The road is nice ahead.
-Okay, let's go.
"We are joyful and carefree."
"We are lost travelers."
"We endured atrocities
and committed crime, Oh sir."
"We are joyful and carefree."
"We are lost travelers."
"We endured atrocities
and committed crime, Oh sir."
"We don't know what's right
and what's wrong."
"We don't know where to go."
"We are the king of this place, Oh sir."
(Clears throat)
Okay, we've reached our area.
You go... go.
I am not going anywhere.
I'll stay with you...
...in your area.
Will you do me a favor?
-What?
Give me a gun.
(Laughs)
Why are you laughing?
It is not easy to fire the pistol.
(Laughs)
How do you fire?
-I'll tell you.
(Gunshot)
Did you see?
This is how a pistol is fired.
If we press the trigger...
...the bullet goes inside and
the brain comes out. -Brain comes out.
Even I want to learn.
Then we all will kill Lakhan.
You are a woman, be under your limits.
-Yes.
Is it?
Tell me a work that woman can't do?
(Laughs)
Let's go... Let's go.
Women can't do this.
(Laughs)
You all are great.
Run!
-Hey!
Stop!
"This life is a boat.
There's no rower."
"We are getting stuck."
"We are running
a race against wind, Oh sir."
"This life is a boat.
There's no rower."
"We are getting stuck."
"We are running
a race against wind, Oh sir."
"Who do I complaint to?
All the relationships broke."
"We are the punishment of
this birth, Oh sir."
You are a nice girl.
If you were young,
I would've married you.
Is it?
(Laughs)
You can marry me even now.
What say? Will you marry her?
Gorak will marry when
he turns 21, right?
I am just 13 years old, but married.
(Laughs)
Avdesh, your marriage is wrong.
Guy should be 21 and girl
should be 18 for marriage.
(Laughs)
You all are very nice.
Why did you go in the wrong path?
What wrong we did?
You murder people and ask
me what wrong you did?
Who did we kill? Who?
Raghuveer thrashed
my father to death. He?
Mahadev...
...being a police inspector, he used to
tease the women of our village. He?
Paras wanted to swindle
your school money.
He? Did we do wrong by killing him?
We will kill Lakhan now.
He is everyone's leader.
Tell me, what wrong do we do?
What you do is the work of the law.
Violence is wrong.
Few goons came to the school
and abducted Neha.
In front of everyone.
I think it is the doing of
those three guys. -Yes.
They would've kidnapped Ms. Neha.
Inspector, do something.
-Yes, inspector.
The entire day has come to an end,
but Ms. Neha has not returned.
Neha's car is parked near the ruins.
But Ms. Neha is not in it.
-Yes.
They are children...
...but remember that
they can do anything with Neha.
They dwell in the ruins.
-Yes.
You don't worry... Look...
...I've called for special force
from Betiya.
To nab those three guys. Had
you not come, we would've gone there.
Hey...
-Yes, sir?
Let's go.
-Okay, sir.
Hey, hurry up.
You don't worry.
Everything will be alright.
Police is here.
Did you have fun?
You are very nice.
What is this?
You abducted Neha in my presence.
All the villagers know that Lakhan
kidnapped me and brought me to this state.
But you don't know...
these children saved my life.
Okay... these villagers spread rumors.
But madam, we have to take them.
Shall we?
Go...
Come on...
-I'll follow you.
Come on, you scoundrels.
You've made my life miserable.
We didn't take
so much time to nab a dacoit...
...the time we took to look for you.
Senior officers have made
our lives miserable.
You were playing hide and seek with us.
-Let's go.
Let's go...
-You were playing peek-a-boo with us.
We'll show you in the police station what
punishment you get for carrying a pistol.
Come on, sit inside...
or I'll thrash you.
Sit inside. Come on.
-Yes.
Come on, drive.
Come on, come on. Sit there!
You made us run after you so much.
You killed Mahadev.
What do you think of yourself?
How dare you stare at me?
Hey, why are you hitting him?
I am not hitting him.
Tell her... I was just...
why will I hit them?
Look, Lakhan did whatever
he wanted to do with me.
These three children are with you.
They'll tell you. Ask them...
...who gave pistol in their hands
and told them to murder?
Then I'll see how Lakhan
escapes from the law.
How long will he escape?
-I'll write a FIR.
I will make a dairy,
then I'll see how Mr. Lakhan...
How long can Lakhan escape?
He has ruined the peace of the village.
His future generations
will directly go to jail.
His hooliganism is too much.
Ms. Neha, I am with you.
I am with you.
Hello sir...
Ms. Neha...
-Yes.
Yes... three guys are
in the police custody.
I want to meet you.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Who are you calling?
Dm.
He has called me.
He wants you to enquire
the children by tonight.
We'll have to take them to the juvenile
home tomorrow morning.
(Laughs)
Ms. Neha, you are great.
You called the DM directly.
I had known that you are influential.
Does anyone come to this jungle
from so far to build a school?
You will put an end to Lakhan's chaos.
Look, I have to go.
But I'll return tomorrow morning.
I will take you three along with me.
Okay?
-Okay.
Take care of yourself.
Dm...
Didn't I tell you that one day
they'll find the right path?
Look, they are in front of you.
Ms. Neha, you did the right thing
by getting those three arrested.
I've told SP,
Lakhan will be arrested tonight.
SP was apologizing for whatever
Lakhan and his men did with you.
Now you go and relax.
(Keyboard clacking)
(Sighs)
(Phone ringing)
Hello?
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Yes, sir. Goodbye, sir.
Mishra...
Yes, sir?
-Get the jeep.
SP had called.
We have to shift them to Betiya.
Okay, sir.
-Go.
You don't worry.
Everything will be alright now.
SP had called.
We have to take them to Betiya,
to Ms. Neha.
Wake him up. Wake up...
-Hey, Gorak.
Hari, Gorak...
-Hey, wake up.
Ms. Neha has called.
-Come on.
You take rest.
You've been up all night.
You don't worry. We are here.
Come on. Let's go.
Will you sit here? Go home,
we'll talk tomorrow. Didn't you hear me?
(Yawning)
Get down... go and freshen up.
Come on.
(Gunshot)
-(Groans)
Mishra, make a case of encounter.
-Okay, sir.
They were running
after firing a bullet at you.
(Gunshot)
-(Groans)
Hello?
Sir, the work is done.
(Yawning)
Boss, police killed those three guys.
Their bodies are at the well.
(Laughs)
I was on phone all night.
Until I don't see their dead bodies...
...I won't get peace.
Let's go.
She is here.
-(Car door closes)
Did you see the consequences
of doing hooliganism?
(Spitting)
If you pick up a pistol,
you'll die from one.
So, don't do crime.
Live respectable life, understood?
Yes, sir.
"They didn't grow up,
but had pistols in their hands."
"They left the house
and wandered in the jungle."
"Get back the childhood, Oh sir."
"Oh sir, put us to sleep
in mother's drape."
"Oh sir, sing us a lullaby."
"Oh sir, please don't leave us."
"Oh sir, take us to the stars."
"Oh sir, make us float
in the river Ganges."
(Laughs)
They died.
They were after my life.
Look now, they three are
lying dead on the ground.
(Laughs)
I am the God here.
One who worships me, will live.
The one who messes with me will meet
the same fate as these three guys.
Did everyone understand?
They messed with Lakhan.
They shout at Lakhan?
Will you attack Lakhan! You!
(Laughs)
Hey, put it down... put it down.
Hey, put it down.
Hey, stop them.
Hey, where are they running?
(Gunshot)
-(Groans)
(Neha)'A big demon of this small place
is lying dead on the ground.'
'I have pistol in my hands.'
'But I am happy that life of two kids
got saved because of me.'
'Even you would've seen
such a kid around you...
...who is being abused in some
or other way.'
'If you support any such kid...
...I'll think that my hard work
was successful.'
'My fight will continue even
after getting released from jail.'
"Touch the gem of education
with knowledge."
"Make our lives worth living."
"Make our lives worth living...
...by giving education."
"Touch the gem of education
with knowledge."
"Make our lives worth living."
"Make our lives worth living...
...by giving education."
"Touch the gem of education
with knowledge."
"Make our lives worth living."
"Make our lives worth living...
...by giving education."
"Touch the gem of education
with knowledge."
"Adorn your life in such a way...
...that you make it like
a sun in the sky."
"Don't get distracted from your karma."
"Touch the gem of education
with knowledge."
"Make our lives worth living."
"Touch the darkness of illiteracy."
"There's a new star
in the sky every night."
"Drive away the darkness
with brightness of education."
"No matter where you go,
there'll be a new morning."
"You repay the debt of
the earth with pride."
"You repay the debt of the earth..."