Ratanlal Bagula.
Sub-inspector.
You're in our custody today.
We're going to question you..
...until you don't
give us answers.
Who was she?
How did you know her?
You don't know that“
...you're a police
officer yourself?
Tell us...
...how it happened?
Who paid you to do this job?
How were you connected
to that girl?
Sir, this is Satyakam.
Shyam Dada.
JB sir.
How were you connected?
Sir.
Bagula.
I am the head of
this investigation.
Arun Roy.
And my study is..
...you'll be rotting
behind bars for a long time.
Be sure.
I can help you.
H you...
...help me.
Look...
Bagula, I know that the..
...person who shook up
the law and country is a girl.
Her name isn't Sigdi.
Her real name is Kaanchi.
I can see confirmation
in your eyes.
Right?
We will catch her, soon.
Be sure of that.
Soon she will be behind bars.
And maybe...she'll face
rigorous punishment.
What difference
does it make, sir?
It won't make a difference
to her if you hang her.
She will just smile.
She's a b***h.
Forget it, sir.
Look...
I want to know everything.
I want to know the real story.
A petite girl like her
can't do such a big job.
It's impossible.
What's the truth
behind these facts?
How are you
related to Kaanchi?
We're friends.
Since we were kids.
We studied in the same
village, the same school.
She was junior to me.
Seven years ago
I came to Mumbai.
And she grew up there...
in that village.
Koshampa.
A village for retired
army soldiers in Uttrakhand.
She was the star
of that place.
Kaanchi.
Kaanchi!
How did they get in Kakda
Land without permission?
"The scorching heat,
cooling shade."
"Entire village against
one small girl."
"Wouldn't you want
to know her name?"
"Kaanchi."
"Scorching heat,
cooling shade."
"Entire village versus
one small girl."
"Wouldn't you want
to know her name?"
"Kaanchi."
"You're fragile like glass."
"She's like fire."
"She's a girl
from my country."
"Let the world
know...hello, hi."
"She displays all
the seven colors."
"The entire world's
assessed from her heart."
"Kaanchi."
Kaanchi!
You played foul.
Get lost.
Why you..
"Kaanchi."
We've to turn this
Koshampa valley..
“Into JB Koshampa
city in a year.
World class valley.
And anyone who
causes obstructions“
...will be responsible
for his position and life.
Don't you know
who you slapped?
Yes, I know.
He's that scoundrel
inspector Bhagwafis son.
You hurled the trophy
which the MLA presented you.
You're no princess.
What else did you expect?
I was holding the trophy in my hands..
...so that's what
I hurled at him.
You're still arguing with me.
You're a girl still
you abuse people.
What do you expect?
Did you want me to
bow before that rascal?
- Be quiet.
- Don't beat her.
Get her married. Her
in-laws will do the beating.
Get going-
Nirman Singh,
will Kaanchi ever change.
N eve r.
What?
That Deepu
complained to mother?
Yes. To mother.
And he even cried before her.
Kaanchi. Where are you going?
Please spare some change.
Hold it!
Hi-five..
Did you complain to my mother?
Yes, I did. So?
Why you..
Now go complain to her again“
“that I slapped you again.
And this is in advance..
...for the next time
you complain to her.
- You'll get it tomorrow.
- That's okay.
Hail Goddess!
She slapped my son,
now watch“
...how I sc***
her and her family.
Mind your tongue.
Okay, here. See.
You will all have
to mind your tongues.
When Kakda family
comes to Koshampa..
“And exterminates all of you.
Binda has given
Kaanchi an apt name.
'Sigdi' (furnace).
Kaanchi's the brave
daughter of my brave son.
If you mess with her,
she will roar back.
So do you women want
to burn everything down?
Your father...
died in the Kashmir war.
He left us few pieces of land.
Now Khajra, Bhagwat will
trouble us to sell the lands.
We were born in Koshampa..
“And we'll die here.
Your Binda has gone crazy..
...by doing rounds
of the court.
And you..
If you keep picking fights
with government officials“
“won't they make
our life difficult.
Even if we all join hands..
...we still can't
face this storm
Mother,
who are you talking to?
You.
Mother, you're singing
in the wrong tune.
And the words are wrong too.
Mother...
It's been 19 years since..
“I've been hearing
this wrong lullaby.
The words can be wrong,
but the meaning is right.
Can I say something?
If I say sorry
will you forgive me?
Sorry, mother.
Don't cry.
She's crying.
Fine, go on cry.
Wretch“
Only one man
can set you right.
Your Binda.
Let him set himself
right first.
Who does he think he is?
Is he back from
the city or not?
No. He never tells me.
One, two, three, four, five..
One, two, three“
Come on, come on.
Faster. Faster.
Faster.
Yes, sir!
Five, six...
Faster. Faster.
Come on, come on.
Come on
30..
29..
Come on, come on.
28...Z7...Z6...
Come on. Go back to training.
Come on.
Z4.
Your hands are amazing.
Kamla, you haven't
seen my magic yet.
Come on, I'll show you magic.
- Hey..
- Quiet.
She falls down intentionally.
Don't I know?
So that Binda
picks her up and..
...touches her under the
pretext of applying balm.
If you feel jealous then
don't come to my compound?
Learn if you want to,
or else leave.
Fine, I won't come.
Don't try to boss me, wretch.
What did you say?
Scoundrel“
Get going all of you.
No anger.
No anger at all.
Binda has to look
after all the students.
- That wretch“
- No abusing.
Girls don't abuse.
- You don't know that ***
- For my sake.
Fine.
He loves you.
I see. ls this love?
He applied ointment
on her back..
Quiet!
I am quiet.
He's returned tired
and worn out from the city..
“And is already training.
He's also brought gift
for you and your mother.
I don't want any gift.
He didn't even say sorry.
Scoundrel“
Get lost.
Papa, why are you
wasting time on her?
- Because I like her.
- I see.
Give me one reason.
She's untainted, honest.
And second,
she's my martyr friend“
“soldier Surat
Singh's daughter.
She still steps out
wearing his army belt.
With pride.
Is that the only reason?
Yes .
Papa...you're totally great.
Completely.
Have some shame?
- What's shameful in this?
- Return the towel.
First I want to know why
did you stay so long in the city?
I went to see a girl for myself.
Papa said so.
Did you find one?
Her name's Haseena.
Is she more beautiful than me?
Every other girl's
more beautiful than you.
- Lie.
- And one more thing.
I went to see a boy for you.
Your mother asked me to do so.
So did you find one?
You'll be really happy to see him.
Then do one thing.
Come like this to my house.
Hey! Kaanchi.
Kaanchi.
Hey naked, here's your towel.
Cover yourself.
Binda.
Yes, Pa Pa-
Son, are you okay?
Sorry, P3Pa-
I forgot to take the towel.
You forgot to take the towel.
Don't feel shy from me.
Here you go.
Tell me...what's your new plan?
See what I do tomorrow, papa.
I'll take a gorgeous
face along for her.
Let me introduce you.
This is Paddu Pahalwan.
Hailing from the village Surajmukhi.
Famous singer,
Basya Maharaj is his father.
And harlot Reshma Bai is his mother.
Paddu Pahalwan is
their youngest son.
Actually speaking
his name is Padam Singh.
I really like the boy.
Paddu.
We won't find a rich
boy like him again.
He's nice, sister.
Take him home once.
Can I say something?
I was looking for a
successful man like him.
I don't want a fair,
handsome looking mouse.
I am ready for the marriage.
Start preparing for the marriage.
Binda, you just lit the furnace.
Go inside and see the
consequences of your charade.
She's Kaanchi.
Glass may shatter, but not Kaanchi.
What do I do with this crazy girl?
You teased her,
now you convince her.
She couldn't take a small joke.
She troubles me all day long.
Kaanchi.
"Ev, Sigdi.
"The goat gazed on the grass."
"The girl got scared."
"Crossed the seven seas."
"And drove everyone insane."
Scared?
Yes .
What would you have
done ifl had died?
Followed you.
Why?
'89' YOUr point?
What?
Should I say it or do it?
Do it.
I almost forgot.
Papa gave me this, it was for you.
I told him to remind me.
I gave the t-shirts,
bags and everything else, but“
“but one should give
this beautiful bracelet“
...to the beautiful girl first.
Get lost. Rascal.
Next time you do
something like this..
...l'll hang you from a rope.
That fatty was right for you.
- You should marry..
- I'm looking for a fatty for you too.
Find me one.
I'll have real fun with a fatty.
This girl has no fear of death.
When it comes to
teach someone a lesson..
...her brain runs
faster than a computer.
One.
Two
Three.
Four.
Now keep stretched.
Everyone stand straight.
Come on.
Brother, Kakda's men
are here to buy our land.
- Good morning, Binda.
- Good morning.
Good morning.
You still have an eye.
I do, Binda.
There's 2 million, in this bag.
And Kakda sir has sent
it especially for you.
All you need to do is sign.
One sign, chapter close.
You don't get such an opportunity,
try to understand.
- Give it.
- Yes.
- Take a look.
- It's heavy.
Chandu, give it to papa.
O kaY-
Thank you, Khajura. Thank you.
Hold on.
Just one sign.
One sign.
Very good.
Very good. Very good.
What are you doing?
This is cheating.
What have you done?
The school needed money, Khajura.
Because I need money
to defend my case against you.
You don't get it, Binda.
This is cheating.
Your bosses are doing the cheating.
They bought the lands of
the soldiers by paying peanuts.
You won't get a sq.ft.
If you play games like this“
“then Kakda sir won't spare you.
Who is Kakda?
Why don't you bring
this weakling before me?
If Jhoomar Babu shakes
hands with Binda..
...his fingers will crack.
Do you want to see his strength?
I'll see his later.
First let's test yours.
Go, go to the court.
Let's see who is Jhoomar Babu Kakda.
Sorry, sir.
Bakula here.
Wrong timing but
right information, sir.
Sir, engineer Pandey
turned about to be a ratter.
Yes, sir.
He leaked all the information“
“about the Uttranchal
Project to Davar's CA.
For 100 million.
Yes, sir.
What did he say?
What else.
Kill him.
Koshampa Valley project is a scam.
Mr. Jhumar didn't hesitate“
...to seize the lands
of old retired soldiers.
Because he's supported
by politicians.
Beware of him.
Okay, sir.
Yes, I am Neeraj Pandey.
Jimmy.
It's your brother.
- Yes, brother.
- As your elder brother“
“I've tried telling
you many times“
...that every job should
be done with a system.
Try to understand.
Small mistakes lead to
the destruction of the rich.
I had a word with the
Chief Minister of that state.
We'll have to go to Koshampa once.
You will have Koshampa..
“But only through
political influence.
Through a system.
"Our dream.."
"What is it?"
"The dream of love."
"The rainbow of love."
"I see."
"Everyone's tricolor flag."
"Say it."
"Koshampa."
"Love, affection, Koshampa."
"Heaven on earth, Koshampa."
"Soft like cotton."
"Hot like tea."
"Love, affection, Koshampa."
"You're my heaven, Koshampa."
"It's in the mud houses."
"Dwelling in our hearts."
"On the slopes of the mountains."
"The drenched valleys
are softer than cotton."
"The bonds and ties
are warm like tea."
"Small house are blessed
with the grace of God."
"Love is the only religion here."
"Don't fight with your mother."
"Don't fight."
"Love, affection, Koshampa."
SOT TV, SOT TV, SOT TV-.
- ls he hurt?
- No, no.
I am very sorry. This is the
first time I'm driving in a valley.
Sorry, princess.
HEY-
You look rich,
can't you afford a driver?
No. I like it alone.
Listen.
Can you show me the
way to sunset point?
Look, if you help me out...
...it'll be nice.
That's fine.
How do I tell you?
Do one thing.
See this path.
Take this route down.
Up ahead you'll find a dirt road.
Take a right from there.
Next you'll come across a hillock.
Jump on it.
And as soon as cross that“
...you will come across a lake.
After you cross that“
...Narayan Temple is 40 steps ahead.
Look.
You can see it from here.
That's where Sunset Point is.
You'll get there in no time.
Get it?
Interesting.
But I don't understand shortcuts.
You don't get shortcuts?
It's right in the middle.
You'll get there in 2 minutes.
If you could sit in the car..
“And direct me to Sunset point“
...l'll be obliged.
I like painting.
So it's important
to see Sunset Point.
So please.
Will you help me?
Papa and uncle are here too.
Koshampa Valley
Project belongs to us.
Oh“.
So you're Kakda.
Strange name, right?
Yes, but I am not
like my uncle and papa.
I am different.
You see, I am an artist.
Simple nature lover.
Beautiful Koshampa.
Magical painting.
I want to paint it from every angle.
If you show me a beautiful
spot like this every day?
Who will do the work?
My father.
You're right.
I'll pay you 1000 Rs. every day.
A reward for your work.
Like..
Like a tourist guide.
I hope I didn't hurt you.
I paint too.
Wow, that's great.
Then we can respect each other.
Come, I'll drop you home.
The children are waiting.
No.
I'll take this route.
O kaY-
I'll pay you 1000 Rs every day“
...if you show me a location.
- So did you take it?
- Yes. Look.
Free note.
Kaanchi, people's trouble
start with this free note.
But I want this to
deposit in the school.
Donation.
How's the SUV?
Better than you.
Because he gave you a note?
He respects me, not like you.
Fine, go around with him.
And then come back to me.
Jealous.
The General Secretary of
India's favorite political party.
Creator of many leaders,
benefactor of the poor..
...Shyam Dada will say a few words.
Hello.
I didn't come here to give a speech.
I came here to confess
some of my crimes.
Everything my secretary
said is a lie.
That, "lam great, I am this, I..."
N01 "0, no, no.
The truth is that“
...we've tarnished the
image of this country.
We've tarnished our own image.
We've donned new
garbs of corruption.
We've played sleazy games
for power and position.
The truth is I did nothing“
...that I should've
done for the country.
So I want you to let
your children join politics.
So that they can lead
the progress of the country..
...in the right direction.
Sorry.
I've nothing more to say.
He's playing mind-games.
Hail India.
Hail Koshampa.
JB Kakda, who's going
to build Koshampa valley here..
...we'll say a few words to you.
My brother...
...Shyam Dada's weakness is..
...he crosses all limits of modesty.
He just said he did nothing.
I want to ask,
if he hasn't done anything“
...then who helped
this country progress?
Roads, dams,
airport, school, technology“
...who built all this.
All this is the creation
of your vision, brother.
Due to your efforts.
He has the habit of taking blame..
...for the dirty jobs
of the other politicians.
My brother is great.
My brother is great!
Teach your children
to progress this country.
Make money.
Make money in every way.
Greed...
...is nothing bad, it's a good thing.
"Money..."
"What's money?"
"Nothing's like it."
"Like money."
What are you thinking, Jhoomar?
That you're peeling an orange.
Orange?
These days' politics
is like this orange.
Different from the inside“
“and different on the outside.
Here...eat it.
So...what did you learn from me today?
That always tell the people..
“What they want to hear.
Very good.
But, Jhoomar,
sometimes you get too loud. Loud.
Brother, I am what I am.
This is how I am.
I am not a hypocrite.
Shushant sir liked her simplicity“
“and Kaanchi liked
his humbleness, sir.
We don't know what
anyone wrote or taught us.
- Kaanchi.
- Yes.
Straight.
We just know three things.
1.Fear no evil.
2.Do what is right.
And 3. Fight for your right.
Where's the India
that was better than the rest?
Who'll be the leader of the people?
And who will be the
benefactor of India.
We.
All of us.
Me.
Myself.
Me alone.
My strength, my honesty.
- Is it true?
- It is.
Is it true?
I like this man.
He's my best friend. Binda.
And me?
We just met.
Good friend.
But doesn't he talk too much.
Exactly.
I tired of explaining him.
He's such a bore, right?
Tell me...can a single
man change the entire country.
If it's like this, then so be it.
We've to lessen the distance
between the rich and the poor.
Bravo.
I heard that young man
likes some local beauty.
Shall we abduct her?
But that's not right, uncle.
Ia-
I mean..
Say it. You're sc***.
You're in love with her. What?
How do I explain it?
I like meeting her.
The way she talks.
The way she moves.
She's the best gift
of God in Koshampa.
I see, let's do one thing then.
Let's sell Koshampa..
“And bring your 'God's gift' here.
What do you say?
Yes .
I want to make her mine.
So the fever's all time high.
Go ahead, son.
Let the heat off. When you
cool down, you can come to me.
O kaY-
Do you know what brother's
biggest mistake is?
This boy here.
Lover boy.
Come on.
You know, today I am going
to make a painting of you..
...more beautiful than you.
Why?
Am I not beautiful?
You are.
But colorless.
There's lack of color in you.
Yes...
...so you are there...
to fill in the colors.
That's right.
That's why you will have to“
...close your eyes
like a divine idol.
Please, come on.
O kaY-
Perfect.
You know, I love red color.
And this red color will
look beautiful on your lips.
I hope you didn't mind that.
I want to go home.
- I want to complete my painting“
- I want to go home.
'Why didn't you slap him?'
'You were scared, weren't you?'
Subedar was here last evening.
To ask for Kaanchi's
hand in marriage for Binda.
And he wants to get
them married this month.
When the mango's
falling in your lap..
...then what's the hesitation?
That's what I am saying,
get them married.
Anyway,
they are made for each other.
I don't see anyone else.
Why not ask Binda first?
I'll talk to him.
Early morning?
I couldn't sleep.
Why?
You know...
my family talk about us.
What?
About our marriage.
Will you marry me?
I am not crazy?
Why?
Am I so bad?
Look, Kaanchi.
You're not old enough
to get married, neither am I?
You still need to grow up, mentally.
And I've to fight these
devils to save Koshampa.
Our families have
been seeing us together“
...since we were kids so..
Now...will you marry me or not?
No.
WhY Won't you?
I'll tell everyone
that you kissed me.
Get lost, you're crazy.
You're a rascal.
And if you say no now..
...then I'll tell
the entire village“
“that you kissed me.
And you also did what's
forbidden before marriage.
Now...are you scared.
If you scream at
the top of your voice..
“And tell everyone
what I did with you..
...still I won't marry you.
Now go, get lost.
Fine, don't do it.
Go and die. And I'll die too.
I'll jump to my death.
Rascal, who do you think you are?
Now go tell your family..
“That I did what's
forbidden before marriage.
And...they can put this
noose around my neck.
Noose?
Yes .
So why do you talk about dying?
Everyone knows that
I was born for you..
“And I will die for you.
"Beloved."
Do I have to say
"Love you" in English?
"Stay in my sights."
I see. I was born for
you and I will die for you.
Good luck.
"My life-my heart."
Shushant, look.
Hello. Kaanchi.
Come on, Seema.
I don't want to talk to this rascal.
He's not Kakda,
they are 'Kekde' (crabs).
Sorry my friend.
Kaanchi.
I want to talk to you.
I don't want to talk to you.
Listen to me, Kaanchi.
- Go away.
- Kaanchi.
- Where are you going inside?
Kaanchi.
Sir, this is not
your father's house.
This is Kaanchi's house.
Sir.
You hawk,“
Leave him.
Leave him, Siddhu.
Go leave.
We're kids of soldiers.
Don't mess with us.
What's his name?
Binda.
Kids of the dishonest
and rich have one problem.
As soon they grow up..
...they think they're
rich and powerful.
Bad.
It's very, very bad..
“That he loved your girlfriend.
But what to do?
I am a father.
I'll have to support
him in this battle of love.
You're right, sir.
I am right too.
And if a war's meant to be,
then so be it, sir.
Do you know what war means?
What nonsense.
Sir, even I've read history.
And anyway,
the girl's issue is a short story.
The real issue is Koshampa.
The government has already passed
verdict on Koshampa. What else?
You're the one who
controls the government.
You, you and you.
I am really pleased to meet you.
Every common man of
India should be like you..
“That was Gandhiji's dream.
Sir, every resident of this
village is exactly like that.
But you can't see
it through those glasses.
That's true.
The storm sometimes
doesn't see the lamps.
That's a nice dialogue.
We'll use it in some meeting.
Go, son.
Bless you. Go.
Blessings?
Brother thinks he's Sai Baba.
He just gave blessings
and let him go.
Shoot those bloody ba****.
In all these years you
didn't recognize Dada yet.
He always greets his
enemies affectionately.
Because he never
says what he thinks“
“and never thinks what he says.
I say what I think.
That's why you're not a politician.
You see Dada is far-sighted.
And we cannot lose
Koshampa for one Shashank.
Ia-
Brilliant.
We came here to do business,
rascal..
Not a love-story.
Music please.
Burn me if you can.
I am not worried
about getting burned
In every aspect, in every way..
...l am waiting to make you mine.
Only to make you mine.
"You're my pain, you're my relief."
"You're my companion,
my benefactor."
"You're my love, you're affection."
"You're my happiness,
you're my tears."
"You're everything."
"You're my pain, you're my relief."
"You're my companion,
my benefactor."
"You're my love, you're affection."
"You're my happiness,
you're my tears."
"You're everything."
"You're my pain, you're my relief."
"You're my companion,
my benefactor."
"You're my love, you're affection."
"You're my happiness,
you're my tears."
One, two, three, four.
Hit, hit, hit.
Th row.
"Whenever I dream.."
"..dream about you."
"My eyes start to glimmer."
"Whenever I take your name.."
"..my breath turns fragrant."
"From head to toe.."
"I look completely
in love with you."
"I'm no longer me, beloved."
"I'm no longer me,
I belong only to you."
"You're my words, you're my speech."
"You're my slumber,
you're my faith."
"You're my love, you're affection."
"You're my happiness,
you're my tears."
"Beautiful bride's getting married."
"May your life be
filled with stars."
"May you never separate
from your beloved."
"May the name of your beloved.."
"..stays embedded on your hands."
"O Kaanchi!"
"Kaanchi!"
Dada says you're the
future of Kakda family.
I see no light on your face.
I can see fused bulb, son.
What's the problem, my dear?
He's deeply in love, sir.
But she's getting married to Binda.
So break it off.
What's the problem?
You can commit a number of crimes,
no worries.
We're behind you.
Don't worry!
Such a strong boy, going weak.
Shameful.
Where were you?
- To the city.
- Why?
Sherwani (Traditional attire).
Before your marriage?
I am only going to show-off today.
You mean honeymoon before honeymoon.
Pa Pa, YOu ' re great.
I love you.
Show-off.
Give me a new pose.
Honeymoon before honeymoon.
Not allowed.
But Kaanchi always
does what isn't allowed.
That's the fun.
No one knows we're here.
Let's runaway, get married.
That will be great fun, isn't it?
Yes, great fun.
Now give me a pose.
Look, I am going down,
you stay here.
Stay there.
Wow, sweetheart.
Something filmy.
A bit to the left.
How am I looking?
Honestly...first time
you're looking so beautiful.
You want to know a truth too.
For the first time
you can see clearly.
- Can I say an old dialogue?
- What?
I love you, Kaanchi.
Always stay like this.
Binda.
Binda. Binda. Binda.
Binda, look at me.
Get up.
Binda.
Fight.
Stop.
JB uncle...
...l killed him.
What did you say?
I killed him.
I knew you'll drop a bomb on me.
Now do everything systematically.
Get a receipt from Koshampa
Valley Toll-booth“
“showing that all
of you left yesterday.
I will handle the police and media.
- Savita.
- Yes.
What's the name of
the media-manager there?
Mr. Gupta.
Talk to him,
and you talk to the police.
Yes .
Yes, sir.
It'll be done.
Binda.
Binda!
Can't you hear? I am calling you.
Binda.
Binda!
Suraj Chauhan has lost his mind.
I just met all the villagers.
No one has the courage“
...to stand against
the law and government.
Everyone's scared...
...of Kakda and his government.
Let's go home, dear.
What happened has happened.
I've serving in the
police force for 40 years.
I've just two words to tell you.
Forget everything.
We should be used to accepting
injustice as destiny.
Powerful people like Kakda
run this country, not us.
We're weak.
And that's how we should be.
We're fools,
and we should remain fools.
Everyone knows about Binda's murder.
But in Bhagwafis FIR it's
been termed as an accident.
What can you do?
And what can we do?
Forget it.
I've written that his
death was an accident.
And this record is proof.
Don't stare at me.
If you have the courage,
then fight with the Kakda family.
What are you doing?
Take that and that.
Take that.
Rascal..
Corrupt.
You dare make a false report.
Rascal..
Kaanchi.
Get up rascal.
Kaanchi, what are you doing?
Rascal.
She assaulted a government servant.
I will burn this police
station down to ashes.
I will burn you alive here.
Let me go.
Who do you think you are?
Leave me. Let me go.
Enough!
Who else are you going to kill?
First you destroyed him..
...now you want to
destroy the village.
You want to fight them.
You want to fight the law. No.
I won't let you do what
you're thinking, Kaanchi.
I will.
I will do as I want.
- Kaanchi.
- Move aside.
- For my sake, Kaanchi.
- No oaths.
You're used to living like insects,
but not me.
You want peace, but not me.
I don't want to live
with you cowards..
- ..Who want to forget the truth.
- Kaanchi.
I won't forget it.
I will die but never forget it.
L am going!
Don't try to find me.
Kaanchi.
Kaanchi stop.
Kaanchi!
Kaanchi, stop!
So Kaanchi...
...didn't die.
If she was dead,
would I be sitting here, sir?
With the bruises,
the beating, the wounds..
“The heartache.
After that Kaanchi
swam across the river..
“And reached a village.
From there she travelled
to Katgodam, Dehradoon.
And finally arrived in Mumbai.
Well, I am sorry
to break this news, son.
Kaanchi leaped to her
death and committed suicide.
It's not good for us.
She kept wandering
around for 12 days“
...on a empty stomach.
Looking for whom?
Me, sir.
She didn't know anyone else here.
- No one.
- Why?
We were childhood friends.
She was looking for my address.
Sir.
Yes .
Do you know Ratanlal Bagula?
Yes, he's our chief.
- Where can I find him?
- Who are you?
I am from his village.
Where can I find him?
Same place where there's theft,
robbery, girls and booze. Where else?
"Here we go."
"You're a big boy.."
"You're a big boy, you're sexy."
"You're like a taxi."
"Looking here.."
"Aiming there."
"lam a non-stop taxi."
"I've a carefree big boy."
"A noose of evil deeds."
"I'm puffing way amongst beauties.."
"..while completely drunk."
"I've a carefree big boy."
"Corruption in my heart."
"Seduction in my body."
"Everyone's tensed about this."
"But I've just one intention."
"Take a puffmblow away the smoke."
"Keep Mary on your side."
"To hell with Harry."
"You're a big boy."
"You're a goon."
"But you're a sexy boy."
"You're like a taxi."
"I don't know what's legal."
"I don't what my heart says."
"When the heart's pleased."
"Even illegal is legal."
"Whether I love or hate."
"What do you care?"
"Whether I lust or love."
"Whether I cheat or rob."
"What do you care?"
"Moral or immoral."
"Get up and go get it, son."
"lam the biggest star here."
"Who cares about the politicians?"
"I've a carefree big boy."
"A noose of evil deeds."
"I'm puffing way amongst beauties.."
"..while completely drunk."
"I've a carefree big boy."
"lam notorious."
"lam the king of evil."
"lam an old dog in this game."
"That's why I am still alive."
"Corruption in my heart."
"Seduction in my body."
"I've a carefree big boy."
"lam notorious."
"But I am sexy."
Rascal. It's me Kaanchi.
So you've come to Mumbai...
...to try your luck.
To be successful.
Quickly.
Short-time.
Great.
Doing great.
I've been rotting here for 7 years.
But I am still an
insect in this city.
Listen to me carefully.
No means no.
I don't have a place for you.
Fine. I'll leave.
I'll sleep on the streets.
Starve to death.
But I will stay here.
I'll return home only
when I am successful..
...when I've done something.
Determination.
I understand...
...what you want to be.
Katrina Ka if.
Come on, I'll make you Katrina Kaif.
See that?
VT Station.
Keep this.
3000, keep it.
Buy a ticket and head back home.
Get it?
Bye .
Come on India!
Sir, the youth have
started lighting candles“
...in the day too.
Hail Bajrang“
Tea.
Sir, someone from the
inquiry commission's here.
Can I call you back?
Jai Hind, sir.
What are you doing here?
Aren't you ashamed?
You threw a helpless
girl from our village“
“out of our house.
She's my friend Teji's daughter.
She's looking for a job,
like you did one day.
Kaanchi will stay here, with me.
Come, Kaanchi.
'I was shocked by her intelligence.'
'And what do I see next morning?'
So you convinced mother?
You've grown very smart, Kaanchi.
Now get up, today is a Sunday.
I want to see Mumbai.
"You're like a taxi."
I really am like a taxi.
You've become really
naughty in Mumbai, Bagula.
Those who decide to
come and die in Mumbai..
...Mumbai belongs to him.
Get it?
A city of big people, big stars.
Do you know Kakda?
How do you know him?
They're building a city in Koshampa.
Kakda. Tremendous power.
I'm one of his important men.
"Don't forget the childhood love."
You haven't changed.
Better, Kaanchi.
Much-much better.
Sigdi.
My name's Sigdi.
Did you forget?
My childhood name is Sigdi.
And I like it too.
Listen, get me a
job with the Kakda's.
Don't you like me wearing
these good clothes?
Why?
Impossible.
My job's still safe,
and that's what matters.
Drink the cola and watch the sights.
I refused to get her
a job at Shyam Kakda's house.
Believe me, sir.
She stood outside Shyam
Kakda's house for 12 days.
To see who goes in,
and who goes out.
And she started identifying
every person going in or out.
And you know what she did one day?
She made Shyam Kakda's housekeeper,
Maya, her target.
Where are you from?
Uttranchal.
What do you do?
I am looking for a job.
Anything, small household chores.
Maya sister, Vidya from
our staff is on a month's leave.
So appoint her instead.
She looks poor.
I don'tjust look poor, I am.
What's your name?
- Sigdi.
- What?
Sigdi.
Do you know anyone here?
No.
No one?
Yes. I knowjust one person.
Dada, C news' report
on the exit polls is..
...that Satyakam
and the youth party..
...are getting stronger.
They are the only
obstructions in our polls..
“And there's nothing
else to worry about.
Dada, the situation is serious.
We'll have to do something.
Bagula, what's the news?
Sir, Satyakam has been
talking rubbish in the media.
You know him.
He's your friend, isn't he?
Not actually.
- Vedant.
- Yes.
Call him.
- And this“
- Hold on.
Hello, sir, Satyakam speaking.
Yes, this is Vedant speaking.
On behalf of Shyam sir.
Why, can't Dada talk to me?
Look, Satyakam,
just your name's Satyakam“
“but you're no honest person.
Brother has served
the country for 50 years.
No, he's scavenged
The youth are really angry, sir.
And they're prepared to uproot you.
Satyakam,
I comply with all your thoughts.
These discussions are
just an exchange of words.
You move ahead,
we're behind you.
God bless you my son.
He hung up.
Satya, it's not easy
to expose Shyam Kakda.
It's not difficult either.
One day we'll definitely
expose his lie.
What's this?
Didn't you hear?
I said "You move ahead,
I am...right behind you".
Tell me Delhi's schedule, Savita.
The media's been favoring
Satyakam because..
“They keep giving them secrets“
“through RTI or different contacts.
We'll have to do something.
Even I shouted slogans
when I was young.
Let them.
They'll calm down eventually.
But what about the media?
The media's job is to shout.
Event to event, person to person.
They want to raise TRP.
When we do an event, our TRP soars.
When they show the event,
their TRP soars.
Bagula. What are
you looking around for?
I've done your job. Happy?
HaPPV?
What are you staring at?
On your reference
I appointed Sigdi“
...in Vidya's place for a month.
Right, right, right.
- Can I meet her?
- No.
Is this house?
Now you've to do
my son Ritesh's job.
Get it?
Those who come to Mumbai
and decide to die..
...Mumbai belongs to him.
Thank you, Bagula.
"Kaanchi."
What did you say her name was?
Sigdi.
Reference, Maya.
Thank God you're here.
Otherwise I've to do all this alone.
You don't know...
...the Kakda family
are a big scoundrel..
Who else lives here?
JUSt the senior master.
Public meetings during day.
Private meetings at night.
He has a son too.
Yes, he does.
Shushant.
He's insane, completely mad.
Scoundrel.
Thank God he's gone
to Dubai for a month.
They've a big house out there.
Kaanchi has committed suicide.
I am sorry, but you were
too obsessed with that girl.
I am sure someone will
definitely come from there.
To destroy you.
Who?
Some youngster from Koshampa.
Shake hands.
What are you doing?
Shushant.
I am Kakda, you know that.
Kakda.
So just chill.
Who else do you have here?
I have a brother. Sudhir.
He's a party worker
with Sanjay Pathar.
I had a mother.
But she passed away last year.
Do you have a mother?
- Yes, I do.
- Where?
In the village.
I really miss my mother.
Don't you.
That's how mothers are.
She yells,
beats us, then she cries..
“And then feeds us.
'For 25 days she
waited for Shushant.'
'But he didn't come.'
You look sexy in this hairstyle.
I like the way you
call me sexy, Savita.
Did you see anything?
Yes .
Savita was combing your hair.
And you were kissing“
What you saw...
...you did not see.
And if you tell anyone what you saw.
Then you won't be able
to see yourself tomorrow.
Sweet girl.
Go.
Sir.
Jhoomar sir's call for you.
Yes, Jhooma r.
What did you see?
What you saw...you did not see.
Get that?
Good girl.
"Kaanchi."
There's a powerful failure
outside the bungalow.
Call Dhanraj.
Where's Sigdi?
She's gone to call her aunt.
I see.
The electrician's here.
We'll have power back on in a while.
Sir's sleeping inside.
Don't disturb him.
My brother Sanjay called.
He was asking when is Shyam Dada..
“Getting you a MLA ticket?
I said I don't know.
I know your aspirations
of becoming a minister.
I've been with you for 9 years.
I gave you everything.
That's why I am with you too.
Forget it.
We should talk about public
matters in a private room.
Make love, with a system.
You and your system.
I love you...Savita.
Siam!
Call her.
Yes .
She hung up.
Mohanlal, open that door.
I hope you remember, tomorrow“
...is my brother's musical night
at Mustaq lttarwala's bungalow.
You will have to come as my guest.
Savita, you know.
I've to attend Godrej's Holi party.
You won't go there.
Is that a threat?
Yes, it is.
If you don't come...
...then I'll have to request“
“Satyakam to come there.
Then...
...you will have to join his party.
Maybe.
You'll have to tell him my secrets.
You said...
...anything's possible in politics.
Savita.
You're my confidante.
Yes, I am loyal.
Swiss Banks, millions in scams.
That boy's murder
in Koshampa Valley..
“And your relations with girls.
I've hidden everything
in my heart for all these years.
And even Sanjay doesn't know this.
For 9 years I've
given you everything.
You must understand.
My patience is running out.
- Vedant.
- Yes, Dada.
You were right,
Savita's running out of patience.
I was thinking...
...Savita will have
to pass our ordeal.
We'll have to erase
Savita's name from our list.
But with a system.
Who's going in sir's room? Check.
Balbeer, check who's at the back?
See, someone's there.
Hello. This is Nattu,
Hello, Bagula.
"You didn't come,
at least your voice did."
"O Technology."
Bagula, I want to meet you today.
Look, I am busy the whole day“
...in the government's
budget session.
Do one thingmcome
to Sajjad bhai's party.
I am doing a super item.
You're going to
do this with Kaanchi.
Watch my talent too.
Look, it's urgent. Please.
That oldie Kakda's coming too.
Kaanchi!
Brother, I can hear
the danger bells ringing.
I can see it in my house.
I was looking for Shushant.
Kakda. I will tell you everything.
Your life's in danger too.
Many people are after you.
MY Phone.
My name's Bagula.
BA pass, policeman.
Yes, BA pass, policeman.
But tonight I am a singer,
for this musical night“
...for the wedding of my dear friend,
Sanjay Pathare.
The brother of Savita Pathare.
Future minister.
Clap. Clap. Clap.
Now. Now, now, now.
Tonight I am going to sing a song.
Yes, I am going to sing a song.
And all of you are going
to hum just three words.
Only three words.
"Under...the...blanket."
With your permission
I'd like to start.
"Today's the groom's night."
"Under the blanket."
"His bride will be with him."
"Under...the...blanket."
"They will talk softly."
"That's when they
will actually meet."
"Under...the...blanket."
"The plethora of love."
"The plethora of love,
Under...the...blanket."
"Let's make love Under...
the...blanket."
"Under...the...blanket."
"Two heart's are meeting, but."
"lam no hero, I am a villain."
"Under...the...blanket."
"The passion arouses."
"Loneliness makes me restless."
"The night passes away."
"Under...the...blanket."
"The plethora of love,
Under...the...blanket."
"Let's make love Under...
the...blanket."
"Under...the...blanket."
"The plethora of love,
Under...the...blanket."
"Let's make love Under...
the...blanket."
- Hello.
How are you, sir?
"Shameless heart."
"Under...the...blanket."
"I want my right, right here."
"The water's blue.."
"Under...the...blanket."
"Lungi Dance."
"The moment will come."
Mahima Chaudhary.
"When love will burn through."
"Nothing will be important."
"Yet things will happen."
"Under...the...blanket."
See you... I am getting late.
"Grandma felt young again."
"Under...the...blanket."
"Granny was fed up."
"Uncle was troubled."
"Under...the...blanket."
"Aunt was bothered."
"Bablu was pleased."
"Babli was ruined."
"Under...the...blanket."
"The plethora of love."
"There was once a beauty,
and a crazy lover."
"Under...the...blanket."
"Match to my beats."
"The plethora of love."
"Clap your hands and say."
"Dance the night away."
"This the right way."
"Under...the...blanket."
"The plethora of love."
Madam Braganza, my party
is for the rich. - Yes, sir.
I want imported foreign dancers.
Not these local ones.
Absolutely.
- In my party I want the best girls.
- Yes, sir.
Okay, let's go.
My nephew ShushanL.
...is specially coming
over for this party.
'As soon as she heard
about Shushant..'
'..she turned her attention to JB.'
'And then what did she do?
Look at her charade.'
Cheers.
Oh, God!
Where's my bag?
My bag“ My bag!
- Which bag?
- Oh, God!
My bag was here.
Oh my, God.
What am I going to do?
- Ma'am.
- What?
- Your bag.
- Thank you.
He was trying to flee with it.
I snatched it back.
Thank you my dear.
Thank you.
Get me a job at her place.
Ma'am, Sigdi wants
to join your company.
Why not.
You're a pretty girl.
And I need pretty girls.
You join me tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?
- Yes.
Thank you.
Girls.
As a hostess,
you've to remember three things.
Smile like an airhostess.
And your body language
should be like a model.
- Am I clear?
- Yes, sir.
Would you stop that please?
It's very disturbing.
Thank you.
Sir, I've a question.
Go ahead.
If a VIP guest winks at us,
what should we do?
Good question.
Then you should wink back.
Shouldn't we slap him?
Sigdi, do you know
who you're talking to?
It's alright.
Yes. The very handsome JB sir.
Right.
Well...
Thank you.
- Sorry sir if I've offended you.
- No, no, no.
You should always speak
what's in your heart.
Before you ruin my party.
You know, I like this.
I like this girl.
Welcome, Jacob Taylor.
Welcome.
- Please meet my wife, Gayatri.
- Hello.
Better known as Mrs. JB.
- Oh really.
- My husband's been speaking a lot..
- “About you and your wife.
- She's in America.
Sir.
Yes .
Thank you, Bagula.
Thank you.
Sir, the way you were
staring at it, I knew..
“That you want it too.
Anointment.
No one anoints the host.
I did it only because you said so.
Such a sweet girl.
Shall we?
Come on.
I can see pain on your face.
Yes, I do.
From top to bottom.
Get lost, scoundrel.
Very important, sir.
Today evening at 5 you've
another meeting with Jacob.
And this is the discussion
on cash-flow. - Yes.
Fine, fine, fine.
We'll see these accounts later.
- Sir, this is for you.
- No.
Excuse me.
Bagula.
Sir.
You go, we'll see.
Do one thing.
See that girl in the front.
That one.
Give her these chocolates“
“and tell her I sent them.
Her?
Go on.
Where did you get them from?
Some scoundrel...has sent it.
Take it.
With this development
we'll need $200 million more..
...to complete Koshampa project.
We need that kind of money for.
And I've given the entire
cash account to Harry Chang.
We just need a
confirmation from you.
And this way I can show you..
...nobody can do better than us.
Will you excuse me,
I'd like to go the restroom.
If you don't mind.
Please. You sit down
and please watch this.
Just be back. Excuse me.
Well, Mr. Jacob.
Good afternoon, sir.
Good afternoon.
Don't look at me like
that when I am in a meeting.
They are important people.
My mind gels diverted.
But...you waved at me.
So I waved back at you.
When you wave your hand,
it makes my heart shake.
Please don't do that.
And...
I've many things“
- Good afternoon, sir.
- Good afternoon.
I've many things to say to you.
The flowers in the bedroom
upstairs have withered.
Please change them.
And I'm mostly free after 8.
8 o'clock.
L...always so busy that“
...l can't find time for myself.
I have no friends.
They are all greedy.
They have their eyes on !B's pocket.
But you're so rich.
Yes, that's true.
But...l've the heart of a kid.
I'm always looking
for friends like you.
Yes, Shushant.
There are lot of discrepancies..
...in Jacob Taylor and
Harry Chang's cash accounts.
I've my own doubts.
Fine, fine, whatever.
Shushant, my nephew.
He troubles me a lot.
- When he is coming?
- He's coming.
He'll come for the party.
What are you doing?
Jhoomar.
Jacob's already at the dining table.
Come soon, my dear husband.
Alright.
Welcome, sir.
Everyone's waiting for you.
Time is short.
6 pm, you've the
sign the Jacob deal.
And 8pm, party celebration.
JB sir's surprise item.
Even I have a surprise for you.
Nattu got killed.
I know, sir.
Police department is on it.
So relax.
Can we go now?
This is about cash.
If anything goes wrong,
we'll all be behind bars.
That rascal Harry
Chang has reported“
...only $43.8 million
instead of $45 million.
- No, sir.
- Because Rupee rate is falling.
I don't care if the
Rupee rate is falling.
I want my money.
I want my full $45 million.
Sure, sir.
One more thing, sir.
Shushant has arrived.
Yes, yes, yes, I'll be there.
You called me, sir.
Oh Sigdi, I..
One minute, Sigdi.
This is very important.
Very very important work.
Here we go.
Come, Sigdi. Come.
So what was I saying?
I was saying that today's party“
...will be attended by famous people.
So maybe I won't
get time to talk to you.
So don't mind.
After the party we'll do it.
O kaY-
Okay?
Do you love me?
How do I believe you?
How will you?
Give me a kiss.
Kiss me.
Kiss me here.
Come on.
I've to make today's night special.
"This is the only night."
"Whatever happens is right."
"Go crazy on the dance floor."
Ladies and gentlemen,
can I have your attention please."
You're all here to welcome
Jacob Turner and his team..
“Celebrating the
biggest deal signed..
“Between the JB Company
and Jacob Company.
Please give a big
hand to Shushant Kakda..
...for making this deal happen.
We all request JB sir
to come on the dancing floor..
“With Albela Girl.
Sir, didn't they
invite you to the party?
No.
"We need to make
this night special."
"This is the only night."
"Go crazy on the dance floor."
"We need to express
through our eyes.."
"..what we can't say."
"For my sake,
do something amazing."
"Solve your devotee's problems."
"Shake a leg with the hermit."
"Shake a leg."
"My stars are shining."
"Shake a leg with the hermit."
"Shake a leg."
"Lose yourself and shake a leg."
"This is the only night."
"Whatever happens is right."
"Shake a leg."
"Let this night pass like a dream."
"Fill the gaps in
my lips with yours."
"Solve your devotee's problems."
"Loosen yourself with the hermit."
"Shake a leg with the buddies."
"Shake a leg."
"Shake a leg with the hermit."
"My stars are shining."
"Shake a leg."
"Lose yourself and shake a leg."
- What?
- It's true, sir.
Few people saw him
run after a girl.
"This is the only night."
"Shake a leg."
"Whatever happens is right."
"This is the only night."
- Bagula.
- Yes, sir.
You've to find a girl.
Who?
The girl that ran with Nattu.
Done, sir.
Bagula, secretly.
"This is the only night."
"Shake a leg."
"Whatever happens is right."
"This is the only night."
"Shake a leg."
We need to make
this night special.
Sweet hart.
Can I drink some water?
- Go.
- Be right back.
Go. Go. Go.
Love you, Sigdi.
My husband unconscious,
but I am still conscious.
He's gone mad.
But youmlittle girl“
If you value your life, then“
“get out of this
house in 3 minutes.
And don't even dream
about this man.
Just save your life and get out.
Get out!
God favors the brave.
Mission JB successful.
But a bad news was waiting ahead.
The entire city's under a shock..
...because Shyam Kakda's secretary“
“Savita Pathare died
in a bomb blast yesterday.
Who and how this
bomb blast took place..
...the government has no answer.
Shyam Kakda's personal
secretary Savita Pathare“
...who was present here
during the incident“
...fell prey to the bomb blast.
Home Minister's secretary
JB Godbole has stated that..
...terrorist from the
neighboring country..
...can be behind this bomb blast.
And an enquiry commission
has been appointed.
This is women killing.
Sister Savita was very nice woman.
Savita Pathare was supposed
to get the MLA ticket.
But unfortunately, she fell
prey along with 4 other people.
This is Jananta, Zee News.
Savita's death isn't
just a loss to the country“
“but for me too.
Savita was the daughter
of this country.
She was a rising youth.
She was the future.
May God give peace
to Savita's soul.
Hello.
Can I speak to Manjari?
The rival country hasn't
done a good thing“
...by killing her.
The enemy should know our strength.
Those rascal terrorists
killed sister Savita.
That's why I was calling you.
I lost my phone.
Lost.
Hold on.
I found this phone in the garden.
This is my phone.
Come on India.
Where's that India that
was better than the rest.
We got it.
Not one, but two.
We politicians concentrate
more on power..
“And less on doing our jobs.
We spend 70% of our
time in party politics.
And do less development.
The real leaders are those“
...who take the demands
of the poor to the Parliament.
We'll have to erase
Savita's name from our list.
But with a system.
Terrorists kill innocent
people and leave.
When girls like Nirbhaya
get raped my heart aches.
My heart aches seeing
these poor people.
My heart aches when
I see these kids.
Protection of women
is my first responsibility.
What other responsibilities
do you have?
Do tell us.
Shyam Kakda!
Calm down. Everyone calm down.
This is a game of
the opposition party.
Look...Satyakam's party is..
I am standing right here.
And I will stand here.
No one can budge me.
'You want to fight these people.'
'The law.'
Famous Indian Politician
Shyam Kakda's..
.30 year old reign
has come to an end today.
The opposition has demanded an..
...attach on all of
Shyam Kakda's property.
High court has given orders“
...to keep Shyam Kakda
in judicial custody.
Sir, I've received a list Mr.
Jhoomar's foreign bank accounts.
Who gave it to you?
The 'Jai Yuva Sang'.
And who gave it to them?
They don't want to say it.
- Good morning, sir.
- Yes.
Nishikant from CBI.
So what do I do?
Get up, sir,
we've an arrest warrant for you.
What's my crime?
I've a list of all your companies..
...laundered money list of crimes.
And I even have all your
foreign bank account numbers.
- Account numbers?
- Yes.
Account no. Z3PCSX0009300..
“And many more.
Wow, very good.
Very, very good.
Who sent you?
The government.
And who owns the government.
- You do.
- So?
Sir, this is why I
came to meet you alone.
Friend, catch your breath.
I don't have the time.
Okay, tell me something.
Do you like music?
- Yes.
- Then hear this.
Kill him.
Kill him. Kill him.
Sir, sir, sir.
Satyakam's antenna's functioning.
Why are you committing
crime after crime after crime?
Crime after crime after crime?
Look there. It's all recorded.
And the entire police
team is watching you.
So why are you shooting?
"My beloved."
"Always stay in my sights."
Everyone knows I was born for you,
and I'll die for you.
Okay, guys, we've made
all preparations for evening.
Let's have a conference
tonight and tell them..
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Stop it.
I'm calling the police.
Stop it!
What's going on?
At any cost we won't let
the Kakda brothers get bail.
They will get bail, sir.
Don't worry.
All under control, sir.
Kaanchi.
Why did you come here?
Who brought you here?
Meena sent me a letter.
I came running.
Come home with me, Kaanchi.
Come home.
I came here breaking
ties with you, mother.
To fight.
Girls don't get furious
like this, dear.
Only girls get furious like this.
Don't lecture me, mother. Go away.
Kaanchi.
I beg you Kaanchi.
Let's go home.
Kaanchi, stop.
Sister.
Kaanchi.
" Lonely. . .youth . "
"Dreams fading away."
Go back, mother.
"Barren eyes."
"Can't cry or sing."
Stop, Kaanchi.
"Such is my pain."
"How do I tell you my pain...
mother?"
"Such is my pain."
"How do I tell you my pain...
mother?"
"I've accounted some
of the small pains."
"Situations have shattered me,
they haven't."
"My view towards life has changed."
"I'm unique from others."
"Such is my pain."
"How do I tell you my mother?"
Stand there quietly.
I will shoot you.
I am police officer, you know.
Look, Kaanchi, you're angry.
But no matter what you do,
the world won't change?
Will the country change?
What's there is there.
I used to say the same thing.
But what there won't stay for long.
It won't.
Now only the right
thing will happen.
What's right!
This is my fight.
And I will fight it alone.
What will you do, Bagula?
You bow before these devils.
You only run your home,
not the country.
And that's why you cannot shoot me.
Ican.
I destroyed Shyam Kakda.
His power.
Jhoomar Babu. JB.
All of Shushant's strength.
And now I will finish Shushant.
You can do whatever you want.
Go.
I am going,
and if you have the guts“
“then shoot me in the back.
"Jai He!"
"The world's so big."
"Let's find him."
"Jai He!"
"The world's so big."
"Let's find him."
"Where's that India that
was better than the rest?"
"The world's so big."
"Let's find him."
"Where's that India that
was better than the rest?"
"Jai He!"
I'll apologies to her.
I'll convince her.
If you bring her to me..
...l'll give you 5 million, in cash.
If you don't,
you know how dangerous I am, right.
Many people have calling about you.
- It's getting dangerous.
- I know.
Do one thing, go in the office.
Get ready and then come back.
"It was liberated and
was heading this way."
"Was lost in the way."
"Or has it shattered?"
"There was compassion."
"There was righteousness."
"We only heard about dreams."
"Jai He!"
"The world's so big."
"Let's find him."
"Where's that India that
was better than the rest?"
"Jai He!"
"It had a song too."
"I remember it now."
"And every politician's
singing it.."
"..without knowing it's meaning."
"Jai He!"
"Tell them...we'll sing."
"We know that song."
"When the people.."
"When the people
will be the leader.."
"Benefactors of their fate."
"Jai He!"
"Where's that India that
was better than the rest?"
"Jai He!"
"Where's that India that
was better than the rest?"
"Jai He!"
"Where's that India that
was better than the rest?"
"Jai He!"
Come.
Where have you brought me?
Thank you my friend.
There's 5 million in that bag.
You kept your promise,
here's your reward.
Thank you, sir.
Forgive me for taking a peek.
Here's your memorabilia.
Can I go?
- Thanks.
- Thank you, sir.
Thank you, sir.
Bagula. Rascal.
You betrayed me.
You dare sell me out.
I will kill you first.
Bagula.
Obsession.
After you left...
...l could see only your
face in every painting.
Your gleam.
Your eyes.
These cheeks.
These lips.
I still love you.
I will make another
painting of you.
Naked.
Nude.
You can kill me if you want.
No so easily.
You should feel the same pain I did.
Look.
Look. Look.
Ba**** wrong timing.
Sir, this is not the way.
Out.
Sir, this isn't right.
Sigdi snatched my gun.
I am a police officer, sir.
- Out.
- This isn't right, sir.
You bring Kaanchi's sister
home and don't tell me.
- This isn't right.
- Out.
This isn't right,
sir, you're pointing a gun at me.
I am your servant, your friend.
I am loyal to you.
And you're pointing
a gun at me. At me.
There's just one way to show you.
And that is to kill you, sir.
Kaanchi, run away.
I'll deal with this rascal.
"Jai He."
Now watch my way.
Take this. And that.
And this.
Nini.
Fight.
Kill me.
So where did Kaanchi go?
To her village Koshampa.
With her mother.
Just like Kakda fled from Koshampa..
“Without leaving any evidence.
Similarly,
Kaanchi returned to her village“
“without leaving any evidence.
You mean Kaanchi fled from the law.
One, two, three, four.
Come on, come on, jump.
Jump, come on.
One, two, three, four.
Faster.
"Stay in my sights."
Sir.
Is it true that you gave
orders to close Kaanchi's file?
What do you think?
Who is right?
Kaanchi or Kakda.
Sir, there's tremendous
pressure from the superiors.
I'm getting calls from Delhi.
- Let it ring.
- But, sir..
Leave it.
You do know Arindham
Barua from Delhi Office.
'75 batch.
One day when he was
drunk he told me that“
“the minister gave
him his unnamed flat“
...to change two lines in his report.
More than 60%
politician politicians“
...have amassed from 100
to 1000 crores in 10 years.
From system.
The law is sold outside the court.
Deals are made with the media.
MLAs are bought and
sold in party politics.
MPs are bought and sold.
Businessmen make the
news laws of business.
Wow!
You do know that.
You, me, we all know it.
Yet, we keep quiet.
Because we're slaves of the system.
And these politicians
make this system, control it..
“And break it too.
Corruption dwells
in our blood, Gautam.
What a shame.
But Kaanchi's the new youth.
She gave a fitting reply
to a power like Kakda..
...from her system.
And said...Fear no Evil.
And do what is right.
And that's why I
closed Kaanchi's file.
And I know I'm doing
the right thing.
Because I feel good.
Kaanchi!
You know, Kaanchi..
“Both the Kakdas were
sentenced to 15 years ofjail.
The court has also
cancelled Kakda's project.
Koshampa's lands were returned too.
With the grace of God.
Right.
You were furious for
no reason and left us.
Everything became
alright after you. Right?
"Kaanchi."
"Stay in my sights."