Lajjo! Cover your head.
This wind feels wild!
It's touching me everywhere!
Rani?
You want a taste?
She just turned 15.
You won't find a better bride for...
What's his name?
Gulab.
Gulab is my only son.
Really, Tulsi...
My worries are over.
I couldn't have found a more beautiful bride...
If I had looked with a lantern!
It's all God's will.
But for me,
God sent one daughter after another.
I have four more to marry off.
One less to worry about.
Janaki is ours now.
Wonderful!
Let us fix a date then.
Just one request...
Could the dowry be raised
from 3 Lakh to...
To 4 Lakh?
Gulab, your bride better have big boobs!
Or else get a refund!
I have to make a call.
You'll get it back, I need to call my Ma.
Please eat.
You have a long ride back.
Is she any good?
Worth the money?
Did they reduce the dowry?
Later...
I'm still in the meeting.
Do your meeting Ma...
But listen...
I'll want a refund if she's rubbish!
What's the matter?
Hello! How is Champa?
I'm begging you...
Leave us alone!
Don't get an educated bride Gulab.
These educated types,
have books riding their minds...
Then what will we ride?
You got a problem?
Nah...
Just enjoying the view.
Careful or you'll enjoy a beating.
Leave it Kishan.
They're not worth our time.
Witch!
How dare she look us in the eye!
Look at Rani. She's better than any son.
The way she takes care of
her mother-in-law.
Gulab. I said I'm in a meeting.
Gulabo?
Is that your name? Like a Rose?
Does every part of you smell like roses?
Who is this?
Your lover. Your hero.
Your Shahrukh Khan!
Rani...
That thing looks like trouble.
It's new, Gulab bought it for me.
I'm still learning it.
What an exciting place to keep it!
Ma is saying this now,
but she cursed me every
time I birthed a daughter.
You with your raging hormones.
Couldn't keep your skirt down!
She was a girl-vending machine!
It's the same everywhere Ma.
If men had their way
they'd be pounding us round-the-clock.
Thankfully God created
barren women like me!
Or else the volume of babies produced,
Would fill a whole new nation!
What beautiful eyes.
Such long luscious hair.
Gulab won't believe his luck
when he sees you!
Namaste.
Tell me truthfully Lajjo.
My hair is graying.
My eyes are turning weak too.
Last night I didn't recognize
myself in the mirror.
Do I even look like a woman?
Let's see...
Your eyes are so deep...
Like whirlpools to drown in.
Your mouth is like luscious berries
I want to suck the juice from them.
Duffer!
If only you were a man!
Then I'd get under that skirt!
Stop!
Tell me something.
Who is this Shahrukh Khan?
Is he a film hero?
Shahrukh Khan??
Not just any hero.
He's the hottest!
Manoj took me to his film once.
Why do you ask?
He called my mobile.
Must have been a mistake.
Let me see!
Shahrukh Khan called!
And you didn't tell me?
It has come to our notice...
Champa has run away
from her in-laws' home.
Before trouble starts
between the families...
She must go back.
I won't go back!
My husband doesn't give a damn!
I've come home to my parents'...
How is that wrong?
After marriage,
your parent's home is not yours.
Go home to your husband.
Go back before you bring shame to our village.
Lakdi manage your daughter.
Just like we managed Ganga last year?
What happened to her?
She committed suicide.
Times have changed Kheema.
So should we.
Or we'll suffer.
Quiet Kishan!
Don't interfere with the Elders!
You've shamed the village enough...
By bringing in a foreigner bride.
You shamelessly
parade her on your bike!
Keep out of our business!
I'm not some alien from outer space.
My name is Naobi. I'm also an Indian.
My husband drives me to the bus stop,
So I can teach the children in the next village.
What is shameful about that?
Do not flaunt your education here!
We also educate our kids!
As for you Champa...
This village is as much
mine as it is yours!
Society has rules for a reason.
Don't question the Elders!
We won't survive without their support!
Their support can go to hell!
Okay... Calm down.
Moving on.
Devi...
Head of the village women,
has something to say.
Namaste.
The women have a request...
The trucking contracts
keep our men away for weeks.
While we women are trapped
inside our homes.
We are the last village without TV.
TV would entertain the men too.
Then they wouldn't need to
visit the Dance Company...
We already regret giving
into your last demand.
You demanded mobile phones,
To keep track of your husbands.
We relented.
But what happened?
Shiva's daughter eloped with
a man she met on the mobile.
In the next village...
Girls who watched TV
started wearing jeans pant.
Hear this brothers...
Next thing we know...
These women will be
driving our trucks too!
Then there's the matter of money.
A TV dish is expensive.
Kishan has negotiated...
A large order for our handicrafts.
We will get paid before
the Dussehra festival.
We women will pool our earnings,
And buy a TV for the village.
First get the money. Then we'll see.
And with that...
This meeting comes to a close.
Hail Lord Ram!
Hail Lord Krishna!
Ma! Don't send me back!
You should be grateful.
Your in-laws
have agreed to take you back!
They have forgiven you!
Forgiven? What for?
My husband doesn't
even touch me.
He has a mistress
in the next village.
Quiet, Champa!
You have shamed us enough!
I take responsibility for her!
Kishan and Naobi will employ me.
You stay out of this Kishan!
How dare you speak for her!
My brother-in-law forces himself on me!
All the men in the house don't
miss an opportunity to fuck me.
Even my father-in-law!
Can you bear to hear more?
I had to abort a child because
I didn't know who the father was!
Ma... they will kill me!
Don't send me to that hell!
She'll come around.
All will be well.
I look like a clown!
Like a Prince!
Such a beautiful face.
Eyes just like your father's.
I'm not a girl!
Beautiful? Grandma tell her...
Have you seen Kishan's wife?
Brazenly rides the bus alone!
Exposes her midriff to the world!
That is Kishan's business.
All his education drivel
is corrupting our village.
You stay out of it.
You know as a child,
I loved reading books too.
But my mother said,
"Girls who read make bad wives."
So, she married me off at 14.
You're trapping me the same way!
And why did you build this wall?
Oh... You'll see...
After your wedding!
Now listen, don't take on a new contract.
I need you at home.
No way! It's my last days of bachelorhood.
I'll call you from the mobile.
I won't answer.
See you in a few days.
Take care Grandma.
Ma...
Our boy is becoming a man.
Lajjo!
Is the wedding order ready?
It's due in 2 days!
Just one blouse left.
I tried some new designs,
From that magazine you gave me.
Yes...
Naobi, meet Rani and Lajjo...
Very important members
of my craft team.
And this is Naobi. My new bride.
She is college educated.
Speaks English fluently.
She negotiated our new contract.
Soon our business will boom.
You're so beautiful!
Such soft skin!
Fair like a foreigner.
Kishan you have a good eye.
Let's meet tomorrow.
I'll arrange the advance till then.
I've heard foreign women bathe
in milk. That's why they glow.
Duffer!
Only one thing makes a woman glow...
Not milk, soap or cream.
In Bijli's words...
It's called sex!
That's why you and I look so sad!
What's the date today?
I heard the dance company is here.
Lets go to see Bijli tonight!
BIJLI... The Earthquake-maker!!!
The Dance Company is back!
Once again in your village!
A night of lust and passion...
With the queen! Bijli!
First show tonight at 8!
Pull out your wallets,
the Earthquake-maker is here!
Shake it my prince...
Shake it Inspector...
Sit back, relax Inspector...
you're off duty now!
Shake it my Prince...
Shake it Inspector...
I will shake down your courtiers...
Turn their squirrels to snakes...
I will break your pride...
I will disrupt your peace!
I will zap your brains...
I will make...
I will make your earth shake...
I will make an earthquake in your bed.
Yes, an earthquake in your bed.
She agreed to sex you up for 500.
You have an hour.
Go get deflowered!
Make your father proud!
I hope your shooter works.
Like an AK-47!
When I stretch like this...
Even the morning gets shy...
When my anklets ring...
The earth comes alive...
I'm an angel...
A witch...
A babe...
A bitch...
No innocent flower.
Go ahead deflower!
She will make the earth shake.
She will bring an earthquake in the bed.
Look Bijli...
We don't turn away clients.
Make your money while they still want you.
My heart's not in it.
Get it?
Life's more than just money and sex.
And don't start about
bringing on a new girl.
Or I'll run off to Mumbai!
Aha! Marilyn Monroe
and her stardom dreams...
I've been hearing this for 3 years.
Listen... I'm like your father.
So I'll tell you the truth.
You are a whore.
And will always be a whore.
So shut up and go earn!
In that case daddy dearest...
I have a request.
My body is a little wrung out today...
Tell your client to come another night.
This shop is closed!
Here is your bottle.
I am glad you refused that client.
Why?
Thought you'd get lucky tonight?
Bijli...
Please shut your tent securely at night.
When I came to wake you today, your skirt...
Why is it you always wake me?
Does the boss pay you extra for it?
You'd prefer someone else?
I wish!
But just my luck...
You are my only cuckoo clock.
Bijli... You're back!
Lajjo! It's been ages!
Hello!
Goodbye!
Yeah... I'm going.
Hey Rani...
So I said to the boss...
"No way. Go to hell!"
From now on...Bijli opens only for love.
You want to give up your life
and become like us?
She's lost it!
Can't she see how
boring and sad we are?
Come here... I have a secret.
I met a man in the last village.
He taught me to dream.
Rocked me to the
moon and back all night.
In the morning he said...
"Hey Bijju... dream away."
"Your whole life is ahead of you."
What a man!
I'm still burning up.
Those long dancing fingers...
Soft tickling moustache.
Hang on!
Should I imagine fingers or moustache?
You choose.
He stroked me the whole night...
Pressed all the right buttons.
I went straight to heaven!
And then he aroused me...
With his words!
I doubt I've ever spoken
so much in my life!
Did you tell Bijli?
No?
Gulab's date is fixed!
We found him a bride!
Wedding is on the 9th.
Her blouse was so tight...
No wonder men fall at her feet!
I think Bijli makes up these stories.
I have never heard of a man
talking during the act!
Hello?
Gulabo, why are you panting?
I am out of breath.
What are you up to?
I'm walking. What's it to you?
I think I'm falling in love.
Do you feel the flutter too?
No!
Will you be my Valentine?
What?
Valentine?
Valentine day?
It's a day for naughty love.
I've got to go!
That was Shahrukh Khan.
First call was by mistake.
Now he calls all the time.
Says naughty things.
He calls me Gulabo... His rose.
He's outrageous!
You're blushing.
Maybe I should tell him the truth?
About the real me?
Is this all wrong Lajjo?
Why wrong?
Ma, remember when I'd spilled water...
And you slipped on it?
I'd burst out laughing.
I was so young!
What a beating you gave me that day.
Your son Shankar,
had to save me.
But who could save me from Shankar?
When he started staying out all night...
You said...
"All will be well."
When he kept that mistress...
Again you said... "All will be well."
When Shankar died in that accident...
First you cursed me...
And then said... "All will be well."
But nothing changed.
Years passed... Gulab grew up.
And I...
Once Gulab's bride gets here...
It'll be my turn to lie on a cot...
and all will be well.
What you doing Lajjo?
Going for a competition?
No... I have a delivery tomorrow.
What?
A delivery.
What do you know about "delivery"?
You, with your infertile womb.
Booze has drowned all the love inside you.
No... no... no... no!
What did you say bitch?
If I hadn't spent so much on you.
I'd have trashed you long ago!
I'm not your whore!
What?
I'm not your whore.
Barren bitch!
Don't! Please!
The donkey chose water over booze.
So the moral of the story is...
A man who doesn't booze is an Ass!
Right Gulab?
Man up! Have a drink!
When is your date with God oldie?
Marry me? What say?
He's so sweet in public,
such a monster at home.
Last night he was so drunk.
He said to me...
"No matter how deep I drill...
You remain a barren desert."
Why is she crying so much?
Has she found out...
About your tiny willy?
Rani I need to show you something.
What's this?
Her hair was infested with lice.
There was no other way.
I asked her father to postpone...
But he refused.
Said that the money's been taken.
Is this what I paid for?
I'll lose face in my community!
For the sake of both our families,
please take her.
I apologize on behalf of my entire family.
Please take her Rani... Please.
Our precious daughter.
Beautiful as a flower.
She doesn't know how much she is loved.
Goodbye darling,
you leave us with a heavy heart!
The animals and birds will miss you...
Trees and plants will go dry...
You are the center of our Universe...
Our precious daughter.
Beautiful as a flower.
God Himself watches over you.
Because you are God's favorite too.
Namaste.
Congratulations Gulab!
A small gift for the bride.
When you finish reading these.
I'll give you more.
I live just two lanes away.
Your bride will be smarter than you Gulab!
She'll make more money too!
Put out the candles,
the Earthquake cometh!
It's the Queen of the Dance Company!
She has some guts coming here!
She is Rani's friend from childhood.
Rani!
Congratulations!
Many many congratulations!!
Oh I know...
I've come a bit early.
Huh?
I should have waited till everyone left.
But I was too excited!
And look! I even forgot Gulab's gift!
Ok...
I'll leave.
Don't want to spoil this night for you.
Everything is ruined Ma.
Gulab won't even look at me.
He thinks I did it on purpose.
I thought I'd finally rest easy tonight.
But everything is ruined.
Here, take a sip.
Ma?
Gulab!
My mother said...
She died of shock
from seeing your bald bride.
Rani spent a fortune on your joke-bride.
The oldie died laughing.
Where have you been for the last 2 days?
Are you drunk again?
What's your name?
Janaki.
Take this off.
Why?
What are you doing?
Lie down.
Come here.
Don't do that!
Shhh...
Please!
Bijli?
One second...
Rani?
It's late!
Come in!
What's wrong?
Rani?
Bijli.
Forgive me for the other night.
Are you crazy Rani?
It was my fault!
I shouldn't have come.
I was just so excited!
Look. You're sorry. I'm sorry.
Our sorrys cancel out!
Tell me about the wedding.
How is the groom?
It's Gulab's wedding night.
I forced him to marry her.
I have ruined his life!
No, Rani!
Just watch! In no time...
Janaki will have him
wrapped around her finger.
It's not a big deal!
It's just hair!
Bijli.
How is your hair so beautiful?
Always so perfect?
You're so fair...
But you are the dark horse...
With a wild streak!
Bijli?
Bijli!
Yes?
The boss sent your share.
He said a big client
is coming tomorrow.
Ok.
What is it Raju?
Is there someone with you?
You can play detective tomorrow.
Now good night!
Darling...
Sweet dreams...
Sweetest dreams to you too Bijli.
You're going to work Gulab?
"Such long luscious hair Gulab..."
"You'll be stunned by her beauty!"
There, I'm stunned.
Worry not Mother,
I've performed my husbandly duties.
Finally... The Princess wakes.
This isn't your mother's house.
There.
Chop this.
Do some work.
Cover your head.
You've shamed me enough already.
Not on the floor!
Didn't your mother teach you anything?
They sold me a useless goat.
I squashed her boobs...
Then I slammed into her!
Showed her who's the boss!
Lucky bastard, getting double action.
Got a bride and a whore.
Gulab!
Stop! That's Kishan's stuff!
Bastard! That skirt-fucker!
Challenges the village Elders!
Sisterfucker!
That motherfucker.
Piss on his handicrafts!
What will he sell now?
Hey... grab a stack!
Dick!
Corrupting our women...
Let's show him!
Stop asshole!
My Ma stitched that!
Fucker!
Run!
What's going on?
Fuck you Kishan!
Gulab?
Where have you been?
I came by your house... it was locked.
What happened?
Shahrukh Khan?
Ma?
Ma the dough is ready.
Should I fire the stove?
Yes.
What happened?
Who did this?
Forget it Rani.
Some people don't like progress.
But we will not back down.
We'll continue our work quietly.
Why is everyone in this village
deaf and mute?
Why don't you tell her the truth?
Gulab has gone mad!
Look what he did!
Control your son!
"Twinkle Twinkle Little Star"
"How I wonder-"
Get inside! Now!
Haven't you been told?
Girls who read make bad wives!
Learn to please your husband!
Or he'll dump you and never look back!
Hello?
Not Gulabo! My name is Rani.
Rani Kanwar Jaiswal!
A 32 year old widow,
with a 17 year old son.
My eyes are getting weak! My back hurts!
Want to hear more?
It's been 15 years since
I've been touched by a man.
Tell me Shahrukh Khan...
Where and when do you want to meet?
And then...
His pants tore open...
To unleash his dragon.
But as soon as his dragon got out...
It shrunk into a mouse.
What is this Bijli?
How long can we sit like this?
Its mud from the ocean floor...
It will make you look 16 again.
No mud can bring back my lost years.
What's with the mood Rani?
Did you fight with your mobile lover?
Shahrukh Khan.
Oh! Shahrukh Khan!
Don't frown!
You'll get wrinkles!
Then he won't call you!
No phone. No tring tring.
He won't be calling again.
Ever!
I don't need wrinkles to put him off.
I told him the truth about me.
Off he ran! Tail between his legs.
Lajjo!
Don't keep roaming around!
Go fix me a meal. I'm starving.
You better go.
You'll get the money.
I assure you.
Look... There's his mother.
Gulab is in trouble.
He owes them money.
Pay up now!
I need time to arrange for the rest.
Sir. Could we get an advance?
It's an emergency.
Yes. We'll deliver on time.
I sold my wedding necklace.
I'm still 5000 short.
Don't worry. We'll get the money.
It's done!
Mother dear...
You brought my money?
Where is it?
He owes me for more than a month now!
I run a business after all!
Little motherfucker!
Don't have a dime in your pocket!
Calling mommy to save you?
You want free sex?
Get it from your wife!
Bloody dogs in heat!
Always looking for a quick fuck!
Janaki!
Rani?
Ma's not home. She's gone to the city.
You have completely disgraced us!
I was already in debt from your wedding!
And now this!
It's your fault!
I didn't even want to get married!
Send her back and get a refund.
Anyway she's bloody defective.
You'll trade your wife
for booze and whores?
It's only money, okay!
Light yourself another.
Where is everyone?
Boss has gone to the Village Elders.
To plead our case.
Why?
The village women are asking for a TV.
If that happens Bijli,
we'll be out of business.
What bullshit!
TV can't replace Bijli's thunder.
No Bijli!
Yes Raju!
Bijli No!
Raju Yes!
C'mon, Lajjo.
Can anyone stop you Bijli?
No!
Then go!
Move your stupid sheep!
Rani!
You two look like monkeys!
Hey Elephant Queen!
Ride with us to the zoo!
Come on!
I'll die before I'm seen on that!
You're both insane!
Forget what others say...
Follow your heart Rani!
Bijli's craziness is infectious!
Come be crazy with us!
What will people say?
They'll say "Rani's having fun!"
Hurry or everyone will see!
Janaki's really an innocent.
May she remain so forever.
Don't nag her to have children soon.
But she must bear children!
Without bearing a child...
A woman's life is nothing!
Rani!
You talk such shit sometimes.
A woman has value, even without a child.
We weren't born just to bear children!
Lajjo...
Don't worry.
You can't give up.
Life can't be that unfair.
We have just one life.
We too will find our share of happiness.
Have faith.
Wait a minute!
Maybe he's the problem!
Huh?
Tell Manoj to get himself tested.
What?
What do you mean?
Men can be infertile too!
It's not always a woman's fault.
Get Manoj tested.
Lets see who's barren. Him or you?
Are you saying?
That I could be a mother someday?
Men can be infertile?
Absolutely!
I didn't know that was possible!
How can we test this?
Bijli, do you have a magic potion?
Or...
A doctor, a priest or a healer?
Those frauds can't get you a baby.
Let me think.
I'll figure something.
But first you tell me...
Why do you want a child so badly?
To save your marriage?
What kind of a question is that Bijli?
I want the joy of having a child!
Manoj can beat me all he wants,
but I won't be beaten by fate.
If I can have a child,
I want one.
That motherfucker...
He's hurt you so much.
Motherfucker.
Who invented these cuss words?
I bet it was man.
Why is a woman getting
fucked in every cuss?
Motherfucker! Sisterfucker!
It's time the men got fucked!
Sonfucker!
Bijli!
Unclefucker! Fatherfucker!
Brotherfucker!
Shout it out Rani!
Shout it!
Fatherfucker! Sonfucker!
Sonfucker!
Brotherfucker!!!
What's happening to Rani?
You're sitting on Shahrukh Khan!
See what I mean?
Who needs men...
When a mobile can get us off!
This will free us from men!
Hail the mobile!
Hail the vibrating signal provider!
It's stopped vibrating!
Wait it's happening again!
Hey... It's Gulab.
Hello?
I'm out.
Janaki is with me.
What?
Fix your own dinner.
We'll be home late.
That's right.
Was that Gulab?
Rani...
He's getting out of hand.
You need to control him.
Janaki.
Go wait by the bike.
We're leaving soon.
Go.
It's good you sent her away.
Gulab has gone mad...
Forget about Gulab!
Worry about yourself.
The village women have
complained to the Elders...
That you lure their husbands.
The Elders called your boss.
Right?
They're going to shut down your tent.
Aah!
I get it.
Their husbands come
to me of their own free will...
And that's my fault?
Gulab goes to a whore...
That whore in the city!
And that's my fault?
And Lajjo!
Your husband stays out drunk all night.
That must be my fault too!
I have corrupted your saintly men!
You didn't have to
sell your wedding necklace...
To save your child from pimps!
It is easy for you to talk!
Truth is...
you have never lived our lives!
Try managing a home, family, and children.
It's not child's play!
Gulab isn't a child anymore Rani!
He came to my tent,
with a bundle of cash...
Whore!
Janaki...
Wait.
I slapped Gulab just as hard!
Told him to get lost!
I was there when Gulab was born.
I saw him before Rani did.
Truth is... I am not from Rani's village.
Nor are we childhood friends.
I first met her years ago.
When I dropped
her very drunk husband home.
Shankar was my client.
She was a new bride. Barely 14 or 15.
Just a child.
She thanked me for bringing him home.
Even made me stay for dinner.
I was a child too.
A child with no friends.
We sat up talking till dawn...
I'll never forget that night.
Next year when I returned...
I heard that Shankar had died
in an accident.
Year after year...
I made sure I came back to see Rani.
Today there is nobody in my life...
More dear to me than Rani.
There they are!
Rani... Wait!
Rani... Don't be stubborn.
Where were you all day?
Answer me!
I haven't eaten all day!
You were with Bijli, right?
I'm warning you!
Stop meeting that dirty whore!
You can visit that "dirty whore".
But not me?
Open your booze-addled eyes Gulab.
And look at your wife for once.
Don't hurry to be a man...
Learn to be human first.
Bijli?
Oh. Sorry.
Hey Raju...
Who's taken my stage?
No one.
Tell me! Who's on my stage?
Tell me!
Bijli. The boss is furious!
You took off without a word.
And you keep refusing clients!
He said he'd fire me...
For letting you take the bike.
He said "Gas doesn't come for free!"
Don't spin yarns.
Just tell me who's on my stage?
She's nothing!
Just a filler...
While the crowds wait for you.
How do I look?
Nobody compares to you Bijli.
Go. Work it.
Go make the earth quake!
Go!
Please stop!
Let me shut that mouth of yours!
I want no part in Bijli's crazy plan.
It's such a huge risk.
What if someone finds out?
What if your husband finds out?
How will he?
He'll never find out!
Of course he will.
We won't let him.
These marks of love he leaves on my body...
Should I ignore them?
Accept this as my fate?
Just imagine, what if I'm not barren?
Remember what you said?
"Life can't be that unfair..."
"We too will find
our share of happiness."
I want my share Rani.
Bijli?
Here?
Yes. Here.
Right in the middle of the road.
Duffer chick!
There's a cave behind that hill.
That's where you're going.
Hey Rani... I'll be back soon.
Hello?
Rani Kanwar Jaiswal?
Who is this?
I'm still Shahrukh Khan.
But not the film hero.
Just a 42 year old bachelor
called Shahrukh Khan.
I have a hearty laugh...
And a long mustache.
You want to hear more?
My eyes are sharp but
my joints ache in the winter.
Tell me Rani. Will you meet me?
And please don't say...
"What will people say?"
But what will people say?
Hey. You're sure you want this?
According to my calculations...
This is the right time of the month
for you to conceive.
Yes. I'm sure Bijli.
Remember the lover I told you about?
The one who taught me to dream?
He's the one!
Lajjo...
Don't be afraid.
Go make your village proud!
You know Raju?
I think he's falling in love with me.
Your Raju?
I've noticed how he looks at you.
Everybody falls in love with our Bijli!
Oh sonfuckers!
It's dawn.
Why are you sleeping here?
Did the boss fire you again?
Bijli it's morning!
Where were you the whole night?
I called your mobile also...
Aye Raju.
Do you know?
You're my most favorite.
Quit this shitty life.
And run away!
Go to the city. Get a respectable job.
Then find a nice girl,
and love her like crazy.
He's sitting in the well...
Hiding in the foliage...
He's quiet and shy...
O Tortoise...
Come out and play!
What the hell are you doing?
Beware Bijli!
The boss said I'm the new queen!
O Tortoise...
Come out and play!
You're back?
Pinky is busy. Get lost.
I've brought money asshole!
Get the fuck out!
You're not welcome!
Why don't I call Mommy again?
Get this punk out of here!
Stay out of this Kishan!
Gulab, let me take you home.
Stay away!
Go make your skirts.
I fucking hate you!
I licked him to life...
I slither... I slide...
I shake him... I sway him...
But I can't seem to wake him!
Please rise and shine...
Oh floppy creature of mine...
Tortoise!
O Tortoise!
Come out and play!
Glorious Tortoise of mine...
Rise and shine!
Who is it?
I need some talcum powder.
The boss wants me for a big client.
You must've been quite hot in your time.
Must have been in demand too!
Goodnight Raju.
What was she doing here?
She's a cheeky bitch!
She's perfect for you.
Go be her slave.
Make her your ATM machine.
What are you looking at?
Your eyes.
Your eyes are beautiful.
You're hilarious!
No man ever looks
above Bijli's chest.
And you?
You see my eyes?
Not just your eyes Bijli...
I see all of you.
When you dance on stage...
I feel like...
And when you laugh it's as if...
And when you tease me...
But when you're angry with me...
I piss in my pants!
What are you trying to say?
Nothing... Just...
You should value yourself. That's all.
Hey!
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
You'll get your full payment
before the Dussehra festival.
But no days off after the festival.
We're getting a huge order!
Kunkoo here's your bonus.
Here's my share for the TV.
We just need 2000 more!
Then we're getting TV!
Rani here's your bonus.
The client is pleased with
your and Janaki's work.
One more announcement.
The Handicraft Committee
has awarded Lajjo...
The 'Best Worker' title!
They want to offer you a permanent job.
You'll get a monthly salary...
And a bonus!
Wow Lajjo!
Lord Krishna has blessed our women.
Last year Kunkoo prayed
to Him and got pregnant.
So what if it was a girl.
This year Lajjo has been blessed!
Next year it's Jhumki's turn.
But she needs more than a miracle.
My son refuses to touch her.
He says she's as skinny as a reed.
Does he want someone as flabby as him?
I can't understand these men.
They want everything!
Long hair, doe eyes, voluptuous body.
Rani... Big boobs!
Not everyone has big boobs!
Yes Lajjo, you poor thing.
You have them but still no action!
Rani!
She took a big loan for Gulab's wedding.
Even mortgaged her hut.
I haven't paid interest in 3 months...
If I can't pay up?
I'll have to sell my hut.
Sell your hut. Come live with me.
I want to meet you.
Really? You're asking for trouble.
- I love trouble
- Send me your address.
I'm coming!
Just say when.
I've got to go!
I wouldn't have come back.
If I saw you happy.
My uncle got me a job in the city.
It doesn't work this way.
Lets run away. Start afresh!
Please!
I beg you.
Hey you!
You have some cheek!
How dare you enter my house?
I will hand you to the police!
What are you looking at? Get lost!
Before the village folk
beat you to a pulp!
You'll have the TV
by the Dussehra festival.
Congratulations!
Oh my... Lajjo!
Look at you...
Glowing like a new bride.
You haven't worn this necklace in ages.
It's been passed down for generations.
Grandma wore it on her wedding day.
She passed it to my Ma.
And Ma gave it to my Lajjo...
At our wedding.
And you'll give it to...?
I'm starving.
Serve dinner.
So much food.
Have we won the lottery?
Something like that.
I got a hefty advance from Kishan.
He said...
The Handicrafts Committee loves my work.
I'll be getting a salary every month.
A salary! Plus a bonus!
And there's more news...
I'm two months...
Get me water!
Why don't you chuck it in my face?
Make me look like a good for nothing!
Bloody bitch! Do yourself a favor.
Buy yourself a brain with that bonus!
Bijli...
Has the boss found a client for me?
Voil!
What's this?
Just an advance.
The rest after the job's done.
He's a big catch.
Meet him at the bus stop at 10 o'clock.
You won't need the boss any more!
10 o'clock.
I... Rajesh Rana...
Have mustered up my courage...
And my money...
Let's run away Bijli!
There's nothing for us here.
The boss can't see beyond the new girl.
He doesn't value you!
He's itching to throw you out!
Run away with me.
We'll go to Delhi.
I'll handle the business.
And you'll be my Queen!
I've arranged everything.
Please say yes.
You and I together... We'll rule Delhi!
Just say yes!
I see...
You want to be my pimp.
Great!
Done.
Let's seal the deal!
Right here? In the open?
Come on!
You want it under that tree?
Behind the well?
Or we can go back to my tent!
Come on!
Isn't this too much for a simple fuck?
You could have just paid my daily rate!
What kind of pimp will you be?
Ranaji! Save your festival bonus...
For some other whores!
Why are you doing this?
I did all this for you!
Raju proposed to me.
He asked me to be his Queen.
He wants to be my new pimp.
The boss is right.
I forgot.
I am a whore.
And that's what I'll always be.
I really am the scum of society.
I want a smoke too.
The village gets TV!
What a momentous day!
This has been possible
only because of Kishan.
The entire village thanks you.
God bless you!
Janaki?
Janaki!
Come here!
How dare you steal my money!
What money Ma?
Who did you give it to?
That boy?
Who is he?
Don't you run from me!
I'm struggling to pay back
the loan for your wedding!
You know I mortgaged the house for you!
Still you stole from me?
First Gulab,
God knows what he's up to!
And now his bride...
Steals from her own home.
Rani?
What's wrong?
Is everything alright?
Get in!
Why don't you both just kill me!
Oh come on...
Don't turn us away.
We've done business before.
But the new girl's special.
Fresh on the market.
Her rate is 1000.
No discount.
Fine.
800 and not a penny more.
A trip to the moon for 800.
You get to ride the rocket.
Bijli!
Back off!
He wants the new girl!
I'll find someone for you.
I've had a change of heart.
I choose the rocket ride with Bijli.
I'm coming... I'm coming...
With one full month's advance!
What?
I'll call you back.
Ma can't find her money.
Have you seen it?
Oh so now you can speak also!
You took the money, didn't you?
You took it, didn't you?
You're calling me a thief?
You took the money, didn't you?
What did you say?
Yes! I took the money!
You're calling me a thief?
C'mon! Say it again...
How dare you call me a thief!
Bloody bitch!
Go little rocket!
Go! Go! Go!
Ah! More astronauts!
C'mon! Climb onboard the rocket!
Speed up... 120... 130...
I'll break this bed today!
Adios amigos... I'm going to the moon!
Moooooon!!!
Bitch!
Gulab! Get off her!
This is my house!
Not your brothel!
Don't try to find me! Ever!
You both disgust me!
May you rot in hell!
Now I know why my father
left you for a bloody whore!
I want to see!
How you bitches survive without a man!
It's all my fault.
That boy was at school with me.
He wanted to marry me.
But his parents couldn't afford my dowry.
I cut off my hair.
To stop the wedding.
He rides for hours to see me.
I never called him... Ever!
I didn't steal the money Ma!
Bijli?
Excellent Bijli... Good job!
What a comeback!
They'll be back next week.
Paid an advance for you.
Keep your share.
You beat the new girl!
Good for you!
Put your thumb print here.
After deducting the loan amount,
this is left from the sale of your hut.
Count it.
Where will you go now?
Maybe I'll go see my parents...
I never went back after marriage.
Take it. Take it.
She's smart and loves books.
Enroll her in school.
She's my daughter.
If anything happens to her,
I'll kill you!
I bought you a mobile.
To keep in touch.
Ma.
I will miss you!
I'll come visit you in your new home.
Go on.
God bless you both.
Look, it's that skirtfucker Kishan.
His game needs to end.
The New Village Hero!
Hero soon-to-be zero!
Motherfucker...
Gulab what are you doing?
You're no hero!
Show him! Bastard!
Today is Dussehra,
a most auspicious day...
A day of transformation... And truth.
Today Lord Ram decimated
the Demon King Ravan.
Today is Victory day!
Let's go to the temple tonight.
It's a day of thanks.
And we have much to be grateful for.
If it's a boy...
We'll name him after Lord Ram.
He too will destroy evil.
But to tell you the truth...
I want a daughter.
What are you saying Lajjo?
You're listening?
I'm pregnant.
What?
I'm pregnant!
Finally!
What's wrong?
Isn't this what you wanted?
Tell me, who did you fuck?
Whose sin is in your belly?
No one's!
Who else's would it be?
It's yours!
My child?
You think I'm an idiot?
That you can trick me?
Fucking whore!
Why can't it be yours?
Tell me why it can't be yours?
Hit me all you want...
It won't change a thing...
This child is yours and yours alone!
IT CAN'T BE MINE!
Because you're a whore!
A dirty whore!
I may be a whore...
But I am not barren!
Naobi!
Kishan?
What happened?
He's lying half-dead in the hospital.
We can't live here anymore.
We're leaving!
If fate allows, we'll meet again.
Today we celebrate
the Divine power of the Feminine.
Today Goddess Durga decimated
the great demon Mahisur.
Listen...
Accept this child as your own Manoj.
You've always wanted a child.
This is your chance!
Fine. Go tell the Elders...
Announce to the whole village...
That your wife is a whore!
She slept with another man...
And that's how she got pregnant.
Because you couldn't do it!
Because YOU are the barren one!
Lajjo!... Open the door!
Lajjo!
Let go of her! Bastard!
As Lord Ram's arrow
pierced Ravan's navel...
The Demon King burst into flames!
Lajjo! Help!
Good won over Evil.
Truth defeated Deceit.
Today we cleanse our lives.
Today we rise above our fears.
Today we let the Light enter.
Today we leave darkness behind.
Bijli!
What's wrong?
It's burnt.
I feel like I have to go all the time.
Like there's a well inside me.
Bijli...
I've never seen you like this.
Will you really run away with us?
Leave everything behind?
You've done so much for us.
You have no idea what
you both have done for me.
I've heard many
promises over the years...
But no one came through.
You did. You set Bijli free!
Look Rani.
Your hair is burnt.
Rani's hair is burnt!
Hey Rani...
Imagine... What will people say?
Rani will have to
cut her hair like Janaki.
Quiet! You duffers.
Where should we go?
Mumbai!
Oh no... Not Mumbai!
Why not?
I want my child to have
a childhood like mine.
She'll dance in the fields...
Bathe in the river...
Catch butterflies in the Spring...
And who will earn the money?
Your father?
There are no men now. Just us.
Kishan has shown
us that we can survive!
Skillful sewing...
beats skillful screwing!
Rani your phone's ringing!
It's Shahrukh Khan!
Rani... Answer it.
Ask him...
Should we go left or right?
Rani? Where are you my love?
At a crossroad...
Wondering whether to go left or right.
So what will it be?
From now on...
I'll let my heart decide.