26th November, 2008...Mumbai.
9:54 Pm.
Two unknown men stormed
Chatrapati Terminus..
..and started firing bullets.
For the next three
days and three nights.
...Mumbai was brought
down to its knees.
1O terrorists trained
by Lashkar-e-Taiba.
..e><ecuted the most dreadful
attack on Indian soil and..
..turned the city of
Ivlumbai into a battleground.
By the time this
terror attack was over..
More than 160 people were dead.
Many bodies had torture
marks on them as well.
Seven years later... the
bullet holes have been re-plastered.
The broken windows
have been replaced.
But the wounds inflicted on
our heart and mind is still fresh.
Because,
those who planned the attack,
executed it
and attacked our pride,
are still sleeping peacefully.
Beyond the grasp of India.
Come on!
What's wrong with you, Man!
Oh no!
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
Oh sttt!
Hands up!
In a case of violent road rage.
..a man was thrown off the bridge,
into the icy waters of the river below.
Strangely, police have still
not been able to locate his body.
It's yet to be seen how
that will affect the triaL.
..of the man arrested in
connected with the alleged killing.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Case no: 066F505.
State of Illinois Vs Jude Rosario
Verdict.
When I tell you to stop,
and turn face the table. Stop.
We the jury find the defendant.
Upper lip. Lower lip.
Tongue up.
Guilty!
Turn around.
Here's your Passport. ..
Pan Card...
Voter ID...
And this - new thing...
Aadhar Card.
Cell Phone...
...and money.
I hope you remember everything.
Get in through Chirai...
then take a bus to Lakimpur.
Stay in Lakhimpur for two months.
Then travel to Uri by train.
Once I get there,
I need to switch on this cell phone.
And get rest of my orders.
And..
No falling in love
with an Indian girl.
Bravo, kid. Go on.
Yeah, tell me.
Ivlousa Hamid.
Resident of Quetta, Pakistan.
His mother died when he was eight.
..and his father died
two years later in Afghanistan.
I don't want his family history...
Get to the point.
During the interrogation
he divulged.
..that Lashkar-e-Taiba is
planning another attack on India.
Where?
- He doesn't know.
He does...make him talk.
Sir, we've already
tortured him to the limit.
He would've definitely
told us if he knew.
Sir.
Sir, even if we manage
to avert this attack..
...we won't be able
to stop the next one.
Who is he?
Samit Ivlishra.
New deputation from NTRO...
I told you about him.
Sir, they will attack us again.
They will keep attacking
us again and again.
Until they don't
fulfill their motive.
Because no matter how
many times they attack us.
..we never do anything.
Nothing.
We only stop playing cricket.
Sir, I have an idea...
...and this way we can
stop all the attacks.
We can't do that.
Sir, if America can...
why can't we?
You won't find anyone
in the Government.
..to approve this plan.
But sir...there's no need
to tell anyone in the Government.
Where did you find this crazy guy?
Why not, sir?
Because we're not America.
Roy, do you want
to start another war?
Sir...just one more attack,
and we'll be waging war anyway.
You're sounding like those fools.
..who keep screaming
on Facebook "Let's go to War".
"Let's go to War."
We can't risk millions of lives
in order to avenge a few hundreds.
Sir, please talk to the PM...
This meeting is over.
Take me back to the office.
Whatever is discussed
in this office cannot be repeated...
not to your colleague, not your
father, your wife... not even your dog.
Yes, sir.
Am I clear?
- Yes.
Let's do it.
Sir, this is a suicide mission.
There is no chance of
the team returning alive.
There won't be a team.
Exactly what I was thinking, sir.
Do you have someone in your mind?
We'll have to find some crazy guy,
Isn't it 3 hours yet.
Yes.
Sir...
This is '97 batch.
He lives with his parents.
No, no.
You didn't send me files
of the Northern region.
No! - I sent a request
for army personnel as well.
You didn't send those either.
Won't do. - Please hurry up,
you're taking too long.
Too high-profile.
Will attract unnecessary attention.
L-low many times do I
have to remind you'? - No!
Send me those classified
files as soon as possible.
Satyajit Bagga.
BSF Officers.
- I should get everything by tomorrow.
Won't do.
- I've these 3-4 options.
He's too old!
It's been too long.
Did we come too far?
It's somewhere around here.
Address does not exist.
You've left all the pages blank.
What do I do with these?
You're not doing your job,
please pay attention.
Too old, won't do.
Sir, he has no passport, no
driving license... no ration card.
He isn't even on Facebook...
or Twitter.
Sir, on paper he doesn't exist.
Just like Phantom.
Who is he?
Sir, Phantom?
Him?
Sir, there's one piece of
news about him on the internet.
It's quite old,
and without a photograph.
Sir...e><cept for this small problem,
he's the perfect man.
Small problem?
This is a big problem.
But, sir...this is what makes
him our perfect candidate.
Trust me, this is our man.
Daniyal Khan!
But, sir, he refused.
What do you mean he refused?
I didn't send you two so far so that he
says no and you two come running back.
Okay, sir, we'll try again.
We'll pay any amount you want.
What will I do with your money?
I would already be dead.
And I've no interest in being
the richest man in the cemetery.
Please don't waste your time.
I don't want your money.
What about honor?
You were dishonorably discharged
from the Army, Daniyal.
We're giving you a chance
to earn the honor you lost.
Sir, he clearly refused.
What did he say?
So what now, sir?
- Fine, lam coming.
Okay, sir.
Whose foolish idea is this?
If I say...give me 1O illiterate,
street kids.
..and I can create havoc in one
of the biggest cities in the world.
You would've
called that foolish too.
Right?
You certainly would, sir,
But they did it.
And if those 1O illiterate
boys can do it, then why can't we?
They were ignorant, I am not!
Your father, Col. Usmaan Khan.
L-low long has it been
since you two last talked'?
Imagine how happy he'll be
to see you in the Indian Army again.
If you do this job, I promise..
...you'll be honorably re-appointed
on the same post in the Army.
"Your shoulder sways,
My chest sways,"
" l-low will these broken hearted,
Carry the burden of my faith?"
"My infidelity sways,
My loyalty sways."
" Your slave sways"
"My lord sways"
"l have smiled And broken myself into
a million pieces, For you my lord."
"I have scrubbed,
And coloured myself, In your hue."
Hello.
Hello, papa.
"You are in the stars, In the earth,
In every direction, My lord."
"I surrender, My conscience,
I come home to you."
They will keep killing our people.
And the day isn't far..
..when both our
countries will go to war.
What you're trying to do,
will certainly lead to a war.
It won't.
If their deaths look like accident.
They are not fools.
They will soon know
that we're behind this.
I want them to know
But they won't have
any proof to accuse us.
For the world, it will be accidents.
Look, Daniyal, we're not
attacking the people of Pakistan.
We just want to
finish the terrorists.
In the last 10 years, more than
50,000 Pakistanis have also died..
..in this kind of violence.
We must avenge 26111.
And once Lashkar knows
the consequences of attacking us.
They will think twice
before attacking us again.
But why me?
I'll be honest with you, Daniyal.
For you world you've vanished.
And if you go somewhere for
2-3 months, no one will notice.
And if I don't return, it won't
make a difference to anyone, right?
We both know this
is a difficult job.
And you won't get a medal for this..
..nor will your picture
appear on the front page.
Because no one will
know what you did.
Because this mission never existed.
Passport...
Tickets...
Cell-phone.
Call only from this phone.
This call will get re-routed from
a third country and then come to us.
Actually, don't call us at all.
Because we don't know you.
Cash...
Cards...
Locker key.
And a ticket for tomorrow's match.
Navvaz will meet you there.
There are 30,000 people here.
If he's here,
we've only 2 days to find him.
Are you Navvaz?
10% seats are in the smoking area.
And he's a chain smoker.
So chances are he'll be here.
Why do you want to identify him?
RAWs making a new fi
e..
...of the people involved
in Mumbai attacks.
And as you Know, there's
just one existing photo of this guy.
And that too is very old.
ls that him?
No!
Do you recognize him properly?
- No one does.
I saw him just once.
And after that he underwent
plastic surgery.
So who are we looking for?
Don't worry.
According to the
Intelligence reports.
..his face hasn't changed much.
Wait!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
What happened?
- He must be somewhere around?
He always breaks the filter
of his cigarette before smoking it.
What are you doing?
Can you get off the ground please?
There must be similar
filters in his vacuum cleaner.
What...
I just saw one.
- Guys, I've got a job to do.
What...
What do you do in London?
Can we stick to business?
I am a security consultant,
for Dark Water.
It's a private company.
..that provides supplies, security and
weapon's training in high risk zones.
To whom?
Those who can afford us.
What's your connection with RAW?
Why are you helping me?
10,000 Pounds.
I identify him,
I get the money.
10,000 Pounds?
You can buy me a drink then.
I think that's him.
You look that way.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Hello. Hello.
This is a trial for our people.
I'm deeply grateful for your help.
It's him.
But you didn't get
a good look at him yet.
But...his voice.
His style of greeting...
it's exactly the same.
'Only one of our agent's
has seen this man.'
'Nawaz Mistry.'
'Back then she was working
for Medicine International.
'75,000 people died and
millions were injured..'
'..in the 2005 earthquake
in Pakistan Occupied Kashmir.'
'Many medical-aid workers from all
over the world were going there..'
'..because Pakistan government
were issuing immediate visas.'
'Nawaz was there too.'
'This is the only photo we have.'
'.which was on his
visa application form..'
'..when he came to India
posing as a cricket fan'.
'But after that he changed
his face... Plastic surgery.'
We'll need to confirm it's him.
Okay, you follow him.
If he comes back, call me.
Where are you going?
- I've to be sure it's him.
But.
Sajid Mir.
Lashkaﬁs top military trainer.
Sajicl lvlajid,
Sajicl Bill, Uncle Bill, Abu Bara.
..they are all his aliases.
He's got 26 passports.
He trained all the terrorists
of the 26/11 attack.
Planned all the operations.
And also gave instructions
to the terrorists from Karachi...
...while watching everything
on our news channels.
"Make him stand on the
other side of the door."
"The bullet should
pierce his head."
"Now shoot."
"Just do as I say."
What happened?
- He's coming back.
Did you figure out if it is him?
Hello?
No!
You'll have to get
closer and confirm.
Are you crazy?
I 'm saying I am pretty sure.
Are you 100% sure?
- Yes, almost.
We're not paying you 10,000
Pounds to be "Almost Sure".
I need you to be a 100% sure,
What do you want to do?
- Ask him for a lighter.
You can see his face closer.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Can I have a light?
Thanks.
Yes.
- That man and kid.
Who are you talking about?
They just stepped out
of the green Volkswagen.
What are you talking about?
They just went inside
the building with Mir.
Get them out. Now!
Vvhy?
- Their lives are in danger.
Get the old man and
his daughter out now.
Excuse me...sir?
ls that green Volkswagen yours?
Yes. Why?
The car's alarm just went off.
Alarm?
Come quickly.
Where are they?
What the hell is happening?
- Where are those tvvo?
They must be on their way down.
What they hell was that?
Your plan was always to kill him.
You knew he was Sajid as soon as
he entered his apartment.
So why did you tell
me to ask him for a light?
When a chain-smoker
sees someone smoking.
..he feels the urge to
smoke a cigarette himself.
And I wanted him to enter
his apartment with a lit cigarette.
My job was to identify him.
Why did you involve
me in his murder?
Murder?
Do you know how many
people he has Killed'?
We've been looking
for him since 6 years.
I had just one chance to kill him,
and I couldn't lose it..
..no matter what the cost.
Not at my cost.
This is not the way I work!
Sir!
The massive explosion that ripped
through the apartment block behind me..
...reportedly killed two people.
London Police say that the
explosion was caused by a gas leak.
According to the local counselor,
one of the men.
..was a Pakistani businessman
called Abid Ansari.
Other unconfirmed sources
say...he was also called Abu Bars.
Residents of this area
are shocked by this incident.
Some of the people we spoke
with say that Mr. AnsarL.
..was rarely ever seen by them.
Case no: 066F505.
State of Illinois Vs Jude Rosario.
We the jury find the defendant
guilty of second degree murder..
..of Mathew Brody.
David Coleman Headley.
Lashkaﬁs most important man...
...responsible for planning
the attacks on Mumbai.
Mother's American
and Father's Pakistani.
Birth name. . . Davvood Gilani.
But in 2006 he changed his
name to David Coleman Headley.
And made a new American Passport.
Because of this western name.
..it was easier for
him to come to India.
He understands
Hindi/Urdu really well.
But he told people
that he's an American.
Headley searched for
the targets in India.
Gathered GPS coordinates...
and made contacts.
After each trip,
he travelled to Pakistan.
..and showed his videos to Lashkar.
Places where the terrorists
could get in easily.
..attack and return when required.
In 2009 Headley was
apprehended at Chicago airport.
But America refused
to hand him over to India.
Now he's serving a 35
year sentence in Chicago jail.
Hello.
That guard told me
that... you're also an Indian.
.J ivesh.
L-low did you get here'?
I mean...what did you do?
Murder.
You know who he is, right?
Bloody rascal.
Scoundrel!
I feel like...
...ripping out his heart.
Finish your breakfast quickly.
They'll be allotting us
our entire week's duty today.
L-low much do they
pay for working here'?
Depends on the job.
What do they pay for the most?
All clear.
All clear!
Lights out!
Next.
L-low much for the
Mp3 player and battery?
9O Dollars.
Next.
You Indian?
Yeah.
What are you in for?
Murder?
All clear!
He's got cat-like eyes.
Every time I see him,
it makes my blood
pressure soar...with anger.
Thank God...they're
taking him away.
..othervvise I would've done
the same thing you did... Murder
Where are they taking him?
Texas. . . high security prison.
Hello.
- Hey, baby.
Jude speaking.
- Who is this?
The other day I couldn't
say goodbye after the cricket match.
So sorry.
I can't reach my landline from here.
You know...how difficult it is.
And I have no friends either,
so I thought I'd call you.
What do you want?
- I want 100 Dollars.
Now. Please.
Can you make an online payment?
Note down the website address.
J pa! com,
Location; Illinois, Chicago.
ID NO; 24686.
Hello.
I don't have any money.
%‘w,(
Come on.
24686...you got a money transfer.
For me?
Yeah! 200 Dollars.
Sign here.
Family sent you money?
Great.
Thank you.
Inmates, step out.
Arms up.
Back to the wall.
Did you purchase
this in the Commissary?
Yes.
Where's the receipt?
"What's the plan?"
"Succinylcholine."
“Sued. . . What?“
"A quick acting, de-polarizing
paralytic muscle relaxant."
"It's a perfect poison."
"It leaves no trace,
and even a small dose is enough."
"No need to swallow it either."
"it starts acting as soon as it
comes in contact with the tounge."
"Mossad used this to assassinate
Mehmoocl Al Mamooh in Dubai."
"They caught him on CCTV camera."
"notherwwise no one would've
ever known how he died."
All the muscles of the body
lockup within a minute.
You can't breathe
for almost 5 minutes.
Without oxygen, a man dies.
All clear.
Guys!
Headley's dead!
Heart attack.
According to our sources,
David Headley died yesterday.
..in Chicago prison.
The Chicago Police haven't
issued any official statement yet.
86...
You have a visitor.
I've good news.
They found Mathew Brody.
They found him!
He swam out of the river
before the rescue team arrived.
So now what?
You're a free man.
We'll get you out
of here by tomorrow.
Hello, Pakistan High
Commission, London.
L-low may I help you'?
My name's Daniyal Khan.
I would like to speak
to the High Commissioner.
May I know what this is about?
I've information about
Sajid Mir's death.
This is High Commissioner
Sheriyar Baig.
Sajid Mir's death
wasn't an accident.
He was assassinated by RAW.
I wanted to thank you.
I don't need your thanks.
I just need to know what
the hell you got me into.
What do you want?
I want to avenge my dishonorable
discharge from the Indian Army.
Why are you telling me all this?
I want to meet Lashkaﬁs
leader in Pakistan.
If you tell them that
India assassinated Sajid Mir..
..then what's the point of setting
everything up to look like an accident?
He'll show your
evidence to the vvor
d..
..and make a case against India.
For the last 6 years Pakistan
has been telling the world.
..that there's no
such man as Sajid Mir.
L-low can you Kill someone
who doesn't exist'?
And what did the
High Commissioner say?
Bloody fool!
You think I am Lashkaﬁs servant.
I am the High
Commissioner of Pakistan.
..not a representative of Lashkar.
Don't ever call back again.
Why did you quit RAW?
What is the point
of this conversation?
I have to go.
Where are you going?
- Beirut.
Why Beirut?
You ask too many questions.
Usually we charge
for such information,
VVell...l can pay for your coffee.
We're providing security and materials
to the Syrian refugee camps.
Syria?
Even Lashkaﬁs fighters
are involved in that battle.
That's too much information
for a cup of coffee.
Good luck.
Hello, Pakistan High Commission,
how may I help you'?
This is Daniyal Khan speaking.
- Okay. Please hold.
Sir, it's that Daniyal
Khan calling again.
Tell him I am not here.
Sorry, sir, the High Commissioner
is not here at the moment.
Thank you.
Do you know when?
Hello.
- Daniyal Khan.
Yes. - What do you
know about Sajid Mir.
Sajicfs death wasn't an accident.
He was assassinated.
L-low do you know Sajid Mir's dead'?
Fine, then Abid Ansari...or
Sajid Majid, or Abu Bara.
One of them is definitely dead.
I've proof that the
man who died in that room..
..usecl all these aliases.
Do you want to see?
Why are you calling us from London?
Either you're a fool...
or you think I am one.
Why would an ex-lndian Army
officer contact you from India.
Give us your number.
- No, I will contact you.
Give me your number.
Write it down.
What do you think, Firoz?
Sir, I don't believe
this man at all.
But how did he Know..
..that the person who died
in the gas explosion was Sajid Mir?
What proof can he have?
I think this is some
kind of a trick, Haider sir.
But if he's telling the truth,
he can be really useful to us.
Find out more about him.
What do you want from us?
I want to come to Pakistan.
..and meet Lashkaﬁs chief
Haaris Saaed or Sabauddin Umavi.
You can't come to Pakistan.
We have agents in London.
Go see them and
show them your proof.
I don't want to meet your agents.
...I want to meet
the leader of Lashkar.
Can you come to Afghanistan?
- No.
There are too many Indian agents.
They can spot me.
Then there's nothing we can do.
There is one place.
Syria.
Lashkaﬁs men are
stationed there too.
Call back in five minutes.
Sir, Syria?
- That's the right place.
That place is filled with
Lashkar's people as well as ours.
If he's telling the truth,
we'll bring him to Pakistan.
If he's lying,
he'll be another dead body.
No one will notice in Syria.
Get to Syria.
If you're smart, you can
rendezvous with Lashkaﬁs people.
But.
Hello.
What?
I need to get to Syria.
Are you crazy?
It's a vvarzone.
I want to meet with
Lashkaﬁs people.
Then go.
Every self styled Jihadi is going
to Syria to fight.
You can join them too.
No one's asking for
a visa or passport.
But only you know where
I can find Lashkaﬁs people.
If I try to find them myself,
it will take longer.
I don't have time.
Daniyal, I don't know
where Lashkaﬁs people are.
We're just providing refugee camps...
- Come on, Nawaz.
We all know what Dark
Water does in reality.
Refugee camps are just a front.
America supplies weapons to Jihadis
in Syria through Dark Water.
And Lashkar is part
of those rebel forces too.
So you must know where they are.
Why do you always trouble me?
Hello.
Seems like ISI has already
informed Lashkar about you.
Thank you.
Hello.
We know you're a RAW agent.
I am not a RAW agent.
He hasn't spoken yet, Qureshi sir.
This is what he gave us.
Where did you get these?
I have my sources.
If I can get these,
then imagine what else I can get.
Where did you get them?
I just need a opportunity
to avenge my humiliation.
Military facilities...
Air bases.
I have all the inside information.
All the signal towers
are down due to the war.
It's difficult to get a network.
Fine...I'll send this
once I get to Salayicldin.
If you don't take me to Pakistan.
...believe me,
you will always regret it.
Our chiefs in Pakistan will decide.
..if we will regret this or you.
Keep him here until
I don't speak with them.
Sir.
Alam!
Follow them and let me
know where they are going.
Seems like the battle
has started again.
8*“! Let's do this fast.
Hello.
Qureshi sir, what do we do with him?
Get out of there quickly.
Yes, sir.
We're out.
No, sir...it's difficult
to get out that way.
I'll bring him to Salayiddin.
What have you done?
Daniyal,
government forces are advancing.
My plan was working fine!
You ruined everything.
If..
Somethings wrong.
Let's get out of this area quickly.
Come on...move.
Q Kay-
He's close-by, Take left.
If we don't find that guy,
I'm dead.
And if the Syrian army catches us.
..they will shoot us
thinking we're rebels.
Then we're all dead.
Take a right.
Hello.
Why haven't you sent the video yet?
S**** Syrian Arm y.
Hang on!
Sir, all the signals
in this area are down.
I am trying,
but the video isn't going through.
Come on.
There he is.
Let's go.
Hello...
What's going on?
Someone's firing on us, sir?
- Who’?
I don't know...it's hard to say.
Send his video quickly.
Sir, the signals really bad...
I am not being able to send it.
Get up!
Sending it now.
Daniyau
Find out who is Daniyal Khan.
We'll have to show these rascals...
that we can play this game too.
Rajan Sampat died
in a gas explosion.
Exactly like the way Sajid Mir died.
This can't be a coincidence.
They know, sir.
Sir, it's all because
of what went down in Syria.
Savavav!
"Is there a connection
between these two deaths?"
"I\/Ir. Singh?"
"There's a very clear connection."
"Gas explosion for a gas explosion."
"Rajah Sampafs death
is revenge Killing."
"You mean to say that
the Indian Government."
"..is behind the assassination
of the ISI agent."
Roy. .-
...did your people kill Sajid Mir?
No, sir.
There's no question
of our men being involved.
Sir, we don't have
permission to do all this.
Of course you don't, Roy.
And don't you forget that.
- Sir!
Sir!
The man you killed in Syria
was not on our list, Daniyal.
Sir, I already told you.
Things got out of control.
I didn't have any other choice.
That was a stupid mistake.
Now they know everything about you.
Before things get out of hand,
I want you to come back.
Sir, he couldn't
send the video.
They just heard my name.
We can still..
- It's over, Daniyal.
The media is talking.
The Government is
getting suspicious.
We will be in serious trouble.
But, sir...
- The mission is over.
Come back, right now.
So that's it.
The main terrorists in Pakistan.
..who were responsible for Ivlumbai
attacks will never face trial.
Everything you did
until now will be a waste.
It'll mean nothing.
If you were planning to run
away at the first sight of trouble..
..then why say yes..
- I am not running away, Nawaz!
lam not running away!
There was a young
soldier in the army,
Dilavvar Singh.
Every morning he would
salute me enthusiastically.
With respect. .
With passion.
Do you know why I agreed to
do this mission?
Because I want to see the same respect
in Dilavvar Singh's eyes for me.
I want him to salute me again.
With the same enthusiasm.
The same passion.
What happened?
In the Doda Sector, we were
trying to save our Winter post.
Amidst continuous shelling
for almost 72 hours.
Radio.
- Radio is down, sir.
Alpha...
Sir...
- Alpha Tiger 1 2 3...
if the reinforcements
don't arrive soon..
..we won't be able to
hold them off for too long.
We're just four
hours away from them.
Prepare two soldiers.
Sir..
I'll go, sir.
'None of them were
in any condition to walk.'
'No one had slept or
eaten since three days.'
'I left my men in the bunker,
and decided to go alone.'
‘When they found me,
I was far away from my bunker.‘
'All my men in the
bunker were dead.'
'I was discharged from the army.'
'For deserting my post and my men.'
Daniyal, I can take us to Pakistan.
Us?
Us!
Madam, please.
This way please.
Hello.
Look into the camera.
Arif Ivlirza.
- Yes.
What is the purpose of your visit?
I work with Medicine International.
It's good to have you back in
Medicine International Nawaz.
Thank you so much.
This is my friend,
Arif iviirza from South Africa.
He's done extensive work with
NGOs in Namibia and South Africa.
Can I see your ID card please?
L-low long are you planning to stay'?
1O days.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
This way please.
Firoz.
- Sir.
Why is it taking so long
to gather information about one man?
There's very little information
available on Daniyal Khan, sir.
It's been two weeks, and you..
- Sir.
It's true that he
was court-martialed.
There are reports on the internet.
Other than that we know that
his father is a retired Colonel.
His parents live alone in Devlali.
304 & 305!
Have a pleasant stay, sir.
Thank you.
Call the US Embassy.
I want files on every inmate.
..that was in prison
when Headley died.
And...ask one of our men..
..to pay a visit to
Daniyal Khan's parents.
I clearly said no.
Yes, sir.
But he still went to Pakistan.
Sir, now that he's there..
..we should help him.
That's what I think.
Who's our trusted contact in Lahore?
Sir, Khalid. He runs a small eatery in
lvlohalla Johar for the past three years.
To keep an eye on
Haaris Saeecfs movements.
Ask Vinay from the consulate
to contact Daniyal.
Yes.
Vishal Singh,
voter ID registration officer.
I need to confirm some
details for the voter ID.
L-low many members in your family.
Me, my husband...and my son.
Can I see a photo
of your husband and son?
Photo?
Just to check.
Elections are around the corner.
We've had many cases
of fake voter cards.
Department's orders...
that's why we're insisting.
Checking photos...etcetera.
Daniyal Khan.
Can I see his photo?
I don't have a recent one,
it's a bit old.
Will do.
Fine.
We've found his picture, sir.
But he says it's a bit old.
Call the US Embassy...immediately.
I will pay back
every penny...l swear.
You hardly earn 2000 a month.
L-low do you plan to repay 100,000'?
- I really love Aasia.
Once we get married,
my luck will change as well.
Normally the bride's
parents pay for the wedding.
She belongs to a poor family.
They can't afford to throw
a feast for the entire community.
And you're a king
of some sort, right?
So you won't help me?
- No.
Where are you going?
Who will arrange these?
Make this fatso do it,
all he does is sit and eat.
Yes, mister.
One tea...tvvo fritters.
- Hurry up.
And...the guys were all
praises about your sweet-lumps.
Yes, but its only
available in the evening.
That's his home.
Lashkar-e-Taiba's supreme leader.
L-I aaris Saeed.
His name's on every Most
Wanted list in the world.
But he roams freely
without any fear.
He's protected by Lashkaﬁs
people armed with Kalashnikovs.
..and the police too.
And of course, the ISI.
The American Government
has announced a reward.
..of 1O million dollars on his head.
But everyone knows where he lives.
He's also on Twitter.
And Umavi,
is he really in Rawalpindi Jail.
Mister, I would rather
call it a hotel.
Since the time he's been there,
he's fathered two children.
Even the Pakistan government
have to show the Americans.
..that we're serious
about suppressing Lashkar,
So they sent him
to prison for namesake.
Move it aside.
Haaris Saeed is holding
a huge rally in 5 days.
Daniyal.
Even if we get our hands on one,
it'll be impossible get the other.
The entire Pakistani police
and army will be out looking for us.
Unless...
India wants to destroy Pakistan's.
..peace and serenity completely.
And these conspiracies
have weakened Pakistan.
And today those people sitting
in Delhi are saying.
..that they've put
a price on my head.
Jihad isn't about kill him or
him...or about killing every infidel.
Whoever points their
weapons at us...
Tries to jeopardize our freedom...
Tries to harm our country...
The air of terrorism
that's building up..
But no...
It's just 100,000, brother.
I swear I'll never
ask for anything else.
Why should I lend you 100,000?
Marriage is a one-time affair,
brother.
Friends, relatives. . .the community.
And 100,000 isn't too much.
Food. ..drinks. ..decoration. ..
tables, chairs...
Photos. . . lightings. ..stereo!
It all adds up to this amount.
I swear.
When are you getting married?
As soon as he lends me the money.
Mom's come down too...
from my hometown, all decked.
She's waiting to see
my wedding procession.
For the moment when her prince's
wedding procession comes home.
I swear...
You can swear all you want.
I won't lend you a penny.
Those Ivlujahiddin were
much better than him.
They were recruiting
me at the training camps.
..for 3000 a month.
They were also giving automatic
guns and boots to wear.
And they would've sacrificed
your life by now too.
So what?
I would've gone to Heaven.
It would've been
better than your shop.
So you're eager to go to Heaven,
are you?
Umavi has an old back problem.
Every week a doctor from Lahore.
..goes to the jail
to give him an injection.
When is the doctor visiting next?
He goes every Friday.
Which means his ne><t
visifs on the 14th.
One day before the rally.
Can we approach the doctor?
- Don't even think about it.
He's been with him for 2O years.
His loyalty lies with Lashkar.
You cannot break him.
Not with force nor money.
But yes...the doctor
has an old nurse.
Amina Bi.
Sir! Sir! Sir!
The Americans have sent
the Chicago inmate files.
Great. I want printouts
of every file.
Greetings, mister.
- Greetings.
There was a function at school.
I need to rent some stuff.
What will you need?
VVell...l need one of those
big mikes used in functions.
You mean these?
- Yes, that.
Haaris Saeecfs rally is on the 15th.
And the doctor will be
visiting Umavi on the 14th.
Even if both our plans succeed..
..we can't kill both
of them at the same time.
It's just not possible.
It's possible.
If Umavi's doctor visits
him on the 15th instead of the 14th.
And how will that happen'?
Khalid was telling me about
a nurse at that doctor's clinic.
Your notion was right.
The equipment for the rally.
..is being supplied by Rasheed.
- Good.
Listen, I need to speak
to you about Shehzacfs marriage.
Shehzacfs marriage?
We'll take your
plaster off in a week.
The doctor's leaving in 1O minutes.
And he's asking for Hamid
Adam's medicines, immediately.
Khalid was talking about him.
Her husband passed away
one year after their marriage.
She had only one son. Arshad.
Amina Bi raised him alone.
He became a suicide
bomber for Lashkar.
Khalid was saying,
after Arshacfs death.
..few of Lashkaﬁs leaders
came to her...to show sympathy.
And to give her the money..
..vvhich is normally given
to the family of suicide bombers.
Amina Bi refused to take the money.
He never listens.
In fact, she didn't let
them set foot in the house.
What do you mean isn't not there?
Didn't you ask him?
I got up at 4:30..
And now you expect me to..
I'm getting you married in 2 days.
Are you listening?
I'm getting you married.
I don't like such sick jokes.
It's true.
Here.
This is 50,000.
And I'm giving you 300,000
instead of 100,000.
Let there be a grand wedding.
I'll give you the rest tomorrow.
Take it. It's yours.
Mine?
Stop staring. It's yours.
Thank you, brother. Thank you.
I will never forget this favor.
I will return every penny.
Let go...or I'll
cancel your wedding.
I'll go tell my mom.
Now you see how Prince Shehzad
will get married.
Greetings.
My name's Nawaz Ivlistry.
I work for Medicine International.
We're running a medical
relief camp out here.
But we're short on volunteers...
especially medical staff.
Are you Pakistani?
- Yes.
Your accent is different.
I'm a Parsi.
My family's in South
Africa...since decades.
But we've worked
many years in Pakistan.
We need experienced people like you.
Would you like to
work at this clinic?
Any amount of time
that you can share?
No.
I heard about your son.
We get many blast
victims of Arshacfs age.
You lost your son.
You can understand their pain.
I think you should leave.
Please visit the camp once.
See the condition they are in.
We really need your help.
The rest is up to you,
whether you want to help us or not.
Good bye!
L-low many files, Firoz'?
Sir, I've scanned
through half of it.
And finish the rest
by tomorrow night.
4 mikes,
2 speakers and disco lights.
For a wedding.
When is the wedding?
- Day after tomorrow.
Day after tomorrow?
And you're giving the order so soon?
Are you running away with the girl?
I'm joking.
14th isn't possible.
There's a rally on the 15th.
Look, l'll send back all the stuff
clay after tomorrow night itself.
Safe and sound.
That's alright,
but this is impossible.
After all, it's Mr. Sheikws rally.
Where else can I go now?
That's your problem.
Look...
'
pay you
the money in advance.
Cash.
Huh!
And you can keep your share too.
What do you want?
I'll go take a look.
Two children.
3 year old girl and 7 month old boy.
She had gone to buy toys
for them from jumma market.
He's just 16 years old.
Lost both his legs at the
blast outside the big mosque.
I didn't know anything.
I had no clue...
when he set out on this path.
If only I Knew...l would've
never let him do it.
I would've put him
on a muzzle, but.
I would've never allowed
him to spread such terror.
Sit down.
"It's the Call Of Allah."
"You'll be sent to Heaven."
"A martyﬁs face glows with grace."
This is what they told
him and took him along.
But he returned in plastic bags.
Poor boy...didn't even have a face.
They had slaughtered my son.
And to make sure that Arshacfs
coffin doesn't seem light.
..they put stones
along with pieces of my child.
No mother should face what you did.
Those who separate children
from their mothers.
..and turn them into murderers...
...should be sent to hell.
Don't you want the people.
..who took your Arshad
from you to pay?
Who are you?
We need your help.
What help?
We need your help in saving these
kids from turning into murderers.
Get out.
You can save many more lives.
I said get out.
You know the pain
of losing your son.
Think about the thousands
of mothers like you.
Get out now.
Aunty, is everything fine?
Open the door.
What?
"My infidelity sways,"
"My loyalty sways."
"Your slave sways,"
"My lord sways."
"The first and last letters"
"Of revelation sway,"
"Heaven and earth sway,"
"The skies swoon and sway."
"I won't be able to tell my truth,"
"You won't be able
to bear my truth,"
"My Lord."
"Let me just keep giving my life,"
"In your name,"
"My lord."
Out of these 2000 inmates.
..275 came after Headley.
And 115 of them are still in.
So around 160 of them arrived
in jail after Head
ey..
..and were released after his death.
Give me details of these 160 files.
When is the doctor visiting Umavi?
Tomorrow.
Can you do something.
..to make him go day
after instead of tomorrow.
Jude Rosario.
He was imprisoned few
days Before Head
ey's killing.
..for the murder of some
stuntman called Mathew Brody.
But few days after l-leadleg/'s
I<illing...Mathew Brody was found alive.
Since there was no murder case,
Jude Rosario was released.
Yes...
Yes, coming.
Give it.
Thank you.
Hello, doctor.
- Hello.
How's everything.
- It's the grace of Allah.
Check his bag properly.
- Take a good look.
Same old things that
I bring every week.
Agreed, doctor.
But it's our duty,
we have to do it.
Of course..
Hold on.
What's wrong, doctor?
Hello. - Amina Bi,
you packed the wrong injections.
I apologies, doctor.
I don't know how.. - I wonder
what's gotten into you these days.
I apologies, doctor.
It won't happen again.
I'll have to come back tomorrow.
Last time...
do you know who this man is?
I told you...
I don't know him.
No...
Now...do you recognize this man?
Sir, according to
our agent in Chicago.
..Jude Rosario paid a
fat amount to Mathew Brody..
..for falling off the bridge.
It was a fake case all along.
It means this man Jude Rosario
went to prison intentionally.
The stuffs here.
Setup two mikes and
speakers on the stage.
..and give me the rest of it.
Bring me Daniyal Khan's photo.
"My heart's been murdered."
"Your gaze is a killer."
"A lovely damsel."
"A glowing beauty."
...has been fixed with Razia Abicl
Ali for a compensation of 5000 coins.
Do you accept?
I accept.
"Like the Aghan delicacy."
Do you accept?
I accept.
"Oh wow!"
"Are you going to love me...
at gunpoint."
"Or will you ever
show your face too.
"Oh wow!"
Sir.
It's him...bloody..
Daniyal Khan is Jude Rosario.
"Like the Aghan delicacy."
"A treacherous lover."
"Your lover's mortally wounded."
"oh wow!
I want pictures of every person..
..who entered Pakistan
after Qureshi's murder.
Sir.
Contact every big and small
airports... every entry point.
Hello.
Yes.
- What?
Khalid. It's ready.
I'll check right away.
Don't worry, sir.
I'll check all the photos right now.
I'll check, sir.
"I am a decent guy,
my faith's in Allah."
"But after I played this game,
I am good for nothing now."
"I recited a sonnet of Mir."
"And took a sip of liquor."
"And now my name's tainted."
"O Sweetheart."
"O beautiful girl."
"You're an arrow."
"And my heart's the target."
"She'll fear God
if not her devotees."
"Keep your promises."
"O wow!"
"I'll go and complain
about You to God."
The second one's ready as well.
I'll use this to make a trigger.
This is a toy car remote.
Will it work’?
A similar remote was
used in the Boston bombing.
"I'll complain about you."
"I'll trap your finger in the ring."
What's the range of the remote?
I've installed the battery.
So by tomorrow...it'll work
within a range of 50-60 feet.
And as the battery weakens.
The closer you're to the mike,
the better.
"Don't use your killer
attitude on me."
"Oh wow!
"You'll do more damage
than good to me."
"Will you ever make up
for my loses?"
"Oh wow!
One more thing.
There shouldn't be anything
between the mike and the remote.
Or it won't get the signal.
"Oh wow!
"Are you going to love me...
at gunpoint."
"Or will you ever
show me your face too.
"Oh wow!"
Lahore airport has sent
images only till the 8th.
The one before this.
The injections are in this.
Your new passport.
I'll call you at 10am.
You'll be on a flight
before anyone finds out.
Take care.
Testing.
Testing. Testing.
Zubaid, is all okay.
This one isn't working.
Testing. Testing.
- Open the mike.
Where are the images
from 9th and 10th?
Stop. Stop-
For God sake send them.
Wait.
It's in the wrong socket.
Check now.
Testing. Testing.
It's working.
Working...
Check the rest.
Is it 5'?
When I was a kid,
we used to live in Colaba.
My father, Nauzun Ivlistry.
He was a middle-class man.
Insurance agent.
But Nadia and l..
Nadia, my sister.
He would fulfill all our wishes.
He called us his princesses.
My little princesses.
When we got good grades,
or won a medal in sports.
..or if we simply hugged him.
Father would take
us out for a treat.
There.
At the Tag.
We would all dress up nicely
and go to the Taj tea room.
Drink tea...along with
chocolate pastries.
Then we grew up...
and it felt awkward.
..to go outwith papa for pastries.
It just wasn't cool anymore.
Papa realized this.
And gradually...our tea
parties at the Taj stopped.
That day...
When they attacked the Ta}. ....
...set it on fire.
It felt like someone was settling
my childhood memories ablaze.
They think they will go to Heaven.
These rascals won't even
get a place in hell.
When we get out of here,
do you know what's the first thing
we should do?
Go to the Ta} and have a cup o? tea.
With chocolate pastries.
"Why didn't we meet earlier?"
"Why did we burn alone?"
"Together...we're complete."
"Or were we better alone?"
"My beloved."
Shehzad.
- Brother.
Take this money and leave right now.
Now.
Go away.
Why? And this money.
It's all yours. But please
leave as soon as possible.
Tell me what's wrong?
Nothing, my son.
Just leave. Leave now.
Brother.
Sir.
Haider sir.
Sir, he entered
Pakistan on the 10th.
From Lahore Airport.
Check every hotel,
every guesthouse of the Johar area.
Talk to every estate agency,
every broker.
Maybe he rented a place.
Show me your register.
Have you seen this man?
- No, I have not.
Take a good look.
- No, sir. I have not seen him.
Doctor, I've kept the
injections in the bag.
Did you check them properly? - Yes.
Thank you.
I've to go early in the
morning...all because of you.
Long live.. - l-laaris Saeed!
What's does Haaris Saeed mean to us?
- There's no God, only Allah!
We'll meet back here in an hour.
We will leave for
the airport from here.
What's does Haaris Saeed mean to us?
Daniyal.
- There's no God, only Allah!
Keep the outfit.
What's does Haaris Saeed mean to us?
You're looking nice.
"Couldn't be mine...
nor could be yours."
"I couldn't endure
this atrocity of love."
"Couldn't be mine...
nor could be yours."
"I couldn't endure
this atrocity of love."
Aunty, has the doctor left?
Has the doctor left?
- Yes, he just did.
You're early today.
Yeah, the tetanus booster shots..
What are you doing?
Let me arrange for
the booster shots.
Long live..
- l-laaris Saeed!
Aunty...where did the
second box come from'?
What box?
U m bvi sir's medicines.
Long live..
- l-laaris Saeed!
Long live.. - l-laaris Saeed!
- Enough!
Be quiet!
What's that'?
- It's a toy car...for my son.
Show me.
Professor Haaris Saeed
sir is amongst us.
Sir, I just bought it.
If I open this up,
my son won't stop pestering me.
Didn't you hear...show me.
Or else you won't
get home to your kid.
Please welcome him
with full enthusiasm.
The doctor must have
bought these. Yes.
But he never does that.
And I always give him
a list of medicines to buy.
We purchase this medicine
only once a month.
And I'm the only one who makes an
entry and stocks it in the fridge.
I said I don't know.
I am not feeling well...
I'm going home.
What's wrong, aunty?
Aunty?
Listen up.
Fine, go on.
We're with you.
We've proven to the vvor
d..
..that we Pakistanis
are not afraid.
..when it comes to upholding Islam.
Not from that cruel America.
..nor his infidel accomplice India.
What does India want?
Sir, we're checking
hotels in the Johar area.
Sir...vve just received
a call from Pearl Hotel.
That's where the bas*** was living.
He just checked out.
Circulate his photo all around town.
Every security personnel in Sheikh
sir's rally should have his photo.
Did you get the right
bottles today, doctor?
O lndians...come to your
senses...know your place.
I challenged you before...
Call me to any court
of law in this world.
And we'll prove who
the real terrorists are.
Doctor, where are you going?
Unc
e's waiting for you.
The pain's increasing, come quickly.
I'll answer it later.
- Alright.
You Indians want
action against Pakistan.
Poor lndia...they only express
their motives on television.
The court has
honorably acquitted me.
Did you attach a copy
of the delivery receipt?
Who is it?
If India doesn't want to
settle these problems in the court.
..then what does India want?
Sabahuddin Umavi.
Lashkar-e-Taiba's founding member.
Faster.
Bravo.
He personally trained Kasab...
and the other nine terrorists.
Faster.
Faster. . . like a monkey.
On 27th November,
Umavi ordered his terrorists.
“to bum down Oberm and the Ta}.
Where's the doctor?
Greetings, brother.
- Greetings.
I apologies for yesterday.
- It's alright.
Fine...if India says
they want strict actions.
..then so be it.
He's been pestering for so long.
Why are you calling continuously?
The doctor's busy.
Stop the doctor.
Don't let him administer
the injection.
Stop the doctor.
Just like this
enthusiasm in Lahore..
..it will grow to
every city in Pakistan.
This will ruin India
and set Kashmir free.
What does India think?
The moment has passed.
This is the moment for Jihad.
They play such dirty games.
What does India want?
Our Kashmiri brethren.
Even America and Russia
couldn't stand against our Jihad.
And by the grace of Allah,
India will fall as well.
Haaris sir...march ahead.
- We're with you.
What was the jail security doing?
Rascals!
Seal all exit points
out of the city.
Airports,
land borders, trains, busses!
Shut down the entire city.
Where's Sheikh sir?
Where's I-l aaris Saeed'?
Keep calling us terrorists
and we keep quiet.
At the rally.
Get him out.
Have our men escort him home.
NOW!
What's does Haaris Saeed mean to us?
- There's no God, only Allah!
And that doctor.
Did he say something?
He wasn't behind it, sir.
- Then?
Someone exchanged the
injections at the clinic.
They want us to hide in a corner?
Never! Never!
Listen carefully to
our message to India.
Quickly.
Hurry UP-
Get the car. Hurry up.
Move. Move aside.
Stop.
Stop him!
Someone's chasing Sheikh
sir's car in a police vehicle.
Stop him.
Hurry up,
Sheikh sir's car is coming this way.
Move the barricades.
Fire.
Move the bamboos.
Hurry up.
Break it down.
Wait a minute, brother.
- Come soon, dear.
Move!
Wait a minute, brother.
Quickly.
Come, dear.
Just a minute.
Why you...
Stop.
Why did you do it, ma'am?
For Pakistan.
Mefam!
L-I aaris Saeed.
You keep asking...
what does India want?
India wants...justice!
Where's Amina Bi?
Yes, sir.
Go...go..
What's your exit plan'?
It's impossible
to get to the airport?
Daniyal, they'll close
down the entire city.
Get out of there at any cost.
I'll call you later, sir.
Okay, but keep your phone on.
Fine.
Take your clothes off...
quickly.
It'll expire soon...
get it renewed.
Fine.
- Let him through.
Hey...
Stop!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Sir, what are you doing?
Honestly, sir. I swear.
This man came to my shop alone.
..to rent my stuff for the wedding.
Who's wedding was it?
What is it?
She's in labor.
The pain's excruciating.
We've to get to the hospital.
It'll only take a minute,
let me check.
Rascal...l am dying...
let's go now!
It'll only take a minute,
let me check. Wait...
Don't you have
a mother you scoundrel.
If anything happens to my kid...
I won't spare any of you.
Rascal...get out of here quickly.
Come on.
Let them through.
Daniyal.
The Indian border is
only 26 kilometers from here.
Cover every nook and corner.
Sir, they will seal the
entire border around Lahore.
Sir, we've some
contacts at Dera Nanak.
Tell them to drive
towards north from Lahore.
Seal Lalo and Dhilvvan roads too.
Check every car.
But, sir...they can also
head for the Afghanistan border.
Or...
ran.
- But the borders.
Sir, all the land
borders will be sealed.
Tell them to drive southwards,
towards Karachi.
But this way they will
be trapped inside Pakistan.
Sir, Daniyal can come
the same way they did.
From Karachi...in a boat.
But it'll take us at least
1O hours to get to Karachi.
There is no other way, Daniyal.
It's impossible to cross
any other border of Pakistan.
He isn't here.
Let's look at the back.
After the 26/11 attack.
..we planted one of our man
at the Ivlanora Jetty petrol pump.
Sir, that man can
take Daniyal in his boat.
But, sir...
- But what?
Only till the Pakistani
territorial boater's limit.
Beyond that...the Pakistani
navy will intercept them.
Sir, I think we should send
our boat to Pakistani waters.
Even I know that.
But for that we'll
need Government clearance.
%‘w,(
This one.
Sir, that's him.
What?
Haaris Saeed and Umavi are dead.
- Yes, sir.
The news reports will be here soon.
L-low do you know'?
- Sir...our men...l<illed them.
Speak up.
Sir, brother has a white Suzuki car.
Number.
LEA 1901.
Let me go, I haven't done anything.
I haven't done anything.
Who gave you the authority?
It's our responsibility
to get him out of there.
He's one of us.
- No, he's your man.
You sent him in like Rambo.
Now get him out yourself...
bloody idiots!
I must tell the Prime
Minister everything right now.
But, sir, please listen to me..
- I say get out!
Yes, sir.
LEA 1901.
11 am in the morning.
Sir, 11 am.
From Lal Kuan checkpoint.
Send the car number
to Karachi police.
Let me be blunt, sir.
Did India assassinate Haaris
Saeed and Sabahuddin Umavi?
No!
India has no connection
with their deaths.
Let me strongly
reiterate at this point..
..that India does not
believe in vigilante justice.
The media.
- I have an idea, sir.
M r. Roy.
Sir, Daniyal Khan just called.
He says he's going to surrender
himself to the Pakistani government.
..and admit that the Indian government
is behind both the killings.
Nonsense!
- Sir, Daniyal has threatened to do so.
He said he'll surrender
in half an hour.
If your leave's been approved,
why would we object.
Stop. Stop-
Sir. Yes, sir.
I'll wait for your call.
Prime Minister's office...
is talking to the Navy.
So...where are you coming from'?
Yes, sir.
Show me your license.
- Yes.
LEA...1901.
Samit.
- Yes, sir.
There's a navy plane waiting
for you at Palam Air base.
It will take you
to Western Naval Base.
Me?
The licenses made in Lahore.
Yes.
Go on.
Let them through.
White Suzuki?
Stop!
8990!
Fine, go on.
Where are you heading?
- Ivlauripur.
Take one of our men along.
Yes.
Come on, get in.
Have some shame.
There's a lady inside.
Sit at the back.
Get in.
Sit.
Go!
You're brave...done be a fool.
Come on.
Come, Khalid!
I'll sign this. Keep the rest.
Open this.
They're getting away.
Hurry UP-
We'll take you across
Pakistani waters.
And the Indian navy
will pick you up from there.
My satellite phone is on.
They will know our
location and get to you.
Thank you.
The car was heading
towards Ivlauripur.
I think they're heading
towards Ivlanora jetty.
They will get out using a boat.
Alert Naval command to
stop all boats in this area.
It will be a big problem, sir.
Numerous boats leave
from Ivlanora and Ivlauripur.
I don't care!
Stop all the boats
sailing in the water.
Each one!
Samit!
- Yes, sir.
Yes.
That's the boat's position..
..vvhich we're getting
through their satellite phone.
Okay, sir.
Within 1O minutes this boat
will enter international waters.
Pakistan Navy!
Why did it stop?
Why are you so far
away from the shore?
We're fishing, sir.
It's really difficult these days.
Check now.
- Okay, sir.
Check at the back.
Back there too.
Were there any other
boats in front of you?
Don't know,
sir...there are lots of them here.
The boat's clear, sir.
I think they've been stopped.
Both the boats have stopped.
Sir.
Turn the light that way.
Fire that way in the water.
Dammit.
The boat is still
in Pakistani waters.
But we can't go there.
L-low far is it'?
Not too far.
But we don't have
orders to go beyond this.
They'll have to come
into international waters.
Stop firing.
Turn the boat towards Karachi.
- But, sir...
I said turn it around.
Follow me.
- Fine, sir.
Show me your navigation charts.
Get in.
Wait a minute.
Why are they heading
back to Pakistan?
We'll have to go back.
Sir they are right here.
There.
DaniyaPs at the exact
location where the boat stopped.
We just have to go there.
I am sorry.
We don't have orders
to enter Pakistani waters.
Turn us around, we've to go back.
Sir, we're just 5
minutes away from him.
We can't leave him behind.
I said we don't have permission
to enter Pakistani waters!
Turn back!
No!
Sir...where were you on the
night of 26th November, 2008'?
Where were you that night.
..when 1O men humiliated
1 billion Indians.
Wherever you were, I'm sure..
..even you felt weak,
helpless and humiliated.
Your blood must have boi
ed...
ike
mine, like the entire country.
This man...
whom we're leaving to die..
...he single-handedly
killed all those people.
..who brought India
to its knees that day.
Sir, if we can't
save this man today.
..then what's the point
of this technology, this power?
It's all useless!
I think we won't have
that tea at the Taj.
No!
I'll have tea with you.
Even if we have to swim all
the way to Mumbai.
Okay then, Navvaz Ivlistry...
...have a cup for me as well.
"A traveler of the night."
"Says goodbye in the morning."
"l couldn't be yours
while I was still alive."
"But carried out
his duty while dying."
"Couldn't be yours...nor
could be yours."
"I couldn't endure
this atrocity of love."
Do you know why I
agreed to this mission?
Because I want to see the same respect
in Dilavvar Singh's eyes for me.
I want him to salute me again.
With the same enthusiasm...
the same passion.
Ma'am, we're here to
escort you to the base.
Can you take me somewhere else?
This is the same place that
was attacked on 26/11..
People have gathered here
today in thousands
First morning after the
masterminds of 26/11 were killed.
Around here are
the people of lvlumbaL.
..who are here to pay
condolence to the victims.
People from all over the
city are gathering around here..
..to express their happiness.
L-low do you feel'?
God has given us justice.
But we shou
d've
killed those murderers.
Here's a cup tea, dear?
But I don't have money.
It's alright.
I am not charging anyone today.
Take it.
My son worked at
the Taj as a waiter.
That night they killed him too.
Today when I learned that those
murderers have been killed...
..it felt like my son's
soul attained peace.
So I won't charge anyone today.
Yes.
Uncle.
- Yes.
Can I get another cup of tea?
Of course.
Here.
Thank you.