Our beloved Sun is 60 years old.
The name of the Sun is Mutha Seth.
And the Gods created
him in a leisurely pace
Boss, l am not to blame.
Not to blame?
The Enquiry Committee's report
lays it on you... all your fault.
Boss... this is wrong !
All right, l'm kicking this upstairs.
l'll tell them what you're saying...
it's a committee of assholes.
l didn't say that.
- What else?
Honestly, l am... a very honest cop.
The one honest cop in all of lndia.
Honestly, what've you done?
She was placed in my charge.
l was always with Madam Elizabeth
when she went for walks,
at lunch and dinner.
l ensured that she
took her medicines timely.
l slogged 24 hours, l stuck with her.
- Then how did Elizabeth get pregnant?
Not my fault.
How come her belly swelled?
l didn't...
Come clean. Who did it?
- No one.
Moron... never read biology in school?
No one did anything, still
she got a swelling? Miracle?
lt's a belly, not a balloon.
Who did it to Elizabeth?
Blackie.
- Who's Blackie?
l don't remember him clearly.
Bozo, one shot under that
ear and you'll remember.
l was escorting
Elizabeth to the Police Grounds.
On the way, l stopped.
Why?
To eat betel-leaf with betelnut.
Go on.
There was a crowd at the
betel-leaf-betelnut shop.
He was making betel-leaf-betelnut
and he was taking his own sweet time.
The shopkeeper...
- ls he Blackie?
No! The shopkeeper is a
straight guy, strong, moustachioed.
He only likes wrestling. -
Who likes wrestling? -The shopkeeper.
Get over your shopkeeper!
Make it quick.
l took my betel-leaf with
betelnut and when l turned around,
Elizabeth wasn't there!
What?
- Yes! l was screaming for her...
Elizabeth... Elizabeth madam !
But she was nowhere.
l was walking,
screaming... and then suddenly...
Suddenly...?
There she was, standing under a tree.
Alone?
Boss, this is embarrassing.
She wasn't alone.
- Who else was there?
Blackie was with her.
- Who is Blackie?
Black dog. Mongrel.
- What did you do?
Everything possible! l blew my
whistle! l went at him with my cudgel.
l was about to fire in
the air... but... - What?
By then it was all over.
Blackie had shamed
the police department.
Constable laik! lt's you ault!
All because of your negligence...
Elizabeth the star police bitch
bore a litter of six and she died.
There's no dearth of cunts
like you...
but where will we find one
honest bitch?
Boss, l didn't do anything !
Blackie was raping Elizabeth in front
of your eyes and you did nothing?
Get out of here!
- Boss, please save me!
This Blackie has destroyed me!
- Then find Blackie! Take off his cap!
Take his cap! Go find Blackie!
- l'll be like a father to
Elizabeth's puppies!
Please, save me!
l told you to keep this vehicle in
shape. The new boss is coming...
He was to have come at 7. Now he's
coming at 6! Doesn't value time!
What are you upto?
Get down and push.
Push... give it all you got.
This won't move even a
pubic hair ... pump up the jam.
There's a new boss.
Fist impession is last impession.
Pump it up.
When are we going to get there?
Yusuf Khan here...
speaking... yes.
The officer comes...
car breakdown? Okay.
Sir !
Give me sir, give me...
Welcome to Canda.
Sir... this is Yusuf Khan.
This is welcome...
a traditional welcome.
The local boys dance.
O'Lord, save this spare this poor
soul from the clutches of ghosts.
o! PBlackie las uine me!
My wife deserted me because
of Blackie.
Blackie has driven me to the streets.
Now l stand before You !
Help me to find Blackie.
Help me, Lord !
Tell me where he is.
You know everything.
Tell me... where is he?
Blackie... is that him?
Blackie... Blackie...
Rafiq, take whatever you want.
Give the rest to the junk dealer.
Professor Shastri's new book.
- Which one?
History or Myths? This
will shake up our society.
Nothing can shake our society.
l'm writing an article on this book.
- No place for that in my newspaper.
This newspaper is changing.
Write on astrology.
- l know nothing about it.
l don't believe in astrology.
- You needn't.
Only paint a rosy future.
No one will complain.
Must be Mutha Seth.
Tell him l left long ago.
Ye faithful shall be rewarded with
health, long life and prosperity.
And rice and grains and
profits from all ventures.
And a life of many pleasures.
Stop.
Welcome... welcome sir.
- This is not necessary.
Have l come to the wrong place?
- No sir! Please come in.
Sawant, what's going on inside?
Puja (A Hindu prayer)
You enter at the correct time!
Today is most auspicious.
A sacred day...
A holi day. And you are welcome.
Why a religious ceremony in a
police station? - lt is a tradition.
Come in, si.
lat i sometlin g lappens out tlee
- ike lat
What will happen?
lt's nothing... look up
and behold ! God is there.
Look within... God is there.
Come si, come unto Go.
Go in... stay inside.
We invoke the blessings of our Gurus
and in the name of God we shall pray
We also seek the
blessings of the Goddesses.
Tell everyone to get to work.
No tensions about work.
God takes care of everything.
- Sawant, they must get back to work.
Yes, immediately after the ceremony.
- Right now. Start work.
God help us.
Glory to the Gods,
the Most Benevolent,
Givers of all my life's wishes
We worship your golden idols
with sandalwood and vermilion.
What? Are you insisting that
our newspaper has changed?
l don't see any change.
Today's like any other day.
No sir! Look at this paper...
- That thing is looking to ruin me.
Unlike you, l'm no intellectual.
l'm uneducated. l sold
animal fodder to succeed in life.
l've stopped printing
serious articles.
l'm trying to push light reading.
l have changed the style totally.
Then why isn't my paper selling?
The advertisers have run away.
Circulation is dwindling.
A day will come when you
alone will read my paper.
Building a circulation
takes some time, sir.
l've been hearing that for 6 months.
How long? Until after
we're dead and gone?
Why did l summon you so urgently?
Why?
Why? Why?
Had you arrived urgently,
l'd remember.
Should l wait?
- lf you have work, run along.
l'll call you when l remember.
And come pronto.
Sure, sir.
Shut him up.
Yes, l remember! Kulkarni...
Meet Deshpande.
Who...? - lf you ask too
many questions, l'll forget.
What was l talking of...?
Deshpande...?
- Yes him.
He is a marketing man...
Educated abroad or something
like that.
Kulkarni, you are wise. Keep your
values and principles to yourself.
And listen to him.
But sir...
- Don't ask too many questions. Work.
And listen... say hello to him.
There he comes again.
- Go.
Comfortable?
Badshah... Badshah-boss...
- What?
That horse-cart-wallah
Hamid is stone drunk.
Warn him ! lf he doesn't pay his booze
bills, l'll confiscate his horse cart.
Now get lost!
Come in Shabbo.
Shop inauguration done? - Not
shop. You call a studio a studio.
Whatever, but now you're on.
- Except an auspicious offering.
What is that?
- The first photo has got to be yours.
Then do it quickly.
Sit in the lmpala.
Shabbo, that's an lmpala car.
Not your dad's horse-cart.
Prashant, never ridicule my dad.
Sorry!
Relax Shabbo, no tensions.
You own that car.
Spread your arms, like
ladies who own cars.
What's this lmpala on the inside?
The nails on the bench are pricking.
Then pretend as if it isn't pricking.
Not even nails can hurt lovers.
Don't give me one-liners.
Take the photo.
Come on.
You took the photo?
- lt's perfectly okay.
How could you just snap it?
- Why?
The big photo-wallahs say smile
-smile and all that. Then they click.
You can't get a thing right.
Shabbo, you're smiling 24*7.
No point telling you to smile.
Come on, sit on the moon.
You'll see when the photo is done.
Send it to Bombay. Bollywood
producers will line up for you.
When they come,
they'll hire Hamid's cart.
- l warned you,
never ridicule my dad.
Put on these sandals. l bought them.
You'll look like a fairy.
Now lie down on the moon.
You look pretty.
Shabbo on a slice of moon.
Hey, l'm afraid... what if l fall?
lf you drop off the moon
you'll dangle in space.
Prashant, will you leave me dangling?
- How can l? l love you.
ou'e my leoine.
- ia.
Me, a liar?
Just ask whatever you wish.
A spin around the world in
that copter?
l'll gift Taj Mahal to you.
Just ask.
Now recline on the moon.
This photo l must have.
You're looking beautiful...
- Wait... sorry!
l want my photos taken.
l am going to Dubai.
But here's romance in broad
daylight. Boy Hindu-girl Muslim.
Story in a film !
These films are driving
you out of your minds.
lf you Hindus walk away with
our women,
what will we do?
Stay unmarried?
Stay... Don't go against your own
people. Sit tight... click this photo!
Do it.
Film is same, stoy is same. nly,
eal leo eplaces tle ake leo.
Take this photo... is
your camera paralysed?
Snap to it!
Badshah-boss...
- What is it?
The cops have confiscated our hooch.
lnspector Sawant wants a bribe.
He wants you at the police station.
- l'll sort you out later.
No more credit for
hooch at Badshah-boss' pub.
Here goes Hamid again...
Who is this idiot?
- Don't call him names.
Big political leader.
lf anyone overhears, we're screwed.
- When he broke his arm, l fixed him.
Caeul, lis lea ill topple.
H e keeps tunin g in tle in .
et, iglt, cente.
l said, size it down. But no,
he always wants it bigger.
Now this bugger is disproportionate..
can't even hold his own weight.
Nail his backside.
No use. Screw his rear, his front,
or slug it right into his mouth...
all le ill.
Tinker with history and you're damned.
Shame on Professor Shastri.
Down with the deaf professor!
Now, what do you want?
Ban.
Have you read the book?
- Several times.
Each time l have felt ashamed.
ook outsie, see tle
an ge oe you listoy.
Not just my history, it's yours too.
- No. Our history is different.
Our history is glorious.
A history of sacrifice, valor...
inspires us to fight,
gives us strength to survive.
l write about history.
l do not concoct myths.
What use is showcasing a few
mistakes of our ancestors?
What use hiding those historical
mistakes?
- Why are you digging up dead bodies?
Why are you spreading this venom?
You have hurt our feelings.
History isn't written to
please anyone.
Enough of these histories!
True or not, we won't
tolerate a history that defames us.
l reasoned with them. That is why
they are only burning your book.
Those who hurt religious
beliefs are annihilated.
What is in this rubbish history?
l am so ashamed.
Shame on Professor Shastri !
Those who play with
history will be reduced to ashes.
Where are you off to?
There has been a big accident.
Who will do your job? Your father?
My father has met with an accident.
Which father?
Hamid, the horse-cart-wallah
He is dead.
Hamid? How could he be your father?
Your father died 1 8
years ago, in police firing.
Yes...
- Then...?
My mother married Hamid.
Do you get a new father every
time your mother gets a new husband?
Get to work.
Why are you staring at me?
l need 400 Rupees.
What for?
The funeral.
400 bucks! Are you throwing a party?
That's 500.
Come back quickly.
Right after the burial.
Caeul, please be caeul.
Put him down carefully.
Stop! No! Don't!
Don't bury the dead man.
We want the dead man's body.
What happened...?
What is the matter?
- Give us the corpse.
The corpse is in the grave.
- Why?
The man died. So he was buried.
With whose permission
are you burying him?
Permission?
- Yes!
The body was given to us
after post mortem.
What other permission is needed?
Who is the man you buried?
- Hamid.
He isn't Hamid.
- What do you mean?
He is Kishan, a Hindu.
He isn't Hamid.
This is Anwar. His son.
- Was he your father?
Everyone knows.
Hamid lived amongst us.
Every Hindu living around you will
be converted to lslam and buried?
Let's go.
One minute.
Bring out the body.
The body can't come out.
Go on, start saying the prayers.
- Don't. Wait.
What are you doing here?
Go home.
Kishan was one of us.
His dead body is ours.
Throw them out.
Come on. - Kishan was
a Hindu. We want his body.
He has been buried.
We cannot remove him.
Body will be retrieved. From hell,
if need be! Government orders.
That'd be wrong.
- No tensions. Bring out the body.
This is against religion.
Give us Kishan's body!
- Give him to us!
Send Muslims to their proper place.
- Pakistan, or their graves.
Kishan was my brother.
4 years older to me.
lee i le lie - itl
Fatima... sle is a uslim oman.
She owns a horse cart. He drove it.
Fo lo lon g i le lie itl le
1 9 or 20 years.
Did Hamid convert?
Not Hamid. Kishan.
- Kishan...
Did Kishan become a Muslim?
ls this grilling necessary? He says,
Kishan was his brother. Period.
Why won't you trust a
simple law-fearing man?
Are you with Muslim goons
who buried him?
ls that why you're after
this poor man?
We won't allow this
to happen. Understand?
Return his body immediately.
We demand it.
This is between Laxman and
the police. Who are you?
This isn't a matter
involving only Laxman.
Kishan was a part of the fraternity.
He was a brother to all Hindus.
Therefore we deserve
his body. Understand?
Mr Sattar, AsSalamu Allaikum.
- Wallaikum AsSalaam, Mr Bavdekar.
Are you stoking the embers? - Your
Muslims are. l'm trying to douse it.
l was in Bombay, to
meet the chief minister.
Had l been here... l'd
never have let this happen.
And you... you've just arrived.
You've trusted this Satan?
You dared to dig out our body?
You're lucky that the word hasn't
gotten around. You have insulted us...
Apologize right now. Return our body.
While you take his body away,
you expect us to chant hyms?
lf we do not get the body, then you
are responsible for what is to follow.
Until this is decided,
we'll keep it in the morgue.
Why? Body is ours,
body's brother is with us!
We must get the body.
- Go to court.
Convince the judge. The body is yours.
The body is ours. Why
should we go to court?
ls tle cout bigge tlan eligion
- ook...
You are taking this
decision to please the Muslims.
You policemen and these
Muslims will seriously regret this.
Fatima! l, lat las lappene
No one ever thought this could happen !
lnstead of coming home,
he landed there and suddenly
the photo had to fall...
and of all people,
it had to kill Hamid.
Each man... drawn to his death.
- Why does it happen only to the poor?
ln this world, a poor man has no one.
- We have no one.
Tle police kille Fatima's
ist lusban .
Now, the leader has crushed
the second.
Poor thing, what can she do?
- Cry, cry your heart out.
Think of him and cry!
- Cry out loud...
As long as he was alive,
the police never touched him.
After he died, they've
locked him in prison !
Allah ! What woes have come upon us!
Such troublesome times.
AsSalaamu Allaikum.
What've you decided?
Nothing.
What?
We haven't decided anything.
They pulled Shabbo's dad out of
his grave and you're undecided?
My mother says, let by gones be.
He is dead and gone.
What use bickering
over burial or cremation?
May his soul...
- Allah ! May his soul find peace.
The man died because
of an electric shock.
The government will pay 50 or 60,000.
lf you keep crying over it, the
Hindus will swallow the money.
Don't let them swallow the money.
- Not the Hindus.
Are you mourning with your mother?
Let Shabbo stay here. Come along.
Come on.
Anwar, you won't go.
Don't hold back the sorrow, Fatima.
Let it pour out.
lt's your fate... you are destined
to cry. - Remember him... and weep.
The water is flowing.
We got to collect the water.
Let's go. We'll come by tonight.
Come on, it's water. lf the
water runs out, then we've had it.
The water supply is only for an hour.
- Relana, inisl tle clapte
om Koan.
We must go, or we'll miss
the water. See you at night.
Rafiq... what a photo!
What's your book about?
Exploits of dancing girls?
No. Exploitation of dancing girls.
You are a Muslim. Stick to romantic
poetry. Why chase dancing girls?
l'e been eseaclin g tlem
o 5 yeas.
That's the problem with researchers.
What should
be on the cover, you hide it inside.
This semi-nude photo...
splash it on the cover.
Fom tomoo, pint sucl
lot plotos in ou nespape.
Rafiq, l am going to Baba
Desai's memorial service.
Baba Desai's death is going to
be tomorrow's headline news.
The material is all ready.
l'll get you a few more reactions.
- Not needed.
l have the front page news.
- What do you mean?
A Hindu
horse-cart-wallah was electrocuted.
And Muslims gave him a burial.
ls this front page news?
- Yes, front page.
And Baba Desai's death?
- Not on front page. Elsewhere.
Baba Desai was a freedom fighter.
He worked with Mahatma Gandhi.
He worked lifelong for the country.
- Cool.
A great man. My respects.
But what to do?
Nowadays, there's no
market for patriotism.
Look at this...
Baba Desai 98, was
bed-ridden for 8 years. Now dead.
Where is the news? What is the news?
Great man, no doubt. But
his news is insignificant.
But the horse-cart-wallah
lnsignificant man. Bigtime news.
Know this Kulkarni.
News is important. Not the man.
- Okay, thank you.
But a horse-cart-wallah's
story isn't going on my front page.
Hello, Kulkarni...
Drop that ego.
What you think, what l
think doesn't mean a thing.
What people wish to
read is more important.
As a marketing man...
- l am the editor.
l get to decide what they get to read.
Rafiq...?
- Done.
Everyone who lives in lndia,
is a Hindu.
This is a court.
No lecturing in court.
Hamid was a Muslim.
- Any proof?
Every child knows.
This is a court. Not a
place for child's play.
Did he have a birth certificate?
- No.
When a man is born...
you need a birth certificate.
Yes, or no?
Kishan was poor. How does a
poor man procure a certificate?
How do the rich procure a certificate?
Are they born clutching certificates?
Any school-leaving certificate?
- Kishan never went to school.
Who will give him a
school-leaving certificate?
Why didn't he go to school?
There was no school in the village.
Yes, there was a
school in a village nearby.
Why didn't he go there?
- A big river flowed in-between.
Why didn't he learn how to swim?
- There was no water in the river.
Then why call it a river?
lt is commonly called as river.
And worshipped.
- Any proof?
Yes, in ancient Hindu texts.
A Muslim Hamid in ancient Hindu texts?
- Not Hamid. The river.
What are we enquiring into?
Hamid, or the river?
Hamid.
- Yes.
Did he have a driving licence?
- Hamid plied a horse-cart.
Hose pulle tle cat.
icen ce asn't neee.
This ration card mentions his name.
The horse's ration card?
- Hamid's.
lt's a fake ration card.
Costs 25 bucks.
Hamid went to the mosque every Friday.
Lies! Kishan was a
devotee of Lord Ganesha.
He went to temples on
Tuesdays and danced at festivals.
He mourned and beat himself
bloody during Moharram ceremonies.
Hamid was jobless, poor.
The Muslims tempted him with alcohol,
lured him with marriage and money,
sold him dreams of a heaven.
Now they remember Kishan. He
was poor, jobless, hungry...
Why didn't you help your Hindu friend?
You discriminated. Tormented him.
Sick and tired, he became a Muslim.
He never converted. He
remained a true Hindu.
Any proof that he converted?
l performed the rites of conversion.
He became a Muslim, married Fatima.
No circumcision reported...
what you do to the foreskin...
- A male is circumsized.
The post mortem
doesn't mention circumcision.
Because he was a grown man,
he wasn't circumsized.
lf he wasn't circumsized,
how did he become a Muslim?
A symbolic circumcision was
performed by chopping a betelnut.
Where is the chopped betelnut?
Hamid was fond of eating betelnut.
There is no proof of Hamid's birth.
There is no proof
that he became a Muslim.
There is no proof of his wedding.
No water in the river, no
circumcision, betelnut...
How can l give a verdict? You tell me.
Tell me.
Rafiq ! What is this?
How did the headline change?
Who is the editor? Me, or Deshpande?
Whose orders are you obeying?
Deshpande... damn that Deshpande!
isten Raiq! ou ae in
tlis job only because o me.
Mutha Seth? Who is Mutha Seth?
Screw him !
Do you know what an editor is?
l'm not the publisher's dog !
l always carry my
resignation letter inside my pocket.
What...?
Hello...
What?
What was that?
A conspiracy to throw me out?
How do you know...?
All right...
All right... don't tell anyone
anything.
Don't even let out
that we talked on phone.
You get it? Good.
Come Tommy, come.
Come here, boy. Come on.
Sit.
Sit there. Sit.
Kulkarni, sit.
Yes thank you, sir.
Tommy, now don't move.
Good boy.
New dog. lmported.
l had two before him. lndian dogs.
These lndian dogs can't be trained.
Bit me twice.
He is imported. l will train him.
Tommy, sit there.
Sit.
Kulkarni...
Your wife was in a
hospital and l wasn't informed...?
She's better now.
l don't like being
informed by outsiders.
She is like a sister to me. And
you don't even think of informing me?
l didn't mean it that way.
- What do you mean?
You are always tense. You are tired.
Certainly not, sir.
- The strain is showing.
You need rest. Take a holiday.
Paid holiday. Sanctioned.
- l don't need a holiday.
That foreign-returned Deshpande...
he will manage everything.
What will Deshpande manage...
l mean...
Does he have any idea about
local culture, politics, history? No.
The paper sold like hotcakes today.
Why?
Because l took a risk. l put
the horse-cart-wallah's news...
on the front page.
lt worked.
ocal issues, si.
People are more
interested in local issues.
Not in Baba Desai's death.
Baba Desai is history.
Your doing?
- Yes.
My telephone has been ringing all day.
Yes, sales have increased.
Good job. l'm enjoying this.
Kulkarni, your scooter is obsolete.
Getting it kickstarted is an effort.
And by the time it starts,
the news is stale.
Today, we need speed. Speed.
Dump the scooter. l'll
make arrangements for a car.
Thank you, sir.
Tommy! Go now!
Go from here. Go! Don't come.
ldiot.
You can go now.
Yes.
Listen...
Send your wife's hospital
bills to my accounts department.
Okay, thank you sir.
Tommy, come my son. Come on.
Come back, boy. Come on.
l am sorry. Sorry.
ook, it's you ploto in tle pape.
You're looking pretty.
lt doesn't write pretty things
about you. - What did they write?
You can't read. Good for you.
- What did they write?
A Hindu horse-cart-wallah's lady,
a wanton woman, a lady.
You are the root of all evil.
- Do you think this is true?
Tell me, do you think it is true?
- They say,
newspapers write only truth.
Do you trust the paper
more than your mother?
And they say that l am a idiot.
My boss just fired me.
Everyone's saying that
no one will employ me.
All because of you.
Son, you are cursing me.
l'm going away. Don't wait for me.
The truth has triumphed.
- The verdict is out.
What are you waiting for? lt's
been 4 days since Kishan died.
How long will Hindus
wait to mourn their dead?
Give up the body.
What's your hurry?
- Haven't you heard the verdict?
You will take the body
and you will cremate it.
lf the upper court favors the Muslims,
which body will we give them to bury?
Worrying for Muslims?
You don't care for Hindus?
Nothing is above the courts.
The court has ruled.
Give us our body.
- Don't!
No! We don't accept this
court's ruling.
Mr. Sattar is appealing in
higher courts.
lf you fix the next verdict,
then we will fight.
But we won't give up our body!
We're going all the way!
Go where you belong.
- Go away to Pakistan. Leave us!
But we are taking our body.
Mind you !
lf we don't get our body,
we'll bury the whole lot
of them alive!
En masse, in one
huge world-famous grave!
Enough. Get out of here.
The body stays in the morgue.
Out.
Anyone who rises against our body...
- Will crumble to dust.
lt belongs to us... we
won't give up what is ours!
lt's ours!
We will not give up our body!
Becoming a big leader?
Threatening the police?
You circumcised Muslim pimp.
Damn you !
You want to end up with
your body in the morgue?
Vanish !
Why don't you say something?
- What is there to say?
l made a mistake coming
here to you on the sly.
Thank you, Shabbo.
- l didn't come here to sit mum.
Then speak.
- No, l won't.
Then, start a quarrel.
- You mean l come to you to quarrel?
Am l the one always quarreling?
Am l bad? Quarrelsome?
Enough. l won't come to
see you anymore. - Why not?
Have you gone blind? Don't you see?
- What happened?
The two parties are getting into
a fight. - How are we concerned?
What will my people say
if they find us? - What?
That l'm seeing the other
party on the sly.
- What do you mean...
other party?
Your party.
When did l become another party?
Then where do you belong?
- l neither belong here, nor there.
Mine's a third party.
- Third party?
The party of those in love.
ook, een len e quael,
it's o loe.
We're fighting to get closer,
not to stay apart.
Really?
Or, was that a one-liner?
- l swear, by you.
Prashant... will you
take me in your party?
Entry isn't free.
- But my purse is empty.
Not the purse. The heart.
You got to be rich at heart.
Shabbo...
Will you stay with me lifelong?
Take me away. Right now.
- Where?
Someplace far away. Over here,
l'm suffocating.
Take me away.
- Not right now.
You're backtracking.
- l'm not.
When the time is right,
l'll come for you.
But not on the sly. l'll go to
your house with a wedding band.
Listen...
l bought a ring for you at the fair.
Don't laugh. lt's inexpensive.
But magical.
- A magic ring?
What will it bring?
Help for you in times
of trouble. Wear it.
Tle cue is on...
om pm till  am.
No one here.
Anwar?
Anwar... what are you doing here?
l didn't do anything.
Did you start that?
Caught red-handed. Curfew violation.
So what if he is a Muslim like you?
Show us you're man enough.
Are you man enough?
- No...
What are you doing here?
ldiot! Do you want to
become a goon? A goon? Take that.
And burn down houses... shops?
Hit harder.
Who else is with you?
Bravo! He is loyal.
Oh mother...
Speak up, or l'm going to kill you !
Who is there with you?
Talk.
ln this country, anything that
belongs to Muslims is being grabbed...
everything...mosques,
shrines, schools,
even our burial grounds.
They even kidnapped Hamid's corpse.
lf you remain silent, then one day...
one fine day, they'll even abduct you.
And do you know what they will say?
Your forefathers were Hindu.
You are Hindu.
Worship idols. Sing Hindu hyms.
Conspiracy! This is a
conspiracy to destroy you !
Mr Preacher...one minute...
Sorry, nothing of that
sort is happening here.
You have come from another city.
You don't know about our problems.
So, please don't make
a speech to instigate.
Rafiq, sit. Pipe down.
Why is this happening to Muslims?
Have you ever thought? Ever wondered?
Why it's happening only to Muslims?
Because the mosques are going empty
At the times of prayer,
no one is seen there.
Muslims have forgotten Allah, they've
forsaken prayer and abstinence.
Muslims are floundering... lost.
Muslim women have forsaken the veil.
Remember the sacrifices Muslims made.
What we Muslims were...
and what we have become.
What have we become?
ln Muslim localities, in Muslim homes,
there is singing, dancing, music!
The singers are Muslim, the musicians,
the dancers all Muslim !
And the audience is Muslim.
Muslims drink alcohol.
Muslims sell alcohol.
Apocalypse is upon us.
This is the sign of the end !
A warrior of lslam in the battlefield
and a devout in the mosque
is a true Muslim.
O' true followers, protect your faith.
Put fear in the
hearts of Allah's enemies.
Fo tley ae you enemies too.
l call for battle, for jihad !
Mr Preacher, you should speak of
things that will improve their lives.
Why are you twisting facts and
instigating these simple folks?
This religion talks about humanism,
peace, about the rights of the
weak and poor.
What are you reducing it to?
Aren't you ashamed?
Shut up!
Throw out this hypocrite! Men
like him are enemies of lslam.
He speaks of making peace
with the enemy? - Go outside.
Shut up!
You are the man who lives
among the Hindus. Don't you preach !
What is he saying?
During riots, he comes running
to us to save his life. Coward !
But lslam isn't about...
- What do you know of lslam?
Do you even relate to Muslims?
Get out!
Journalist.
- Don't let him in.
Muslims like him are the
biggest enemies of lslam.
They talk of peace, to
threaten us. Peace with the enemy?
Afraid? Are you afraid of death?
Such obsessive love of
life isn't good.
Think of afterlife, of heaven.
You will be given 70 celestial maidens.
How many?
- 1 7.
Not 1 7.Seventy.
Seventy.
Seventy heaven lyhouries!
ln the embrace of your
wasting wives, you forget Allah?
You salivate over photos of
whores and watch their movies!
To fantasize? Take from
life only as much is needed.
And focus on heaven, on
how to attain that heaven...
where the beauty of the
houries is beyond imagination.
You see one of these beauties,
then you turn away.
When you see her again...
Do you understand what l am saying?
No...? Let me explain.
You see a beauty...
after seeing her... you turn away.
When you look at her again,
she is 70 times more enticing !
May Allah send all of you to heaven.
Fom tlis ay, no one ill
atcl cinema.
No one will watch television.
Women won't step
outside homes without veils.
Girls cannot study
in non-Muslim schools.
No one will sing, no one will
play music. No one will dance.
Mark my words.
Once you step outside, do not forget.
Rafiq,
Stop writing against these people.
Stop writing?
Stop telling the truth?
Then what is the point of my life?
Blackie...
The thief!
Pandu !
Hey Pandu...
- l have stopped stealing.
l'm not a thief anymore,
l swear by God !
l've given it up. l am not a thief.
You are thief no more,
l'm no more a cop.
lt's destiny's game.
- What are you getting at?
How can l explain this?
l lost my job because of Blackie
and l'm on the streets right now.
Blackie... have you seen him?
You must've seen him... a
black mongrel, coal-black!
Pandu, you are a thief.
- Okay, then...?
A thief in any village
will know all the dogs.
You must know Blackie...
tell me where he is...
Where is he?
Blackie... inside the tape-recorder?
ls that you in there, Blackie?
Please send a constable, quickly!
What happened?
Outside the morgue...
- What happened there?
Wasn't a constable posted
outside the morgue? - Yes.
He ran away.
- Must've gone for a piss.
No! Now he's right there...
in front of me!
What do want?
lt's Hamid's ghost! Your
constable is possessed.
The ghost is driving him mad !
He's stripping !
l'm Hamid... horse-cart wallah ! My
soul is suffocating ! Let me out!
Set me free! Or l'll
burn this village down !
There goes my sixth man.
The body is all alone. lf anything
happens to it, you'll come hollering.
No one wants that job,
because of Hamid's ghost.
et me go! Stop tailin g me!
5 possessed cops are already
at the shrine yelling to
get rid of the ghost.
lt's your duty to take care of this.
Fom lee ill l get anotle cop
et me out,
o l'll estoy eeytlin g!
Send a strong cop!
eae me.
Let me go.
Where is Rafiq?
- He hasn't reported.
F or you.
This the 50th time l'm hearing
this story today.
l don't know the truth.
Ask the police.
l'm exasperated !
- What happened?
There's a rumor doing the rounds.
Hamid's ghost possessed a cop
1 1 01 at the morgue.
The possessed cop ran amok
and left the morgue unattended.
Sensing an opportunity, the
Muslims stole Hamid's corpse.
lnteresting...
And then?
The Muslims buried Hamid and put
a duplicate corpse in the morgue.
This rumor has spread everywhere.
lt could actually be true.
This is tomorrow's
headline new son the front page.
Kulkarni...
This isn't news. lt is a rumor.
- Could be true.
What if it turns out to be false?
We'll apologize.
Have you weighed the consequences?
lf people think it's true,
this can spark off riots.
Stopping riots is
not a newspaper's job.
There's the government,
the police, the military.
Go on.
- Hey, stop!
l won't let you publish this rumor.
l am the editor.
l am going to complain to Mutha Seth.
ly ae you astin g you time
et tle nes out.
Go on.
Where is Kishan's body?
What do you want?
There is no body here. Stop!
- Where did the Muslims take the body?
This is a ward, for living bodies.
The morgue for dead bodies is outside.
What are you doing?
The patients will die!
There is no body here...
it's inside the morgue...
We don't care! Give us Kishan's body!
Behold our Lion God in all His glory!
Behold the crown of our king !
And bow to His feet!
Behold the Son, our Elephant God !
Glory to Him, the giver of wishes.
Quick... you needn't
take too many clothes.
What if this drags on?
e aen't goin g aay oee.
et tlin gs cool on, e'll etun.
What if the rioting goes on for long?
What is that? Drop it!
- Just the suitcase.
We'll miss the bus.
- But...
Oh, forget everything.
Bless us God, give us our wish.
You are the shepherd of orphans.
Without You all is lost. You
are the shepherd of orphans.
To You we flock when danger comes.
Behold the Mother Goddess,
the slayer of demons.
Did you pack my novel?
- No, l missed it.
What do you mean?
- l left it on the table.
l don't even have
another copy. We must go back.
We're returning as soon as
it cools down, right?- But...
Just forget it.
O'my countrymen, let
tears fill your eyes
Remember the sacrifices of our martyrs
Pandu was no ordinary man. lt
takes time to understand a great soul.
The police put him in jail
claiming he was a thief.
But look at the miracle...
his shackles came off,
the iron bars melted. Walls collapsed.
And Pandu was set free.
Pandu was born to serve the
Hindu faith.
Pandu died serving the religion.
Willingly he jumped
into the sacred pyre.
We will build a memorial to Pandu.
lt will be a huge monument.
As long as Sun and Moon rise,
Pandu's name will shine.
Till Sun and Moon rise...
Pandu, your name will shine!
Figltin g elentlessly against
eligious conesion,
Kishan became a saint.
Kishan is immortal.
Until we are given his body...
he has decided not to eat.
He will fast unto death.
ln lanes and by lanes this
will echo...Kisan is our hero!
will echo... - Kisan is our hero!
We don't want riches or homes,
give us Kishan's body.
Sit. Hey old man, sit. How
many times will l repeat? Sit.
Sit... quietly... yes, clap.
l am sad, l am deeply pained.
Satta, tlis is no time
o speecles.
Hamid dies and he goes to Allah.
And this is being whipped into
an issue to persecute Muslims.
But l stand beside you. l
won't let you suffer injustice.
l stand...
l stand accused. l killed Hamid.
Politics of murder!
Hamid died under the
weight of my wooden ''cut-out''.
But the truth is, Hamid died
because of government negligence.
Hamid got an electric shock,
so he died.
Therefore we demand that...
..Hamid's son should get
job in Electricity board.
Hamid's family must be given a
compensation of 50,000 Rupees.
And this lane must be
named after Hamid. - Clapping.
Fien s, my oice is beakin g.
PBut my couage is unboken.
ls am telling you...
- Sit down.
We will have an lslamic
school named after Hamid.
And l will pay for that school.
l will lay the foundation stone.
And every Muslim child
will be schooled there.
We say no to this English education.
We say no to this Satanic education.
This is no time for speeches.
Where's biryani?
Say...
Mutha Seth Happy Birthday.
Eeyone gets one sein g.
Fall in line.
Slowly.
ln your hands?
- Give him, give him.
Slow down. Everyone
will get their share.
Mutha Seth Happy Birthday.
Tell them to wish me happy birthday.
- Keep moving.
Mutha Seth Happy Birthday.
By order of the
district administration...
to preserve law and order...
a curfew is imposed
between 7 pm and 7 am.
More than 5 people may not
congregate in a public place...
with guns, swords,
sticks, spears or knives.
Violators will be
prosecuted according to the law.
This curfew begins at
7 pm and ends at 7 am.
Can l leave now?
- There is a night curfew. Stay here.
My mother will worry. She won't sleep.
And l have her medicines.
ls she using the medicine
l prescribed?
She is coughing lesser.
Ok.
Be careful. lt's dark outside.
Listen... don't come
to work for a few days.
Take care of your mother.
- Thank you.
Professor save me!
Professor, open the door!
We have got Kishan's corpse!
Sheer injustice! No one is standing
up for Muslims in this country.
l had warned you !
But no one listened.
- Badshah, we elders are
thinking about it.
What has your thinking got us?
lt has only ruined Muslims.
Quiet, now.
- l won't take this lying down.
Listen...
- Why should we accept this?
What were Muslims asking for?
Not homes,
not jobs, not schools,
not money, not alms.
All we wanted was one body.
And what did your police do?
lssued curfew orders.
Confined us to our homes.
lf we go out we are killed.
At home, we can only starve.
This is our condition now.
But enough is enough.
From now on, we don't need you...
nor your police, your courts,
your government,
Or that pimp Mutha Seth.
Badshah, you've got
this completely wrong.
Where are you going, Shabbo?
To find Anwar.
Tell me the truth.
Police station.
l'll go along.
No, mother!
You cannot come with me.
Why?
Because...
because of the fatwa
( religious diktat).
Women cannot go out of
the house without the veil.
And this is the only veil
that we have.
All right.
Shabbo, don't believe
anything that anyone says.
lf anyone calls, never respond.
You get that?
- Yes, mother.
l am Prashant.
Where were you? l have
been looking for you.
l looked everywhere,
but l couldn't find you.
Why have you switched your party?
l'm in disguise. l wanted to
go to your house to find you.
l was screaming for you.
Why didn't you stop?
l am terrified when my name is called.
Terrified of me?
- Yes, l am afraid of everyone...
And particularly of
anyone who is close to me.
You must hate me...?
- Why?
Because they burnt your shop.
Not only my shop. Even
your moon was burnt.
l should go away.
- Where will you go?
To the police station.
To look for Anwar.
Tell me the truth. You came
looking for me, didn't you?
Anwar... come with us.
What is this Shabbo?
- What happened?
Why don't you smile?
Can you smile
Smile.
The victory march is on.
Everything has been finalized.
Even routes.
Nothing can be changed now.
That horse-cart wallah...
Don't call him a horse cart wallah...
Sorry, Hamid...
- Kishan.
Kishan...
- Yes, go on.
Kishan's home.
- Excuse me.
Please read the court's judgment.
lf you call Kishan by the name of
Hamid, it may be a contempt of court.
This funeral procession...
Not a funeral procession.
Victory march.
e begin tle ictoy macl
om ou paty's leaquates.
e ill go to tle maketplace
an  tlen toas tle mosque.
And then through the Muslim locality
on our way to the crematorium.
Why through the Muslim locality?
- lt's part of lndia, isn't it?
Why this roundabout route?
To enter Muslim areas do
we need separate passports?
Look...
- Sir...
This is the tradition.
Every funeral goes
through the Muslim areas.
No problem about giving permission.
lf you follow a straight route...
- l did not come seeking permission.
l came to invite you.
To be a part of the victory march.
Do join us.
A small advice on my way out.
Do not try to stop this victory march.
Namaskar ( Greetings )
This place is used to riots.
Once every year or two,
there's always a riot.
The riots begin, people
get into murderous fights.
They torch each other's homes,
they plunder one another.
They vent their anger.
After a day or two, all calms down.
The police should not interfere.
You will be in charge
of the victory march.
l am taking a medical test tomorrow.
Push it after the march.
Then take a day off.
Get cracking.
- Yes, sir.
Shoot.
Shoot properly.
Fie... again.
Fie...
Again !
l am so afraid. Are
you not afraid, mother?
No, why fear riots?
As for me,
l've gotten used to violence.
eas ago, na's
atle ie in police iin g.
Now, this circus about your father.
ln his death, your father
has set this place on fire.
l had much hopes on Anwar.
Those hopes are also dashed.
Now... for the next riots, l
have no one to offer as sacrifice.
What have l got to lose?
Where is Anwar gone?
Allah knows. All l know is,
he will never return.
Mother, this might make you angry.
But l must ask you...
Can l ask?
- Yes.
Prashant and l were going to elope.
We'd go to Bombay and
start a family, together.
So many dreams.
l lie down but cannot sleep.
Cannot eam.
Would you have said yes?
- To what?
Marrying Prashant.
No.
Why?
He was Hindu.
What if l had run away?
Then, l would not have stopped you.
Really? You would have accepted us?
Our marriage?
Not today. Papa is tired.
l'll tell you a story tomorrow.
Promise.
l promise you, a long story...
that won't end until
you are in deep sleep.
l'll tell you a story about
this place.
There is a sea here.
The sea is full of fish.
And crocodiles and mermaids.
What else? There's a fair.
People flock from afar
to the fair, for fun.
n  tley take lome olls,
o tlei augltes.
couse, l'll buy you a oll.
Fo you, a special sin gin g oll.
l'll talk to you later.
Ok. Bye.
Why did you take this trouble?
You could've summoned me.
What have you done?
What have l done?
- You gave the body to the Hindus?
And you gave
permission for a funeral march?
When the march begins tomorrow,
what will happen?
What?
People will get killed. Homes will
be torched. lt'll be a disaster.
And who will be responsible?
You.
What can l do? The court
has sided with the Hindus.
l have read the order.
The court says, give Kishan's
body to his brother Lakshman.
Same thing.
- Not the same.
akslman belon gs to a
ieent sect, a lo caste.
Their tradition is unique.
His brother Lakshman
should get the body.
Where is this brother Lakshman?
- Where indeed?
He has been threatened into silence.
l am pleading Lakshman's case.
lt is too late now. l
have solved the problem.
You solved nothing... you
only complicated the problem.
When this news spreads...
thousands will be maimed and killed.
l am filing a petition
against you, for contempt of court.
Very well, sir. Do whatever
you wish. This is just too much !
l respect you. Therefore, good night.
Please, good night.
As long as Sun and Moon rise,
Kishan's name will shine.
l worship The Sun, Giver of Light.
O'Sun, dispel the darkness in
our hearts.
What happened?
- You are being arrested.
You are arresting me? They
maimed us, they burnt our homes.
Those satans are destroying
everything. And you are after me?
Say that in court.
- You should arrest that Satan.
We'll talk later.
- This is injustice!
Mr Bavdekar.... you should
keep on praying all night.
The people out there are
waiting for me.
l have an order to arrest you.
l prefer compromise.
Don't even try to touch me. The
whole town will be set on fire.
And rivers of blood will flow. Not
one of those Muslims will be spared.
You are under arrest.
Pick him up.
O' Moon, Giver of Ocean Tides,
shine in dark, bring to us Peace.
Aren't you supervising
the deployment today?
l wish that you wouldn't
step out of home today.
Are you arresting me?
ls this a house arrest?
Commendable courage.
But the fire is elsewhere.
How can you douse it here?
l'm following the rules.
- The rules?
You got this job because you are a
low caste. Are you teaching me rules?
l'll call the home minister and tell
him to throw the rule-book at you.
He will explain, over the phone.
- Are you threatening me?
Who do you think you are talking to?
l can finish you in one minute!
When l transfer you out of
here and throw you in a jungle...
you will forget what rules are.
You will rot all your life.
Pass the phone.
- That won't be useful.
All phones lines will
stay down for tonight.
Tomorrow, you may call the home
minister, or chief minister or...
As for today, don't even
think about stepping outside.
Take that!
Stop. Listen carefully.
According to the court's order...
Kishan's body will be handed
over to his brother Lakshman.
akslman is itl us.
H e ill get tle boy.
As for as your funeral march,
it ends here and now.
l request you to disperse.
Shoot at sight orders will
be issued after 2 hours.
This order stays in force
until tonight.
Thank you.
Take the hearse backwards.
As long as the Sun and Moon rise,
Kishan's name will shine.
What are they doing?
- Burying the dead.
Why are they burying?
That is the custom in this sect.
They do not cremate.
But the Muslims were burying him.
lf ultimately he was to be buried,
why this huge furore?
Have you read my new book?
- lt was banned immediately.
And they burnt all the copies.
l saved one copy. lt's for you.
You might find an
answer after reading it.
Come on.
A Blood Donation Camp is being held at
the Police Grounds from 7 am to 6 pm.
Sir...
Something's gone awfully wrong.
- Now what?
The name of this place is Canda.
- So...?
You came to Canda by mistake.
- What does that mean?
Actually, you were transferred to
Banda. But the typist made an error...
... about A-B-C-D.
That's how you came to Canda.
Who told you?
- Headquarters called.
Your new transfer letter is ready.
Have l been in the
wrong place for 1 0 days?
Don't mind this, Sir.
lf you had taken God's blessings,
these problems wouldn't have arisen.
Excuse me, l must go
to receive the new boss.
Before starting the new job, you
must do Hindu rituals. Please!
elcome Raiq. sSalaamu llaikum.
One tea for Rafiq. Sit.
What've you thought? Are you
migrating to the Muslim neighbourhood?
Quickly, you'll run out of choices.
- Decided, l'm moving in.
Good. l've spoken with Mr. Resul.
He is migrating to Saudi Arabia.
Nice house, behind the mosque.
You can hear the muezzin's call.
What more could you want?
Your tea is getting cold.
Badshah, our beloved Badshah.
Brother to all in need,
a friend indeed.
Sir...
Yes, Naik?
Blackie has escaped from this town.
- Who is that?
ook, l'e got a oeign PBlackie!
- Foeign
l am also escaping from this town.
- Why, what happened?
Long story.
What will happen to me?
And my F oreign-Blackie?
l'll recommend both of you.
Thank you !
Do a salaam to the boss.
Salute, please.
He's a foreigner, still learning.
Don't let him escape.
Hey, Mr. Bavdekar. Come here, sit.
AsSalaamu Allaikum.
-Wa Allaikum AsSalaam !
l'm going to see the Chief Minister.