Translated By MT
Rustom
Three shots that shocked the nation
It's a story in 1959
When the name of  "Mumbai " was Bombay
"The Gujarat " and Maharashtra
were part of Mumbai
It has been 12 years since the British
left at that time
However their impact is still  exists strongly
Drinking alcohol  is just an utterance
Because the barmen and the wine drinkers were in large numbers
The "Gori" Society modulate between the cases because of the ruling
And Raj Kapoor's film  named" Anari
spark a fire in the cinema
The strength of the Navy increase quickly
in the areas of  the Indian sea
Sir
We have found the signal
Give it to the captain
Sir
We have found the signal
(Jeff Sar)
An extra bridge
Yes, sir
An extra bridge required captain
Sir
Come , Rustom
Take charge
Officer
Sir
Organize this way to Bombay
Jeff Sar
Get the sprinkles ready
I've done it , Siir
Do you hear that?
I'm the responsible officer
Everything  has been canceled
And now we are going to Bombay
We will reach Bombay on April 26 after 16 hours
Prepare yourselves
Congratulations
Madam
Vikram's car has been arrived
♪ This God 's grace♪
♪ Because God has blessed me with you ♪
♪ I have learned to live because i left to you my soul ♪
♪Season is happy because of you , my love ♪
♪ Night has become crazy, I do not see anything in it ♪
♪ Season is happy because of you , my love♪
♪ I will become Yours with one gesturer ♪
♪ I smell your odour whenever i passed any street ♪
♪ I dream of you every night ♪
♪ Our meeting is our love's constitution ♪
♪ Light inside me because of you♪
♪ I'm pretty sky and you it's moon ♪
♪  This God 's grace♪
♪ Because God has blessed me with you ♪
♪  I have learned to live because i left to you my soul ♪
♪  Season is happy because of you , my love ♪
♪  Night has become crazy, I do not see anything in it ♪
♪ Fire ♪
♪ I left everything ♪
♪ And I came for you ♪
♪ Write  your name in my eyes ♪
♪ Nothing for me after you ♪
♪  Your word corresponds to one hundred words ♪
♪ Know that I will never leave you ♪
♪ The God's grace ♪
♪ Because God has blessed me with you ♪
♪ I have learned to live because i left to you my soul ♪
♪ Season is  happy because of you , my love♪
♪  Night  has become crazy, I do not see anything in it ♪
Indian navy ship, Mysore
Hello
How are you?
Quiet
Do not say anything
Cynthia
Where are you?
Madam has gone out
When?
Yesterday
Yesterday afternoon
Thank you
Hello
Britey
I'm Rustom
Hello " Rosi"
When you  arrived?
Just now
Please hand over the phone to" Cynthia"
She does not exist here
In fact she did not meet me since some days
OK
... but
Waiting for you
My dear," Cynthia"
You are an unique person in millions
I respect so much your beauty
The memories of that night which we had together didn't let me sleep
Yours, only for you
V
Hello
Bahanah Bay
The commander" Rustom Pavri" talking....
Hand over the phone to "Vikram"
But.....  commander sir
Sir not at home
I will miss you
Leave it "Jamna Bai "
iI hope that your hand is in my hand
And it's hard on you to let me travel
And we will talk  about everything when our eyes meet together
Your hair's odour still in my breath
My spirit stopped when you came to my arm
How could I forget this word that you said by your eyes ?
How could I forget that night I spent with you?
Yours , only for you
Vikram
Please, listen to me
I can explain
Trust me, darling
You can not
Go to the office
And brought the record
Sir
Good morning, sir
Good morning, Rosie
Is Vikram here?
Sir, "Vikram" did not attend yet
Have a seat
I'll get you tea or coffee
No, thank you
You look very pretty today
Thank you
Goodbye
How are you, "Bahanha Bay"?
Fine
Sir
Did he tell you anything?
No, sir
hello, sir
Where were you during working time yesterday?
I swear
When we came out yesterday by car
the gasoline pump disrupted car
And we found a shop after the passage of so much time
Then we repaired the car there
I do not think that what happened
You went out with that car which it's wireless is disabled
And then one of the wheels get disrupted
Now you return after work
How do we lie to you, sir?
OK
I'll accept your words
Just do something
Write a report about that accident
I do not want a long report
Only Just write which wheel disrupted ?
Without consulting each other
Forgive us sir
The work wasn't too much tomorrow
So we went out for a walk
Patil
Sir
Subtract 7 days salary for those four
Out
A try to give a bribe to a
criminal investigations officer in "Bombay"
This is my the last signatures
OK
I am on vacation since tomorrow
I'll take some rest for 15 days
I'm the commander" Rustom Pavri" Indian Navy forces
"Vikram Mekheja"  have been killed on my hands
And I want to turn myself in to you
Is it possible that you bring me some water?
What?
Come in
Stop madam
Get lost
Who is in charge here?
Vincend Lobo
Investigations officer
"  Rustom Pavri " killed my brother
Arrest him now
Leader "Pavri" has turned himself in to the police
half an hour ago
So what are you doing here?
Go there and interrogate him
Do not tell me what I should do
Do you know who you're talking with?
And who is murdered?
My authority is very stong
It is better to do what I tell you
No, madam
You will do as i tell you
This a crime scene
And We are collecting evidences
So please get out right now
come on Madam
This phone is bothering me so much
Yes, speak
Orissa
I'm "Tuka Ram
Yes, speak
How are you?
" Vikram Mekheja" has been killed
What do you say?
Who killed him?
this new it's  price is 50 rupee
A senior navy officer killed him
What is his name?
Commander" Rustom Pavri"
Pavri?
Yes
I'll give you a hundred not fifty
But do not tell this news to any newspaper
Do not worry sir
My Lord please
My time will return
The killing of 300 people in the fire in" Goudy"
And 12 thousand copies was sold
When gold came down from sky
17 thousand copies was sold
Train collision
And four hundred people killed
13,5  thousand copies was sold
Where are the workers?
Stop printing "Hemenaj"
But the ongoing printing
We will lose
Leave this all
I found the news that it will pay your salaries for the last three months
Come on, stop the printing quickly
OK
sir commander
Your wife still awaits you abroad
Please ,meet her
Please ask her to leave
I  will not  meet anyone
I'm sorry, madam
This incident should have happened in someday
What do you mean?
Sir ,you know " Vikram Mekheja 's personality
He thought that he is an invincible
but I did not understand this
How commander's wife concerned with that person?
Look
four "I"..... four "I
Commander outside his home
And Lover inside his home
Read , who is the person that killed by the commander ?
Go ahead, madam
Take your newspaper
Here it is ,Sir
Go to your House Quickly
your wife is alone there
Go quickly
Lakshman
I want him hanged
Do not worry
Vikram was an important member of our committee
I guarantee to you that I'll hang him
And what shall we do with this?
client
I understood
Seriously, No one respects the head of this newspaper
He is nobody
Thank you sir
Sorry
Go ahead
My appointment with my lord JJ
Of course, sir
Good morning, sir
Speak
What service should i provide to you?
Perhaps you have heard about " Rustom Pavri"
Yes
I did not grieve because of the deaths of" Vikram Mekheja
I just feel sad because of Rustom's news
"I've met him once or twice," Nice
Sir " JJ"
Why is this case has been transferred to
"Lakshman Khngana"?
Why?
"Mekheja and Janda are not of the tribe," Cindy
and "Pretty Mekheja" is  doing something
Come to the point
We must help " Parsi"
Do not talk  anything about "Parsi"
You  did not leave anything even your religion too
In order to sell copies of your newspaper
speak directly
What do you want?
I want to find
I mean, I want you to find for
" Rustam" a strong lawyer
Why?
Sir " JJ "
She's very smart
And we must give  "Rustom" an opportunity to save himself
Do not get angry, Sir
You Know that "Rustom" has done the right thing
And they are wrong.
Now , He is alone
The whole society will be against him
How did you come here?
By Taxi
Did you pay the fare?
Yes
OK
Let's start
Thank you very much sir
(Ayrith)
Yes
Read all the newspapers after waking up every day
People should continue sympathize with " Rustom "
"Giora" Society decides at the end
People decide first
Well, sir
"Vikram Mekheja"  was fond of women
He attracted girls by his magic
Commander " Rustom " will be delivered to court today
We have received an request from the Indian Navy
Talk about yourself, applicant
My lord
I'm commander" Pujar"
From the legal Committee of Navy
We ask the court to put
Commander "Rustom Pavri"  under navy forces protection not the police
Why?
My lord
Commanderr "Pavri" is a decorated officer in the Navy
So it's better not to put him with the other criminals
He is a criminal
He killed my brother
He Should be placed under police protection
Who are you?
I am the sister of" Vikram Mekheja "Pretty Mekheja"
I'm sad for the death of your brother, Miss" Mekheja "
But i'll put you in prison if you intervene in the intervene of the court again
Sit
(Peretti)
Procced
When the court need his presence
we will bring him
The marine forces will take this responsibility
Any objection from the
Investigations officer ?
No, My lord
Excuse me, my lord
I want to be under police protection
I do not want any special treatment
because of my position
Excuse me , my lord
I'mr commander" CB Sharyn"
Is it possible to talk with the commander "Pavri"?
Yes
Rustom
Navy supports you
You will be treated as an officer
And there you will have all the facilities
I want to I stay under police guard
This is a direct order
I refuse
Do you know the punishment of this act?
My lord
I ask the court to put me under police guard
please
Thank you, your honor
What about the case of the charge officer?
Investigations still going
Brought the charge sheet as soon as
Yes, sir
The Court will put commander "Pavri"
under police escort for 7 days
What is the relationship between the commander and "Vikram"?
They were friends
In fact, "Rustom" and "Vikram" and "Cynthia" and me were friends
When Madam "Pavri" and "Vikram Mekheja" were close to each other?
They all meet each other together
"Sir, Madam," Vikram "and" Pretty
When commander went to London
these three meet each other together
So I thought that there was a problem
Then both start to meet each other
Where they met each other?
Madam
Everywhere
In the public and private place
Sir
The lady was coming to the house too
Did not seem to you that her arrival is a mistake?
What's wrong with this?
Cynthia " is not a child
she loved my brother
And became addicted to their meeting
then what?
then what happened?
Then what sir?
He read the messages
And broke part of his image in a tantrum
When did this happen?
At about nine in the morning
Then what?
What happened after that?
Commander  said "quite a bit" then went out
London
Miss." Pavri"
Why commander "Pavri" went to London?
He has been sent for an official work
Miss "Pavri "
How much do you love  "Vikram Mekheja"?
Could i leave, please?
I am very tired
Sir
Why we arrest the commander?
We should set him free after giving him a medal
Is everything fine?
Is there any problem?
No
Thank you for all this
I want to ask you some questions about your character
if there is no objection
It's okay if you did not answer
Go ahead
When you met "Vikram Mekheja" for the first time?
Before one and half year approximately
The birthday party of " Brachant Kamd "
♪ I saw you thousands of times ♪
♪ So why this disorder? ♪
♪ Not able to care of this heart ♪
♪ Because there is something special inside you ♪
My breath come and go sith your permission♪
♪ I do not find myself when I was looking for it ♪
♪ Only you are enough for me ♪
Rustom
You enjoy with your beautiful wife a lot
I also want to share
With pleasure
♪ I can't be away from you even for a moment ♪
♪ because these other disorders ♪
♪However we away from each other , we close to each other ♪
♪ This is another disorder ♪
♪ I saw you thousands of times ♪
♪ So why this disorder? ♪
♪  Not able to care of this heart ♪
♪ Because there is something special in our love ♪
Two cups, please
Is every officer of the Navy is flirting like that?
Some of us are respectable
Commander " Rustom Pavri "
Vikram Mekheja
It is a pleasure to meet you
What about if the annual Navy program?
Excuse me
Navy buy ships
This is not a secret
Everything is fine
We will enjoy so much if we had bottles of wine
Vikram
I see you already met " Rustom"
Just now
This is Miss "Cynthia Pavri"
Cynthia, this Vikram Mekheja
Host of the evening party
He is the owner of all this house
Pleasure to meet you
Not only he is the owner
I also I own it
Here she is
My beautiful sister
hello
Pretty Mekheja
My wife " Cynthia"
hello
I am the person who ignites with his arrival the  lamp
Look at the moon which may bow in front of me right now
His mood is flirting with beautiful ladies
Nice
Brother
Yes
Mr. awaits you at home
Excuse us
Goodbye
Who is?
Just a client for Businessmen
Canadian friend
The representation of many Indian companies
Lesen Jans
Thank you
I've met him in many concerts like that
And we became very good friends
sir
Deputy Police Commissioner is on the phone
OK
Commander, Why you went to london ?
official  work
What?
I can not share those details with anyone
according to the official covert action
I'm sorry
It's okey
Are we have  any legal records?
Not advisable, sir
What is the difference in sojourn commander "Pavri"
here or there?
I need those documents for any price
If those papers reach to anyone
we will be in deep trouble
Send someone to his home
Go ahead
Senior lawyer "Saurabh Khan Falla "
I have come to help you, my son,
I've decided I to struggle for you
How come to your mind to do such a big mistake?
it is an open case
"Vikram" have been killed on my hands
And i admit it
Do not say this to anyone unless no one will help you even your god
Rustom
My sources have informed me that "Cynthia" was
with "Vikram" before the accident
And I will tell everything to the people through my newspaper
Do not worry
signed here on this sheet
You want to abuse the reputation of my wife in order to save myself?
Thank you
but no thanks
please
sir
speak
" Rustom "has refused to hire a lawyer to save him
because he does not want to abuse your reputation among the people
Do you want to see  "Rustom" free?
I do not care what people think of me
but I'm ready to do anything to see him free
You will not need to do anything
We just want to do something
Who are you?
Have you found it?
I'm sorry madam
He did not want to meet you today too
I must meet him
This is very important
Madam
There are laws here
If he did not want to meet you
slow down
Can you send my message to him?
sir commander
Your wife sent this
Go
I am so sorry darling
I want to tell you everything
I have harmed you, and I'm regret about that
I am so sorry
I am tired of all this
forgive me
Please talk to me darling
You can not forgive me
I have sinned
So sorry
I am so sorry darling
After returning from England
When you decided to go to "London" again
I did not want you to go
But you left
Then the whole thing started
I spend most of my time with" Pretty"
hello
Nice to meet you
I forget how i was alone when i
spend some time with her
Sometimes "Vikram" also comes out with us
"Pretty" organized a party for my birthday even after my objection
at her palace
When I go there
"I am so sorry," Cynthia
I've to go to "Puna" immediatley
Actually, An accident happened for my girlfriend
but "Vikram" will take care of your
I'll see you after my return
Goodbye
Take care of yourself
Pretty
I am so sorry, " Vikram"
I want to leave
I do not know anyone here
Do not be silly
it is your party
but I do not know anyone
Come
The most beautiful women on the planet does not need to car about it , right ?
but
OK
Just give me 10 minutes
If you still uncomfortable, you can leave
May I?
please
OK
Ladies and gentlemen,
Here she is the party girl " Cynthia
let's congratulate for her
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday dear" Cynthia"
" Vikram " did not want to miss any chance
To praise me and to be closer to me
dear
Can you close your eyes for a moment , please?
(Cynthia)
Trust me
Happy new year
Vikram, I can not accept this
Why?
Did not you like it?
because it is very precious
because it expensive?
Yes
Why did you do that?
Where ..?
It's hard on you to accept
Because it's hard on you ,you make it hard on me
Why waste our time in something trivial?
You are completely crazy
It isn't something trivial
Come on , Look for it
Will you wear it if i look for it ?
Yes, I'll
"Vikram" was coming out with me for food
and parties in the absence of" Pretty"
Here you go
and One day when me and "Vikram"  were alone in his palace
It seems that the sky will rain
For you
(Cynthia)
Slow down !
Are you okay?
Yeah
What happened to you?
It seems that I'm injured a little
Come inside
I'll call the doctor
OK
It's okey
Relax
Go ahead
(Cynthia)
We did not do anything wrong
Do you know darling?
When you leave,I grieved so much
because you did not accept my words
Maybe I hurt you
All this really hurts me
Then what happened?
Strange!
Commander did not want to meet his wife until yesterday
And now, he met her since one hour ago
I do not know what they are doing
What is written in the letter?
It's written that two men has broken his home and
They searched the whole house
How do you know this?
So why did not you tell me?
I do not know what's matter?
Did they took anything?
Nothing
They were looking for something, and perhaps did not find him
Do not worry
Listen to me very carefully
Damn it
Where he hide the documents?
Commander's wife "Cynthia Pavra" said that
her husband shouldn't be punished because of her fault
Read this news only for one rupee
Know the Story of  "Cynthia Pavra" only for one rupee
You said to me he is nobody
but he has bothered me
His newspaper is sold so much
And hard to get his newspaper
Did you read  "Cynthia's statement"?
That woman
(Lakshman)
The attention of people focused on " Rustom's honesty "
because of this newspaper
Go ahead
sir
His honesty will also facilitate our issues " Pretty"
"Rustom" will admit  in front of the court that he killed your brother
And it will end up
Oh relax," Peretti"
Sit
sir
Yes
What did he say?
Commander" Pavri "
Did not you want a lawyer?
Yes , your honor
You are accused of killing, "Vikram Mekheja" in accordance with Article 302
Did you admit it?
No , my lord
I plead
Not guilty
Order..... Order
The case will start on May 25
Will you defend your case on your own?
Yes , my lord
Remember this comandante" Pavri"
You can not petition if you found guilty in this
court due to lack of lawyers with you
My lord
I say to the court that I will not ask the Supreme Court if
i found guilty
Intermission
(break)
I say to the court that I will not ask the Supreme Court if
i found guilty
sir commander
Play alone?
Then you will always win
Let's start the game
You already start the game
It's okey
Was there any working relationship between you
and "Vikram"?
I am a soldier
Not a businessman
Why did not you say anything when
" Vikram " gave  Lady" Pavri " a precious car ?
I want to, but I thought it's not a good thing to do
On the other hand, the friendship did not let me doubt it
Trust can be a very funny thing
Maybe "Vikram" has dared so much because
you did not say anything to him
Of course it is possible
sir commander
Are you in a relationship with any women
after your marriage?
No
sir commander
Is your body parts intact?
You can not doubt that  man who does not enjoy with
another women except his wife
Check
Checkmate
I recongized your strength , Commander
When you sacrificed your queen, I thought you made a mistake.
But now, I understand
It was a premeditated move
It's about winning the game
Whatever it takes the queen or the pawn
♪ Everyone is stranger♪
♪ Even friends and enemies too♪
♪ We got them after leave ourselives for them ♪
♪ love love ♪
♪ I do not care how it comes from ♪
♪ I do not care what's wrong and what is right ♪
♪ You have won" Rustom "♪
♪ Lover is love ♪
♪ Yes love is a weapon ♪
I am very worried about your future," Cynthia"
Why?
The decision of stopping "Rustom's work" in
Navy has been released
Maybe he will divorce you
And "Vikram" also is not alive
Sad
You know?
It's very difficult for a single women to survive without any support
Please
I've an idea
With it you will not need money for your entire life
Do you want to know?
Of course
We need some important secret documents that exist with" Rustom"
And we need it as soon as possible
Look," Cynthia"
We'll give you a million rupees for this
million rupees?
million rupees
"Ed Merle Kamed"
forgive me
I am very worried about your future
"Rustom "has told me all of this before
Listen to me carefully
"Ed Merle Kamed" will meet you very soon
And he will tell you that there are important documents with me
And he will offer you a large sum of money
When hel tell you that , give him this envelope
Is he mad?
Where we will have 50 million?
Vikram Mekheja's share was 50 million
This money must be transfered to this account
And what if i didn't?
"Rossi" asked me to tell you that you know
the result of not transferring this money
He is a blackmiling and opportunist hiding behind
the face of patriotism
Right?
But what will he do with this money?
because I know he will not survive after 14 years
So you tell me
You do not have to think about it
You just have to transfer the money
Yes
" Rossi "is not stupid to hide these important documents
at home under the pillow or inside the couch
And asked me to tell you this too
If you sent your men to our house again
the amount of money will increase
Thank you very much for all this
There is something we do not know
What's in this portfolio?
You did not write anything about it
We have found it with the commander
Tukea
Look at the data files and told me
Where was the commander on the 27th of April
Commander has left from his home at 08:15 am
Was in the ship at 08:45
And was in "Aimbral Mouters" at 10:00
And in Vikram's house at 10:20 am
How long does it take to go to
"Aimbral Mouters "from the ship?
very close
Ten-minute by car
So
Where was the commander between 9:45 and 10:00?
Madam
Yes
I want some information
sir
I knew him when I saw the picture in the newspaper
This navy officer called" Delhi"
Excuse me
Yes
Please go to the phone booth No. 7
Thank you
Sometimes when we cannot pay the small change
we give stamps insted of money
This stamp was released last week
So I remember everything well
Madam , Tell me "Delhi's number"
Yes, sir
Thank you
Well sir
Yes, speak
What's up?
We have a problem
" Rustom " want 50 million
Rustom, Rustom, Rustom
Will "Rustom"  get justice?
Read this only for two rupees
Vikram's towel by 5 rupees
You wont find it afteryour death
First, I want to welcome members
of " Giori" committee
You have a great responsibility
You have to endured it with honesty and sincerity
Commander" Pavri "accused of killing" Vikram Mekheja "
The both sides will provide
witnesses and evidence
And you have to take the decision after listening and understanding
well
Is "Kilraj Bellew Moriah" in court?
Yes
Yes , your honor
You have written in your newspaper
Will commander get justice ?
Do you deny the existence of justice ?
No, sir
Do you know that you insulted the court by asking
the people that question?
No , i just ask a question , your owner
Ignorant about Writing
It becomes a statement when you put a question mark at the end
of a question
Your question doubts in the ability of the court
And so you will be placed in jail
until the end of court proceedings
Take him
Come
Do i come with you ,sir?
The prosecutor submit his opening statement
Law is one for all
Whatever was the son of a rich or an ordinary person or a soldier
Commander "Rustom Pavri" is sitting in front of us in his uniform
He was also in uniform when
he handed himself in to the police after the murder
He exploits his uniform in a perfect way
And you have to take the decision after seeing the human beign
behind his uniform
"Rustom Pavri" on the 27th of April in the morning
fired 3 shots at "Vikram Mekheja" and kill him
Prosecutor will prove this without any doubt
Thank you
That's all, your honor
defense
Your opening
Dear committee" Giori "
My uniform is my habit
My habit the bad and good part of it
As breathing and protect my country
And it's help me to do my job without any fear
That is right
I did not kill anyone
Prosecutor himself will prove this
Thank you
Thank you, my lord
The first witness is doctor," Asher"
Which is the responsible of autopsy at state hospital
I swear that I will speak the truth and no thing else except it
Doctor" Asher"
Can you tell the members of the" Giori"
for any reason "Vikram Mekheja" has been killed?
Because of three bullets
Thank you doctor" Asher"
The members of the "Giori" note that "Vikram Mekheja"
have died due three bullets in the heart
No more questions, your honor
The court requests from the prosecutor not to repeat all the words
Court listeng at the second time as
It's also listening at the first time
Sorry , your honor
defense
Your witness please
No cross examination , your honor
Do you know commander "Pavri"?
Yes
He is a friend of my boss
He came to our office many times
I see
Is he came to "Aimbral Mouters" on the 27th of April?
Yes
He came almost at 09:45
Do you remember how it was his face expressions
when he came to the office?
I remember it well
He was very angry
His blood became a lighted fire
Then what he did?
He asked me if Mr ."Vikram" is in the office?
Then what you answered him.?
I answered him that he did not attend yet
And I asked him, Do you want him in urgent work?
What was his response?
He responded, saying there is no urgent work
I just want to kill him
Then what he did?
And then he went out from there
Thank you
Commander
Your witness , Please
Miss" Rosie"
I want to tell you that everything
you have said so far is a lie
And I hope you tell that to "Giori" and the judge
Objection , my lord
This is misleading and puzzling
This is not understandable
Commander" Pavri"
You can not ask the witness like that
You have to prove that she is wrong
My lord
I do not want to offend to the lady in front of
people in court by proving she is wrong
Commander" Pavri"
Forget Navy's protocol and it's culture for a few
Consider yourself as a notorious lawyer
can ask the witness anything
Ok
Miss" Rosie"
Is it true that you ask me to sit and offered me
tea and coffee when I came to the office?
Yes, it's true
So, shall i understand that you offering
tea and coffee to every angry person?
No
But when you told me that you will kill my boss "Vikram" So
I wanted to offer you tea and coffee to calm your anger
Miss" Rosie"
You were wearing a green shirt that day
And you really look very bad
No
You said to me that I look so beautiful
I was angry
And wanted to kill "Vikram" too
And praised your beauty too
Is this not strange , Miss "Rosie" ?
Objection , My lord
What for?
Leading question , Your honor
Overrode
Then what you did when I came out of there angry?
I was busy in my work
Did it not come to your mind to call the police?
Objection , my lord
Trying baffling
Overrode
Thank you , your honor
Well, leave the police matter
Did it not come to your mind to call your boss and
told him that i'm angry and i want to kill him?
I ..
I was very scared
But you told me that you was busy
I am very sorry, Miss" Rosie"
I was forced to prove in court that you lied
Objection , my lord
Commander tries to missleading "Giora"  by saying that the miss has lied to us
But it's words prove that she is a lier
And for that I apologized to her
Your honor , Please
The commander should.......
"Mr. Khngana"
I think I know what i should do
I'm sorry , your honor
Commander" Pavri"
Your are not a professional lawyer
And therefore i'll overlook some of your mistakes
but I warn you
Please do not take me or this court for granted
If you do something wrong , I'm going to take action
next time
I'm sorry, your honor
"Giori" have to disregard the last words of the commander
Next witness is Deputy Inspector" Patil"
Who is the investigating officer in this case
But it is written in the record  that the officer of this case
is the senior Inspector" Vensend Lobo"
Where is he?
He went to "Delhi" for an urgent work
Did you get the appointment?
Tomorrow afternoon
I did not understand your plan
Relax
Did you know how powerful he is and his
connections with the Influential people?
We will be transfered to "Ondoman Nicobar" if any problem occurred
Nothing will happened
Shut up your mouth
I'll afford everything
Now I want to bring the witness" Bahanah Bai"
who saw this crime with his own eyes
Bahanah Bai
What happened on the 27th of April in the morning?
The house's bell rang
almost  10:00 am
Is "Vikram" here?
Then what happened?
When I entered my boss's room
I saw the gun in the hands of the commander
Then he fired three bullets in front of me
In front of you?
Yes , sir
He has fired three bullets in front of me
What did you do then?
I asked him why did you do that?
And what was his response?
He responded, saying that he has a fleeting relationship with my wife
So I killed him
I did not listen to you well
Is it possible to repeat again?
What was his response?
He responded, saying that he has
a fleeting relationship with my wife
So i killed him
He killed him
I do not have another question, your honor
Rustom Pavri
Your witness
Are you sure that you saw me firing the bullets ?
Yes
Don't you remember?
You have fired three bullets in front of me
I'll repeat my question," Bahanah Bai"
Did you see me shot bullets to Vikram's chest?
Objection , my lord
Commander is trying to scare the witness
Commander " Pavri"
I know that the witness knows well
What is the punishment of lying in the court
I'm sorry , your honor
How was the state of  Vikram's room When you
entered it?
The room was very scattered
Have you eaten breakfast?
Irrelevant question , your honor
It's relveant, your honor
Just give me a minute I will prove to you
please
OK
Thank you ,your honor
Have you eaten breakfast?
Yes, I ate
What did you eat on breakfast every day?
Bhaka "or" vedra Bhai "or" Bohai
Are you a vegetarian?
Yes
What did you eat at breakfast that day?
I do not remember but.......
Perhaps, I ate vegetables
Why did you come to that room?
I have come to ask my boss, what he will eat for breakfast?
Your honor
These images indicate that the meat was ready in the kitchen
Which was Vikram Mekheja's breakfast
And his testimony, stating that no one in the house except them
Bhanah Bai
Now, Don't tell that you have started eating meat since that day
Forgive me, sir
forgive me
Khngana, asked me to lie
I was in the kitchen when I heard the sound of gunfire
When I came into the room I saw my boss lapsed
And the gun was in the hands of the commander
Forgive me, sir
forgive me forgive me......
No another question, your honor
Forgive me
The court's proceedings for today will end on that
"Mr. Khngana"
Will you come to my office?
Come
Do something
How many mosquitoes here!
Come on , Man
This is a prison and not a hotel
shut up
Crazy
How was the case today?
very beautiful
Commander became stronger than" Khngana"
Someone give me this
He expect a calling from you quickly
He has private information
It seems to me that we  printed copies in large quantities
We will see tomorrow
... five rupees five rupees
"Rosie" had been raped by "Vikram Mekheja
And the abortion of the child was in the past year
They said that he was Vikram Mekheja's child
Read it in the Special Edition
Urgent subject
I want the newspaper
Arrest, "Peretti"
Look
Distribute newspapers between them
Come on
It is written that he was Vikram Mekheja's child
"Rosie" had to abort Vikram Mekheja's child
Is "Billy Kibrigg Moriah" in court?
Yes , your honor
I've warned you , Yesterday
However you wrote about the abortion of the witness of this case"  Miss Rosie"
And you also print a medical report
My duty is to bring the truth to the people
Your duty ?
Yes
I see
And you have been distributed your newspaper to the members of the "Giori" for free
I thought they will get bored
in court, so i distributed it
Silence
Order... Order
" Mr.Billy Moriah"
Yes, sir
The court decides that you will be fined up to one hundred rupees and
one day in prison
Come
I'll go
Sir
Silence
" Giori's members "
You shouldn't put this newspaper's articles
in consideration
Your honor
The next witness is " Jamna Bai"
There
I know
Jamna Bai
Yes
Is this true that you work in
commander Pavri's house since three years ago?
And live there too?
Yes
Can you tell what happened
on the 27th of April at house?
I do not know what happened in my house
I'm here in Bombay
Silence
I mean the commander Pavri's house
Yes, at his house
You sould ask me like that
Madam has come in the morning
And talked with commander
Then commander left
Did your madam came in the morning?
Yes, She came
What do you mean?
She wasn't at home for two days
Was your master commander in the house?
He came in the next day from the sea
Ok
Did he ask you with who your madam gone out?
No
He don't ask such a question
Then what did he do?
Then entered into the house
And open the cupboard
And get out the messages
And read some of them
Then drink "Vska" abroad
How did you know that he was drinking "Vska"?
sir
Sometimes I also drink it
Silence
Then what did he do?
Then he broke a picture frame of Madam because of his anger
Your honor
You note that the photo frame was broken
Sorry, your honor
Jamna Bai
Yes
Why does it seem to you?........ Why did he do so?
So what will you do?
What will you do when you know that your wife was with another man
two nights ago ?
Speak
Silence
Order...... Order
Jamna Bai
Yes
This case is not against me
It's against your master
Yes
Do you know who was that man?
Vikram Mekheja
Why you ask me complicated questions?
You should ask me directly
Look, sir
I'm not an intellectual like you
I am ignorant and illiterate
But know this
When the time come for any soldier to left his house in order to protect his homeland
And someone came and take the wife of this solider to his home
Then this man does not deserve to live
And if sir "Rustom"
shoot him then he certainly has done the right thing
Well done
Silence
She is right
Jamna Bai
Yes, sir
Court does not want to know your opinion
You only have to reply to the question
Well, sir
But you told me
What will you do if you know that your wife
slept with this lawyer?
Come
Damn you
Jamna Bai
You too?
How are you?
Use this
Mosquitoes will not bite you
What is this?
Use it
Do you know about the relationship between
"Vikram" and "Cynthia"?
Yes
She was very impressed by "Vikram" and his lifestyle
What was Vikram's response ?
"Vikram" was a man
And if a woman indicated to a man repeatedly
You mean that, "Cynthia"
is the one who tried to make the relationship first?
Of course
I have no further questions, your honor
Commander" Pavri"
Your witness, please
My lord
I will interrogate miss "Pretty" later
OK
Thank you
Your honor
The next witness is" Mrs. Cynthia Pavrai"
"Ms. Pavri"
Were you in a fleeting relationship with "Vikram Mekheja" or not?
Yes
Commander" Pavri"
Your witness, please
"Pretty" has said shortly before that you tried
to make the relationship with "Vikram" first
Is this true?
No
"Vikram" tried first
And, unfortunately, I associated with the relationship
What are the reasons that have been associated
your relationship with "Vikram"?
And then i moved away from " Vikram "
And "Vikram" wrote to me several letters
And sent gifts
I decided to end my relationship with "Vikram
Is it because I nearly go back?
No
I did not want to hide this from you
I was sure that I did something wrong
Objection , my lord
Yes
I was thinking about you ,Are you okay or not?
Continue
There was an injury to your head when
I returned to the house on the 27th of April
Can you tell the court what happened with you?
I will not meet you nevermore" Vikram "
It's good not to call me after today
OK
So you will tell "Rustom" about our relationship or should i ?
This is not a joke, my darling
What did you think?
Did i become crazy of you ?
So I made a relationship with you?
This is wrong
I want to revenge from your husband
He has showed me the power of his uniform
And now I show him the power of my money
And brought you here
This is the real power
Sweethart
Do not missunderstanding
Whatever you did an effort and earned money
A silly man like you will never become a man like" Rustom"
You are a depraved and silly man
Is this all happened because of "Vikram"?
No
I am the only one who is guilty
I should not destroy your trust
Do you feel regret for what happened?
Objection , my lord
This is irrelevent to the case
Overrode
My lord
I want Ms." Pretty Mekheja" for cross examination
Ms" Pretty"
Was Vikram's pistol always with him ?
He had a licensed pistol
I do not know where he took it
You know that he was irritable
And he was out his pistol on the easiest things
Am I right?
Not true at all
OK
Tell me this
Is your brother was interested in poetry?
Yes, he was interested in it
good
Your honor
This note has been found from his room
Can you tell me Is this the handwriting of your brother or not?
Please
Yes
Can you read this letter
in a bass voive , Miss "Pretty"?
Please
My dear," Cynthia"
"Miss" Pretty
loud
So everyone could hear you
I used to think that you grew up in  "London" and you have modern ideas
I do not think that you have to regret about yourself
"Rustom "spend months at sea
And go to foreign countries
and enjoy there
And I know all this
good
Now read this message
Read from here
You scared for free
Complete
A woman can also made
relationship with more than one man without feeling of guilt
OK
Thank you
Think again
Yes
please
Please, Come in
"Amish Shirky" from "OST Home Department "
sir
How can i help you ?
Sir" Bakhchi"
He is senior inspector" Vincend Lobo"
Bombay Police
He is the investigation officer into the murder of" Vikram Mekheja" case
And he wants to talk to you about this issue
I see
Actually , you won't not believe this
But i have expected you
And I'm glad you here
For the first time I hear of a person he is happy with the arrival of the police
Why did you drink?
Tea or Coffee?
Tea is very good
Bring tea
Well, sir
Come Mr.Lobo
Come , please
Yes, sir
He called me on the day that he killed" Vikram Mekheja"
And told me all this
But he missed
Because he did not know that all communications
to the Ministry of Defense are recorded
This evidence proves that "Rustam"  is guilty without any doubt
Can you give me a copy of this record?
Of course, this is for you
Thank you, sir
But why did not you provide this evidence by yourself ?
" Rustom"  is a decorated officer
And there are certin things that you earn Mr.Lobo
And now you have something that
your earned
Rightfully
Thank you, sir
50 million has been transferedl to the mentioned account
Madam , Give me a ticket to "Bombay"  for 10:00 am flight
Sorry, sir
10:00 am flight is full
I can give you a ticket for 02:00 pm flight
OK
Come
Stay here
Get lost
I'm tired of you
Prosecution wants to ask some questions to
commanderr "Rustom Pavri" , My lord
Commander tell me
What is the first thing come to your mind
when you knew about your wife's fleeting relationship ?
I wanted to kill" Vikram"
Is not this a wrong idea?
It is not wrong for me
Why?
Is your outlook and others look different?
I am an officer in the indian navy
Delay is still considered as a serious crime untill today
And so having a relationship with friend's wife is
a serious crime
And the greatest crime is to raise your hand on any woman
And " Vikram" did the both crimes
And therefore a man like "Vikram"  does not deserve to live
Silence....Silence
And for this you killed "Vikram Mekheja"?
No
I just answered your question
A man like him does not deserve to live
But it wasn't my desire to kill him
So What was your desire ?
I just wanted to know why he did this to me
And you has taken the gun from the ship to know that?
Your honor
I want to call the officer "Aimbist" to prove this
You were the indian navy ship
"Mysore " officer on the 27th of April
And i took a pistol from the ship in your attendance
Am I right?
Yes , sir
Officer" Aimbist"
Did you aske me to sign in the record when i
took out the gun that day?
No sir
You have signed in the record on your own
Is it possible for me to get out this gun from the ship
without telling anyone?
Of course, you can
In fact there are keys in your room
And you can get out the pistol and use it
then put it back in it's place
And no one will know any thing about that
Silence...... Silence
I have taken the pistol
only for self defense
Because "Vikram" was losing his consciousness quickly
And his gun was out because of the easiest things
This is a new thing
Do you have any evidence for your words?
Now I will call Mr. "Ranjit Das" to prove this
Who?
What are you doing Mr. "Das"?
Currently I am chief of bartender in the club" Vlendn"
Before this I was a waiter in the" CC Club"
Do you know, "Vikram Mekheja"?
Yes, I know him well
He was a regular member of the club
An accident has happened to you in
January last year
Can you tell me what happened ?
"Vikram Mekheja" and you and your wife and Mrs.
"Pretty" were on that day
They were playing in "Card" room
Is everything equipped ?
Yes
I'll also travel there next month
Are you going to stay in the "Vex" hotel?
How do you know?
Sorry, sir
Depraved
I have sinned
Don't insult me
Dreaded
Wait.... Wait
Control yourself
Go
No, stop
let me
Stop
You mean that the juice has fallen out of your hand
on Vikram Mekheja's shoes unintentionally
And therefore he wanted to shoot you?
Yes
That's all , your honor
Your honor
I just want to ask a question to Mr." Das"
Are there any other witness saw everything that you said a little while ago
except commander and his wife?
Who agrees on your words and telling us that you are honest
See
I do not want to ask more questions, Your honor
You can go
Just a minute Mr." Das"
One minute
Mr." Das"
Can you tell us what the club mangers do when
such an accident happen?
They start to investigate about the accident
And the club committee should investigateon on this issue well
My lord
There has been an organizied meeting after that accident
And this club is very old since 50 years ago
And they deal with these problem very serious
They canceled Vikram Mekheja's membership until the end of the investigation
And the club return his membership after receiving an apology letter
It's the meeting files of the Club
And here is a copy of the apology letter
And it's written in it clearly that "Vikram Mekheja"
became angry and got out his pistol
And he apologizes to the heads of the club, saying he would never repeat such an act
I have proved with this apology letter and Das's words that Vikram
was lose his temper because of the easiest things
And out his gun quickly
I have seen his behavoir before
So I took the gun with me
And when I went in that day
to "Vikram" to talk to him
Vikram
What's up Commander?
You came early
Are you.......?
Are you going to marry  "Cynthia"?
What?
Shall I marry every woman I sleep with ?
Behave well " Vikram"
Do not forget that you are in my house " Rustom"
If i want...?
So what will you do?
A moment and I'll show you
Stop
No
I've fired the bullets
But only for self defense, my lord
sir commander
Is firing three shots necessary for self-defense?
I must show you something to make
you understand that
May I , my lord?
Ok
Thank you
This is an essential guide for the training of Indian troops
Marine
Madam
Can you open page number 24?
Close combat situations
Now, if you could read the way?
Navy says: Hit first, Hit hard
and Keep on hitting
You can fire bullets if someone
want to shoot you
And you have to fire three bullets
at once
Thank you very much Madam
My lord
All of what happened is a reflex action
Give me the paper
sir commander
There has been a conflict between you and  "Vikram Mekheja"
according to your words?
Yes
So why did not Vikram Mekheja's towwl fall from his body
because of the intense conflict?
And there was no pollution on your
whiteuniform according to the police reports?
Sir" Khngana"
Do you want to say that I went to
Vikram's room and spoiled his room with my hands
And got out the pistol and shot him
Then took Vikram's pistol and put it in his hand
And you say all this because there was no
pollution on my uniform?
And because Vikram's towel didn't fall
"Come on Sir" Khngana"
We were not struggling in the mud
Order... Order
No other witness for me , your honor
I now rest my case
Thank you
" Giori" members
You 've heard the evidence of both sides
Excuse me ,my lord
I senior inspector "Vincend Lobo" ,sir
I have an important information for this case
And i want to share it with the prosecution after your permission , sir
Ok
Thank you
Your honor
Inspector "Lobo"  have done a
very smart investigation  and got this evidence
I ask the court to add this to the case
What is the evidence?
Commander "Rustom"  contact a number in"Delhi"
on the day when" Vikram Mekheja" was killed
And he did not mention that call
And he did not tell anyone
He has been contacted with the Minister of Defense
And the call has been recorded
And I want to submit that record to the court
Commander" Pavri"
Yes, your honor
Any objection?
Not at all, your honor
Go ahead
Hello
Are you Mr. "Bakhchi"?
Speaking
You have a call from" Bombay"
Here you are, Caller
Good morning, sir
Who is this?
Commander" Rustom Pavri"
Oh ," Rustom"
How are you?
When you have returned?
I want to talk
Listen to me," Rustom"
I know why you called me
I will ask "Vikram" to meet you and resolve this matter
I'm going to a meet him
But I will not leave him
Silence.....Silence
Commander" Pavri"
Did you admit that this is your voice?
Yes
Now,There is nothing left to prove , your honor
Commander "Pavri" went to his house
Thne he knew about the love story between
his wife and" Vikram Mekheja"
Then he went to the ship
And took the pistol from there
And call the defense minister and told him, "I will not leave him
Then he went to Vikram Mekheja's house after his call
And shoot him with three bullets without mercy
This did not happen unintentionally
It is a clear case,  a murder of the first class
Commander" Pavri"
Do you want to comment on that evidence?
My lord
I want to ask Mr. "Khngana"  in what dictionary
the meaning of the word "I will not leave him" is i will kill him?
Commander" Pavri"
Do not play the word game, and do not try baffling
Your call before the crime proves that
What does the word" I will not leave him" means
Come on ,Commander" Pavri"
You've planted to kill" Vikram Mekheja
Admit it !
I finally rest my case , your honor
Commander" Pavri"
Do you want to say a closing statement?
No, Your honor
I've said everything I had to say to prove
I'm right
Rest my case
Thank you
Silence , please
"Giori" members
You've heard the evidence of both sides
And you have seen all witnesses
Yes
And now, you have to take a decision
Your decision must be
a majority decision
And there is no specific time for you to make the decision
Giori's decision will be heard ,Tomorrow
Come
Shut up
The case have been transferred to" Giori"
Sir
Thank you for choosing me as a member of " Giori"
Let's take a vote before the evidence
OK
Let's start with you
Of course not guilty
Where is the doubt?
Of course guilty
Certainly not guilty
Not Guilty
I do not know
Guilty
Not Guilty
And I'm not even sure
Three members said that commander "Pavri" is guilty
And four members said  he is not guilty
And Two do not know yet
Let's start the discussion
We will win the case
The death penalty or life imprisonment
He should receive the death penalty
He is a killer
I've decided my vote
Guilty
Yes
What...?
What is your evidence ?
That it was self-defense
He is not a murderer
Stop
Silence
Don't fight
Mr. "Khanna" is right
I changed my vote
Not guilty
What's up Commander?
Sleeping is not coming to you
It is not coming to you too
Let's play
No , commander
Maybe you understand that I'm not interested in defeat
You've defeat me in the chess game that day
And so i defeat you in the court today
You've lost this game
Just i will be said because
I did not listen to the truth from you
Sadness because of me is not something good
You did not seem happy to me because of your victory?
And sleeping did not take you because you know that there is something wrong
Let me help you
Mr." Lobo"
This story started since a year ago
"Vikram" was having many ties with the Navy
When he know that there is
an old empty aircraft carrier for 15 years in "London"
He start planning with my chief "Rare Aedmarl kamd"
Then he transfeed me to" London "
When I examined the aircraft carrier
it was completely rotten
So i refused it
Do not worry," Rusom"
We get it with half price
We'll change everything you want
When we take it to India
What do you think?
Here is the" Vikram"
He will tell you everything
Relax
One scotch , please
Sir
Make a good report
And I'll give you a million rupees
And how much you will get?
Why should i hide?
fifty million
Rustom
Think about it a little
You are very normal
And I have other ways too
What happened?
And decided to deliver this matter to my superiors
Because my chief "Rierl Aedmarl"
was involved
And so i went directly to the Minister of defense" Bakhchi "
Who was in London in those days
Yes," Rustom"
Tell me what is the important thing?
Sir, I'm sorry to inform you that there is
a problem with the aircraft carrier
It's completely rotten
Did you tell your boss?
Yes, Sir
I told the officer,"edmarl Kamd" this matter
And I'm sure he is also involved with "Vikram"
in this contract
In fact, he offered me a million rupees too
Just to think about
their offer
million?
Yes
So I wanted to tell you this directly
Vikram also a completely stupid
This is a game of millions
He should offer you two million
But do not worry
I will talk with him
I will ask him to give you two million
Do not worry
And when i did not accept this offer
They transported me in the same night
And they transfered me to the Indian Navy ship "Mysore"
before filing a complaint against them,
Which was heading abroad for 6 months
Vikram had used my wife to revenge from me
And here I'm , sir" Lobo"
The person who talks about protecting his homeland
was not able to protect his house
It was not Cynthia's fault
My personal life was on one side
and in the other hand, the aircraft carrier
This is the reason for which I plan
everything
I want to talk.....
Listen to me
I know why you called me
I will ask "Vikram" to meet with you and resolve this matter
I'm going to meet him
But I will not leave him
And anotherthing
I have a copy of the london aircraft carrier
report
Which proves that theaircraft carrier was moldy
How much our country lost because of it
I'll see how you are going to save yourselves
" Rustom", Do not be foolish
I'll disclose you all
I have told you before....
I just did not know that my call will be recorded
And "Bakhchi" will provide half of that
call to the court and revenge from me
"When I got to the house," Vikram
What's up Commander ?
You have come early
It seems that your wife......
So why you did not disclose
"Bakhchi "and" Kamd "in front of the court?
Civilians must not lose their faith in
Marine ,sir "Lobo"
I did not want to abuse the reputation of the Navy
because of some corrupt officers
And a problem with the protection of our homeland will happened
I did not want all this
What about the copy of the aircraft carrier's report?
I do not have any copy of the report
It was just a bluff
My only goal was not letting
those rotting ship come to the states
Aircraft carrier will come to the Navy
But after change all i want
Sir commander, What if  "Giori" decided that you are guilty tomorrow?
No, sir" Lobo"
I'll come out tomorrow
" Giori "will help me tomorrow
How could you so sure thus?
You are sitting here
You.....
And " Giori"
And People
Everyone knows I'm guilty
But they admit that I should not be punished
And "Vikram" deserved to die
And I do not deserve punishment
Of course he is guilty
Is this a final decision?
Yes
Ok
Let's inform the court
Is the decision of "Giori" a majority decision?
Yes
"Giori" have found commander "Rustom Pavri" who accused
of the murder of" Vikram Mekheja".......
With eight members voted
Not Guilty
Thank you
Stay away
Congratulations Commander
Thank you
You have succeeded because of my newspaper
Pretty
We will criticize the case in the Supreme Court
Definitely
But I do not need you
Let's go to your homes
Thank you
Darling
Can you ever forgive me ?
♪ I can not live without you ♪
♪ Really going to die without you ♪
♪ That's sure ♪
♪ Smile and Cry only come from you ♪
♪ You also my life ♪
♪ That's sure ♪
♪ See you in every breath ♪
♪ My death is certain without you ♪
♪ I can not live without you ♪
♪ Really going to die without you, that's sure ♪
♪ That's sure ♪
Translated By MT