Vidhi!
- Brother, are you recording me?
Now this video will go to mom.
Mom..
Brother.. I'll also
tell dad you use his razor.
Dad.. Catch brother.
Catch brother.
- I've caught him.
I've caught him..
Let go, Dad.
Dad, let go.
Mom, you have to see
what Vidhi did.
Is it mom's?
- No..
Then..
Everyone uses their mom's
lipstick in the hostel.
But honestly, I've never done it.
N-now close your eyes.
What's going on?
What've you done, Vidhi?
Give mom's lipstick, come.
Where did you get it from?
Go to your room
and brush your teeth.
Dad, don't remove it.
You look so pretty.
Thank you.
Did you talk to Shivam?
What's the point of dealing it?
We have decided it anyway.
Nitin, don't tell me
you can't do it.
No.. I can do it.
Nitin, I'm talking to you.
Nitin!
Don't you think this is important?
Fine. Just remember
it's all because of you.
You hard dark moustaches.
Everyone in hostel says,
the more you shave
the better your moustaches.
Isn't this a college photograph?
Yes, final year
if I remember right.
Was this before proposing to mom?
No.. After that.
Mom was saying that you..
- I thought I'll come with you.
Where?
- Manali.
Manali!
- No, hostel.
But, I'm going to hostel
with my friends.
And I'll be bored with you.
You too will be bored with me.
Why bored?
It'll be a nice drive.
And you can direct me
by looking at the map on the phone.
Okay.
Where are you going, Nitin?
- With Shivam.
With his friends?
No, just Shivam and I.
I have a feeling
he'll tell Shivam today.
Am I patient?
I've always been patient with him.
I sometimes feel it's been
so many years
I still haven't been
able to figure him out.
Let's see what happens.
Vidhi! You've not finished
your milk yet!
Mom, I want chocolate.
Yes, the same route.
But my dad wants to come with me.
'Hmm, Daddy's boy!'
- Shut up!
You sissy! Mom's boy!
'When will you meet me?'
Yes, I'm meeting you
in the evening.
'Then you'll meet Natasha too.'
Don't irritate me.
Listen, did someone complain?
'Did anyone find
our magazine bunch?'
Are you crazy?
- 'Then it must be Shubh.'
'The fat guy.'
- Yes!
He takes advantage
of being a senior.
Shivam!
- I'm coming, Dad.
Okay, bye, pal.
- 'Okay, bye.'
I'll meet you in school.
Okay, bye.
Yes!
Are we on the right track?
Yes. Google Maps says
we're on the right track.
Six to seven more hours.
- Yes.
When is the IPL beginning?
- IPL? Next week.
Can you watch TV in the hostel?
TV? We watch it
on the mobile phone.
Who needs TV?
You know the cricketer
Steven Davis.
- What happened to him?
Someone was saying
that actually
he's..
he's playing well.
Do they show you movies
on Saturdays?
Only classics.
Boring black and white.
Which game are you playing?
- Clash of Clans.
We used to play Donkey Kong.
- Never heard of it.
Oh, no!
Come..
Yes.. Come..
Carefully.
Stop. Yes.
Is it good?
- Yes.
Dad.. - Yes.
That's him.
Who?
- Aditya Taneja.
Is he a friend of yours?
Do one thing, pal.
Your boss, the transporter..
What does he do?
- He's a celebrity, Dad.
Do you know how much money
did he make?
He has two girlfriends
on two different shows.
And he dumped them both on TV.
- How do you know all this?
General knowledge is my strength.
Wait a second.
What happened?
- Aditya Taneja. Please see this.
Is he a model?
- He's not a model.
Is he the actor-type?
No. He's a TV
reality show winner.
He's a TV celebrity.
Are reality shows a full-time job?
- Do you have a pen and paper?
Pen..
No.
Excuse me, do you have a pen
and paper?
Aditya, Hi!
Hi! - Can I have your autograph?
- Yes.
Sure.
What's your name?
Shivam.
- Shivam, right.
Isn't he so cool?
Shivam, I've to talk
to you about something.
Hey, Shiva! Is that your dad?
Say 'Hi' to him.
Dad, would it be okay if my friend
came with us to Mussoorie?
Which friend?
T-that boy?
I offered the ride.
How can a complete stranger
come along with us?
But he's not a stranger.
The whole nation knows him.
If he's such a big celebrity,
where's his car?
How do I know, Dad?
Please let him come.
Shivam, please try and understand.
I'm driving you
to school for a reason.
I've to talk to you.
Come. Come and sit in the car.
You always have your way.
We'll go to grandma's.
After meeting her,
we'll go forward.
Okay?
Oh, no! I lost my missile.
There are cheat codes in all these.
Do you know about cheat codes?
Yes, of course.
How?
Did they exist during your days?
Are you really asking that?
Dear, we invented them.
What do you mean?
I mean..
I know people
who wrote these codes.
Where are your friends now?
In the US?
And how did they do all this?
Darn! We forgot our seat belts.
Don't tell mom.
She is wild.
Just wait I'll tell you.
In those days
we didn't have the internet.
So we couldn't download
the cheat codes.
So we used to write it.
And then we used to store it
in floppy's
and share it with each other.
Do you know about floppy disk?
Floppy's.
- Floppy's!
Dad, how old are you?
100!
Grandma.
My child is here!
Let me see.
They don't give you food
in your hostel.
You have lost weight.
And why did you come
after so many days?
Don't you miss your grandma?
I keep telling dad.
He doesn't get me.
Really!
Come we will talk to him.
Greetings, Mom.
- Greetings, my dear.
It took you so long
to reach here.
Your dad and I have been
waiting for a while.
Come.
Come inside.
Get the luggage.
No, Mom.
We are leaving now.
I have to drop Shivam
to the hostel.
At least have food and go.
- Yes.
Let's go, dear.
What did you all tell Vidhi
and come?
From morning I called
nearly five to six times.
Why didn't they come till now?
When will they come? And then
I hope you're not lying to me.
Now why will I lie
in this old age?
Come.
Mom just left
leaving you this way.
Dad, I can't believe this.
You're still using this razor.
I remembered my childhood.
When I used to use it
stealing it from you.
Now Shivam does it with me.
Dad.
I always wanted to tell you
something about myself.
But I did not have courage.
Whenever I had courage
I stopped myself
for some or the other reason.
Today I initiated this talk
not
because you cannot talk.
It's time for me to say it.
I was never attracted to women.
I am gay.
I just thought I'll tell you that.
Do you remember
when you hit me once?
You saw me cry
and gave me a hug.
I didn't want to loose
that feeling ever.
Sorry, dad
if I have disappointed you.
I just want to tell you that..
Shivam, I..
I was about to tell you.
I didn't want you to know
this way.
That's the reason
I came along with you.
I had thought Sunita
all the good habits.
And she got married.
Now I need to teach everything
to this new girl.
If salt is less do take it.
You're not eating anything!
There is mango pickle.
There is sweet chutney as well.
Sambar.
- Yes, Sambar.
You will like the Sambar.
What happened, dear?
You're not eating anything.
When you get back to hostel
you will remember
how tasty was grandma's food.
If you would stay for some
more time, he would feel better.
You all come to Delhi.
It's done now.
In this old age in such a
big city, noise all over
how will we feel comfortable?
And you are aware
about your dad's health.
All the doctors have gone
to the hospital.
No, we are fine here.
Were you happy with dad?
I will tell you the truth.
Who thinks about all this
in the old age?
Your dad and I used to fight
over silly matters.
And now after coming here
we don't remember anything.
Now I just fear about one thing.
Loneliness? - No,
my knees and your dad's weight.
If something happens to him
how will I carry him?
So you think this about dad?
And his favourite yoga.
'Pawanmuktasan.'
That's the only voice
which comes out from him.
I get satisfied that
he at least says something.
When he leaves there won't
be any sort of noise here.
Just think.
When I was young who knew that
I will crave for someone's fart.
You should always do the things
which makes you happy.
What happened to him?
He was so happy when he came.
Nothing.
His holidays are coming
to an end.
Maybe that's the reason.
Stay blessed, dear.
Come soon.
Mom give a thought
about coming to Delhi.
Water.
What?
One bottle of water.
Here.
Shivam,
that's a celebrity right?
Yes.
Hey, man!
- Hey.
How are you?
- I am good.
Sorry, man. I didn't mean
to stop your car.
No problem. Mussoorie, right?
- Yes.
Get in.
- Really!
Thanks.
Thanks, man.
Shivam speaks highly of you.
But I couldn't recognise
you in the beginning.
It's all right.
Anyway, my shows are not meant
for your generation.
Sorry.
But that's the truth.
Actually this show
was of that kind.
But this time
I won't be able to stand myself.
That's the reason I escaped
from there.
Production also has no clue
of when I would return.
Why?
Why are you running?
You could do it.
The truth is that
I am tired of the same things.
Now it's too much. I can't do it.
Now I want to know
what my life is all about.
What I want to do..
What is the purpose
of my existence.
Therefore, I didn't bring
my phone with me this time.
Wow!
Stop! Stop! Please!
I really need to capture this.
I really need to get this man!
Shivam, I just..
I wanted to..
And what about mom?
We are getting a divorce.
Divorce!
And no one informed
me anything till now.
That's why I am with you.
And what about Vidhi?
She's too young.
What will she understand?
I and your mom
will handle her.
Arun and his friends are nearby.
I will join them in their car.
They also have an extra seat.
Won't you come with me?
You have already
spoken to me.
Now there's no point
coming so far.
It's okay.
They are letting me to know
where to meet them.
They will call me in sometime.
Hello! - 'Hello!'
- Yes, Arun. Tell me.
'Where are you?'
- There was network problem.
Where are you people?
A landslide occurred here.
All the roads are closed.
We are standing here,
in middle of the street.
A little ahead.
Oh! Okay, fine.
I will see you there.
Okay then, bye.
What happened?
The road has been
blocked due to landslide.
They are on the road.
It's few miles ahead.
Landslide!
- Yes.
I have reached at the bridge.
Okay.
Please stop the car..
Yes. Two minutes.
Yes, I see you guys.
Okay, bye.
You stay here.
I will meet them and come back.
How are you?
How were your holidays?
- It was really good.
How was yours?
- It was awesome.
What happened? How long will
it take to clear the roads?
Only God knows!
It was a landslide.
According to me it will
take minimum 12 to 15 hours.
12-15 hours!
It will take the whole night.
There are few lodges in Sinhola.
Many people are
going there today.
Okay, I'll get my bag.
- Okay! - Sure!
I want to talk to her
just once.
The roads will remain closed
till tomorrow morning.
We will have to stay
somewhere nearby today.
What happened?
Nothing.
I'm going to stay with my friends.
Let's just find a place
to stay for tonight.
After that you can
go with your friends.
And I will return
back to Delhi.
Hey! What happened to him?
We need three rooms.
Two of us..
That's true.
Okay. See you in the room.
Hey, guys.
Here's your room key.
- Thank you, sir.
That one, right here.
Tell your driver to unload
the luggage.
Maybe you can go for dinner
dinner and come back.
See you around!
What happened?
I don't want you to stay here.
I will leave in the morning.
Only three!
What are you saying?
There are total seven, for sure.
Just see her!
- Oh, heck! Ten!
She's just okay.
What?
- Are you sure..
You just want things
like this only.
I won't leave you.
I will see.
I'll get that.
Hey! What's up!
What happened?
Should I leave?
You want to stay with Aditya?
Sorry,
can you give us a minute.
Sure!
You're misbehaving
since morning.
I'm not going to tolerate this.
Then why are you
staying with him?
What's wrong with you?
Only two rooms were available.
And you went with your friends.
Do I even know this guy?
You were after me
to bring him here.
I understand everything.
I am not a kid.
Okay, whatever you're
thinking that is right?
I knew it.
- Superb, now leave.
And send Aditya inside.
Shi..
Have you seen Shivam?
Hey, Shivam!
Shivam!
Stop the car.
No!
Shivam, stop!
Shivam!
Shivam,
what are you doing?
What is this stupidity!
Are you out of your mind?
What are you doing?
What have I done to you?
Did you ever think about us?
That's why you
sent me to hostel.
Far from everyone.
Did you ever ask me whether
I want to go or not?
You are also leaving mom alone.
She used to tell me
that you're the best.
What will I explain to Vidhi?
What will I tell her?
I feel ashamed to address
as my dad.
I feel weird even
standing nearby you.
Even grandpa must
be ashamed of you.
It does not matter
if he is dumb.
This is who I am!
I can't change myself.
Do you think it's easy for me?
I can't live like that.
If you and Vidhi were not there
I would have killed
myself a long time ago.
You know what!
You should have!
Pal, tell me something.
One tends to be gay
in childhood itself
or you turn into one
after you grow up?
Pal, then what will happen
to Natasha?
I am not talking about myself.
Forget it.
- Tell me!
Let it be, pal.
Maybe, some other time.
Pal, I won't tell anyone.
I swear!
Let it be, pal.
What happened, pal?
Nothing much.
I am gay.
- What?
Stop kidding, pal.
- You heard me.
Holy crap!
It's cold here.
Why are you getting scared?
What will I do?
What will you do if a girl tells
you that she likes you?
If you don't like her,
you'll turn her down, right?
It's simple, right?
You won't get scared like this.
Will you?
What is the need to get
scared about it?
By the way, you're not my type.
I don't find you attractive.
- What?
Did you get offended?
You want me
to find you attractive? - No.
Don't worry.
You are safe.
But, Nitin, you are married.
You got kids.
Does Shivam know about this?
- Yes.
I just told him today.
He has not taken it well.
Darn it!
What are you blabbering?
Did he tell you all this?
What will happen
to your mom, pal?
I am not feeling sad
about whatever happened today.
But I can't see
my family fall apart.
I just need my childhood
family back.
Being gay and so on..
I don't need it.
Don't worry, pal.
Often, it turns out
to be a disease.
It's not.
I googled it.
Hey, give me your
telecommunication device.
Hurry up.
- What did you ask for?
Give me your phone.
Pal, please don't share this
with anyone.
Do you want your dad to be a man?
Then let me have it.
Look here.
Baba Bengali.
- What about him?
Have you lost it?
All this is nonsense!
Let's not get into all this.
- Your dad will bring a stepdad.
Let's rush before that.
Pal, I told you all this because
I had to get it out of me
and because you
are my best friend.
Don't irritate me.
Let's go.
Go, pal.. Come on, go.
- Are you out of your mind?
He'll scold me and chase me away.
- He won't.
Look at his face.
Pal, I am telling you
he's the sage's follower.
Come on, pal.
Go now.
I said, go!
Go!
Sir.
Yes, dear.
How can I help you?
I..
Where can I find
the bottled water?
Go to your room.
I'll have it sent right away.
Come on, pal!
Come with me.
Let me show you.
Come on.
"Twelve months.."
- Mister.
I'll have it sent right away.
Pal, how do you know
about Baba Bengali?
Everyone knows about him.
Even at school.
You are the only one
who doesn't know.
Where there is a will,
there is a way, dear.
Like what? - Did you notice the
tattoo on the receptionist's hand?
Yes. - Did you?
- Yes.
That is the mark of Baba Bengali.
Pal, all that is fine.
But what if that receptionist
informs my dad about it?
He won't, pal.
It's a secret society.
And hereafter, even you..
Come with me.
Shivam.
We begin the herbal treatment
from where allopathic doctors
quit their treatment.
There are three ways
to have a healthy body.
'Vata', 'Pitta', and 'Kapha'.
Consume the herbal medicine
and remember it.
Tell me your problem.
Well, suppose I suffer a headache.
Suppose someone suffers
from a stomach ache!
Yes.
- Even a toothache.
And..
Suppose one feels cold?
Gooseberry is the key to health.
And suppose someone
is gay?
- Gay.
Being homosexual.
It's a very dangerous disease.
Dangerous than AIDS.
It pollutes the culture,
body, and mind.
It is a gift
from the western countries.
Consume the herbal medicine
and remember it.
Do you have the medicine
for that?
Don't doubt.
If you doubt,
you won't find a solution.
Trust me.
You'll find the solution.
Do you suffer from this disease?
- No.
But you won't share it
with anyone, will you?
Don't doubt.
I am the step to reach
the solution.
Mix a spoonful with the solvent
and get him to drink it daily.
Solvent?
- Liquid.
Such as water, juice, wine.
Hey, Mr. Benevolent!
Why did you donate the watch?
Forget that.
How do I get him to drink it?
Mix it with solvent and get
him to drink. Such as wine.
There's no one.
Let's go.
Pal, do you think it will work?
Pal, I don't think half will do.
Add the whole thing.
What's up, guys?
Well, Shivam.
Your dad is looking for you.
By the way, what are you
guys doing here?
Actually, we are..
- We were coming to meet you.
Is that so?
You are the star of nonfiction
entertainment. - What!
Come again!
- I meant, the reality TV show.
Then tell it like that, pal.
All my friends are too desperate
to meet you. - Is that so?
Sir, please come with me.
- Is that so?
Where to?
- All are in our room.
Please.
- Then let's go.
Let's go.
Where are my admirers?
Come with me, I will introduce you.
- Let's go, pal.
Shivam, I'm sorry to
have lost my temper.
The extent of problem you had
in dealing with what I said
I had to gather much more
courage than that to break
this news to my teenage son.
For a long time, I was in doubt.
I was even confused about myself.
I was wondering what's
happening with me.
I befriended..
I befriended even girls.
In college, I met your mom.
I liked her company.
And I confused a best friend's
friendship as love.
Then we got married,
but nothing changed.
I didn't want to confess
and ruin Nupur's life.
Then you came into our lives.
That was the happiest
moment of my life.
And then Vidhi.
I had felt that I could take
control of myself.
Because I had the two of you.
People saw us
as a perfect family.
Me as a good husband.
But I had been shattering
from within.
I can't tell you how it feels
to lead a false life every day.
I just want you to know that
nothing has changed between us.
I am still your father.
Now it doesn't matter to me
what people think about me.
What matters to me
is what you think about me.
I just want everything
to be like before.
I am going to meet Arun.
Oh, my! - What happened?
Nitin! What's wrong?
We are even in this matter,
not bad, Nitin.
C-Can you please call the doctor?
- Oh, no! I'm sorry..
I-I'll do something about it.
Oh, my God..
Mister!
Listen up!
Oh, God! Please wake up.
Mister, please get up.
The person living with me
is feeling unwell. - What?
His stomach
is in excruciating pain.
Do you have any medicines?
Everything will be closed now.
- Do you have a first-aid box?
I have to check.
- Check and get it upstairs.
Room number 201.
I'm in room number 201.
Come fast.
- I will check.
Where is the first-aid box?
Sir..
I want to talk to you.
I guess it's stomach pain.
I think he ate stale food
while travelling.
But that's okay.
Give him a table spoon
of both these medicines.
But what is it?
- It is a strong medicine.
Whenever I have a stomach ache,
I drink it.
He should be fine
by tomorrow morning.
What if he doesn't recover?
- We'll call the doctor then.
I think there is no water.
I will get it.
Shivam..
Listen, wait!
Be with your dad,
he needs you.
Listen,
I know I have no right to say it.
But when he couldn't find you,
you should've seen his face.
He was extremely worried.
Shivam..
I understand it's difficult for you
but your dad is a great guy.
He is trying to reach out to you.
Not everyone takes such efforts.
Ask me, I know.
I haven't met my family
from 15 years.
I miss them and my dad too.
And it happened only because..
He expected certain things
from me and I couldn't fulfil it.
I couldn't be the son
he wanted me to be.
And you are doing exactly
what I did with my dad.
Just don't lose him, all right?
And listen..
Don't get yourself in a situation
where you want him to be around
but he isn't there for you.
Shivam..
He is feeling better now.
Are you leaving?
Do you want to tell him something?
Don't worry, I will..
I'm here for your dad.
No matter what, I will be
a part of the basketball team.
Leave it.
I hope we get chicken for lunch.
Sure, you only think of chicken..
- You're right. - ...nothing else.
You want to eat everything.
Hey, Shivam.
Come on.
Yes, Vidhi, I am fine.
How are you?
- I'm fine too.
Dad, how's your stomach ache now?
It's okay now.
How do you know about it?
- Mom told me.
How did mom..
- Dad, even I have a stomach ache.
Do you have a stomach ache too?
I don't want to go to school.
- Darling, give it to me.
Hello.
Nitin, how are you feeling?
Shivam called me.
- I'm feeling better.
Did he say anything else?
I won't go.
- Listen, I'll call back, okay?
She started with her excuses again.
I will leave now.
Can I drop you somewhere?
- No, you can leave.
I might go to my house.
I'll also go and meet my dad.
Thank you.
- Anytime.
See you.
- Take care.
"Carry me on your shoulders."
"Take me on a journey
through the polders."
"Gathered clouds in my backpack."
"My pockets are filled with stars."
"I'm still a young boy."
"The world is vast."
"I'm yet to learn."
"I'll be ready when it's my turn."
"Halt someplace and reminisce."
"It will spark memories in bliss."
"Embrace all the happiness
in life."
"Let the wind touch,
let everything revive."
"I'm still a young boy."
"The world is vast."
"I'm yet to learn."
"I'll be ready when it's my turn."
"Everyone returned except you."
"Days passed by, nights went blue."
"Make your house of dreams"
- Hey, Shivam.
"with hope."
- Don't you want to get down?
"Don't be scared, you've a lot
of scope." - Be brave. Come on.
"I'll sleep" - Come. No?
You're a big boy now, right?
"in your arms like a child."
"I'll fly under your wings"
"in the wild."
"Make me sit on your shoulder."
"Take me right away."
"I am a young boy."
"This world is vast."
"I haven't learnt"
"to fly yet."
Hello, Shivam.
Well done, dear.
I learnt that you topped
in Mathematics.
Mom is so proud of you.
Listen to me.
I am coming for your ceremony.
Do you need anything?
Dear, I did tell you
about Mr. Ayush, right?
Even he will come with me.
He has been longing to meet you.
Do meet him.
Shivam?
- What about dad?
English topper from class eight,
Tejbeer Singh.
Maths topper from class nine,
Shivam Swaminathan.
Come on, Shivam!
Social Science topper
from class nine, Ayush Tulsia.
Dad!
Congratulations.
Wow!
It's beautiful.
I am so proud of you.
Hi, Shivam.
Congratulations.
You did well.
Hey, Nitin.
- Hi.
Good to see you.
I hope you are having a good time.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
Why are you addressing me as ma'am?
Come on! You can call me Sonica.
Okay, ma'am.
Sonica.
Right. You didn't come
the previous time. We missed you.
You know what?
I have to leave.
I'll catch you later.
- Sure. - All right. Come, Shivam.
Yes, ma'am.
Smile, please!
Thank you, guys.
Thank you very much.
We have come from Delhi and..
Where can I meet you?
Can I meet you? - Sure.
Living in the art..
- Definitely.
Ayush, I'll just be back.
- Sure..
Starry night!
How is Vidhi?
She is fine.
I dropped her at the hostel.
She does create a fuss
before going to the hostel.
You didn't tell me
that you are coming, Nitin.
Neither did you.
Come on.
Stop pretending.
You know everything.
Isn't he a bit old for you?
At least he is straight.
Until now!
Ouch!
Where are you staying?
- He has his own house here.
Mountain view. - Everything
has a mountain view out here.
It's known as a hill station.
Mom, you came!
Very well done, dear!
After all, he is my son.
Hey, you were never
so good in studies, Nitin.
Nupur, what are you talking about?
You know that I was!
Your dad
just keeps saying all this.
Hi, I am Ayush Deewan.
So, Shivam.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
So, what next?
What are your plans for the day?
Why don't we celebrate?
I have a huge house here!
You will love it!
Isn't it, Nups?
Actually, dad is taking me
and my friends out for dinner.
So, what about tomorrow?
I have classes tomorrow.
We are allowed for outings
only on Sundays.
Okay, Sunday is perfect!
He doesn't want
to come with you.
Nitin, one second.
What is happening, Nitin?
Why were you so rude to him?
He was just trying too hard.
Shivam didn't..
- So?
Come on, Nitin.
We are all trying hard.
Do you think it was
very easy for me?
But I am trying, right?
Why does it always have to be
about choices you have made?
Why is he calling you Nups?
I guess
I am protective about you.
I want you to be okay.
Don't worry about me.
I'll be okay.
Shall we leave?
Bye, Mom.
- Bye, my dear!
Take care of yourself.
Okay?
Yes.
What happened to you
all of a sudden?
I saw your mom
with someone else.
It's okay.
We'll deal with this also.
Yes, I need to get out of here.
Let's get a drink.
- Let's go.
Dad.
Shall I ask you something?
Ask me anything.
Do you find all guys attractive?
Do you find all girls attractive?
Not all.
- Same!
Do you have anyone in life?
I mean, someone special.
Do you have anyone in your life?
Someone special?
- Dad, don't irritate. Tell me.
Not yet.
Your turn.
Someone special?
No!
Who was she?
- Who?
The one you were staring at
again and again
at the party.
- Oh, that one?
Natasha.
- Natasha!
Does she know?
- What?
That you like her.
Of course not, Dad.
- Why?
Hey..
- Who will tell her? Your mom?
109.
This is 109.
- How do you know?
Follow me.
Come with me.
- Dad, let's go.
What's the worst thing
that could happen?
Come on!
Wait a minute.
Yes.
Dad, what are you doing?
Shivam!
- Hi, Natasha. I am Nitin.
My dad. - Oh! Hello, sir.
- Hi.
I just wanted to meet you.
Shivam keeps talking about you.
- Dad.
Which class do you study in?
Ninth grade, sir.
Nice!
Will you get down?
I will tell you everything.
Chouhan sir!
Is he still a cricket coach?
Chouhan sir.. - He'd once caught me
while getting into this hostel.
He will catch you again
if you talk so loudly.
Okay..
It's a good thing that we met.
I don't know when I will come
to Mussoorie next.
I thought I'll come today.
- Dad!
It was nice meeting you, Natasha.
Take care.
- Bye, sir.
I am sorry.
- It's okay.
Also, I wanted to say something
from a really long time.
And is this the way to say it?
Actually, I wanted to say that..
I wanted to say
that I really like you.
You, what?
I really like you.
- Okay, go now.
Follow me.
Even I wanted to tell you something
from a really long time.
I like you!
I..
I really love you.
Dad, are you okay?
Hangover.
Why do you think
they called us here?
I don't know.
She said she wanted to catch up
when I met her at the party.
I think this is why
she has called me here.
Sir, ma'am is calling you inside.
Hi, Sonica.
Have I asked you to sit down?
Sit.
Shivam, I don't even know
where to begin.
Never before have we been
so embarrassed
because of a student's parent!
Sonica, what I..
- Please don't interrupt me.
Don't you feel ashamed
of doing such a thing?
Shivam, do you have any idea
what your father did last night?
I did a few things last night.
I don't know which one
you are specifically referring to.
For God's sake! The girls
hostel at 11'o clock in the night!
The watchman saw you!
You even left
the bloody ladder behind!
As an adult, I would expect him to
behave a little more responsibly.
You find this funny!
Ma'am, you don't know..
- You should be ashamed of him!
Ma'am, you don't understand.
He..
He is gay.
Ma'am, how I wish he was
interested in women but he is not!
He is gay!
What?
You don't mean to come up
with a joke like that
and get away with it, do you?
No!
- Yes, ma'am.
My father is gay
and I am proud of him.
No matter what
I always will be.
He was with me yesterday
as I wanted to meet someone.
Whatever it is, I am extremely
upset about all this.
Mr. Nitin, you have jeopardised
the reputation of my school
for your atrocious behaviour!
And I am going to need a written
apology from you for this.
And Shivam, you are suspended
from the school
for an entire week
for your complete..
But Sonica..
- What, Sonica?
Please address me as ma'am!
Okay, Sonica..
Ma'am, it was I who..
That will be all.
I said, that will be all!
So, what now?
Home?
Your mother will scold you.
You got suspended because of me.
But that's cool!
A week's extended holiday.
Suspension.
Dad, how far is Manali from here?
Can we drive there?
Get in.
"We have moved on."
"If someone comes along with me."
"We will meet again"
"even if we get lost."
"A problem is solved."
"We have witnessed a new morning."
"It was drowning somewhere."
"It was my breath."
"There were many problems."
"It seemed very childish
with you."
"It seemed of no use."
"I got everything I lost."
"My eyes are opening slowly."
"It is awake now."
"A problem is solved."
"We have witnessed a new morning."
"So, come!"
"Let's go together."
"Come on with me."
"Let's fill the new times"
"with the new moments and dreams."