The Father of our Nation, Mahatma Gandhi
wasn't just the first 'Satyagrahi'...
...but, also the first
'cleanliness activist' too.
Even though it's been 100 years
since Chaparan Satyagraha...
...we still couldn't get rid
of the filth in our country.
But now, under the leadership of
Prime Minister Narendra Modi...
...Gandhiji's dream of clean
India will become a reality...
...on his 150 birth anniversary,
that is 2nd October, 2019.
This is our small
contribution to his campaign.
Our heartfelt
homage to Gandhiji.
Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. Enjoy The Flick.
Once she starts insisting,
there's no way to turn her down.
You just can't say no to her.
So why don't you go
for a third one?
I am not Farah Khan.
She's already had triplets.
But here, keep continue...
And if you're so fascinated by the idea
then why don't you try for another one?
Forget it...
I've my hands full with
one 'Ninja Hattori'.
By the way, Chulni, how is
your mother-in-law's knee?
It's as good as new.
No wonder she's been racking
her brains a lot recently.
My mother-in-law has
lost her marbles.
She makes me slog over the
sewing machine all day.
I see...
Well, speaking of machines, I've heard
Neelam goes on and on like a machine.
What have you been feeding
your husband these days?
Tell us too.
She can't stop smiling.
- Tell us too.
- Spill it out.
Our husbands fall
flat on the bed...
...as if they were moving
mountains all day.
Tell us...
Where did you find
this magical herb?
Tell us.
Oh, my... where did
you get that done?
Well, last month he took me
to Delhi... for sight-seeing.
We must get one soon too.
Normally, men get us pregnant
and then forget all about us.
Listen to my
mother-in-law? But why?
She just needs a reason...
You'll get a stomach-ache...
Who is he?
Oh, my...
That rascal intentionally
flashed his light on us.
- You are right.
- Rascal.
No, you go, I can't come?
Sonu has made a mess at home.
Hey madam, won't
you let me pass?
If I flash my dipper
now, you'll get furious.
Keep flashing your
dipper now. Rascal.
- Jaya...
- You taught him a good lesson.
- Bye.
"There are many
beautiful girls.."
"But all eyes staring at you.."
Oh my, God! Oh my, God!
"But what do I say about me..
Even the moon praises me.."
Is someone going to lower the
volume of the television?
It's pointless...
"Oh my baby doll of gold.."
Kakka... you won't
see more that way.
Actually, son, I can see more.
My number has increased.
- What are you saying?
- Yes.
- Kakka, let me take a look.
- No.
- Just once... only once...
- I said...
I hope you can see
all big and clear.
Vidya, you just broke
our concentration.
Scenes like these... makes
it a 'good morning'.
Jagdish, my son... why did
you change the channel?
- Why did you change the channel?
- Yes, why did you?
If he can watch it in front
of his daughter-in-law...
..then you can also watch it in
front of your young daughter.
She watches it on her
mobile, he on the computer.
And 1 watch it on the TV...
...Instead we should
all watch it together.
Why not? Let's forget all shame.
- Listen Sunny...
- Huh?
- I mean... what's her name?
- Vidya?
Listen Vidya, I may
have a dirty mind.
But I have a clean heart.
And... one of the
most religious..
..and cultured country in the world
has one of the largest population.
Kakka i had.. no
contribution in it.
I only have one daughter.
And for a fact, she's
so pampered...
...that she's still studying
when she should've settled down.
Haven't you seen kakka's
Japanese degrees?
Yeah.
It's only natural for some of his talents
to rub off on his granddaughter.
I wonder what good are these
Japanese degrees in agriculture.
No one even knows
what's written on them.
- And you know.
- You're spoiling our daughter.
- Me?
- Stop all this right now!
Don't you have any shame?
"Fair boys... fair boys..."
Sunny. again?
Not you..
"I sway my hips and dance. I
wear my earrings and dance."
Is it her birthday today?
You're going to look stunning
in your wedding dress.
Even you'll look quite
appealing in your suit.
Keshav, why do you keep playing
with my thumb all the time?
Can't help it, baby. That's as
far as I am destined to get.
Never imagined we'll be getting
married on the same day...
...but to different people.
Naru's calling. Here.
- Yeah, go on.
- Radhe-Radhe, brother.
Only five more minutes before
the Auspicious time to start.
Are you planning
on starting a war?
The bride's family is waiting.
Be quiet... you make it sound like
I am marrying Mallika Sherawat.
Doesn't matter... at least
she has the same name.
You see... the wedding cards
have been distributed...
...guests have arrived and the
procession is ready to leave.
So... where are you?
- Naru.
- Yes.
Is that Keshav?
Tell him, if we miss
this auspicious day...
...the next auspicious date
comes only after 36 years.
Tell him.
I'm sure you heard everything.
Tell him... I'm going
through a break-up.
This will take time.
So... what are your plans
for your wedding night?
What about you?
Don't forget to take the
glass of milk on time.
Forget it...
Your beloved wife will bring
an entire milk dairy with her.
Well, then I'll send you all
the cottage-cheese you want.
My God, cottage cheese
makes you blush.
I wonder what you'll
do if I say cream?
Well, that's the end
of this love-story.
Now go marry your groom.
I wish you had mustered some
courage to talk to your father...
...then you would be
getting married to me.
And not with that Mallika.
Doesn't matter... we both
had our share of fun.
We had some really good
time together, right.
Listen... we'll keep meeting even
after the wedding, won't we?
After the wedding... never!
I have a strict policy...
Never fiddle around with
someone's television or wife...
You'll get the shock
of your life.
Oh my boy of principles.
Are you going to post your
wedding photos on Facebook?
I will, sis...
Get lost. Go marry
that milk-maid.
Radhe-Radhe, brother. Brother,
father is very furious.
Then ask father to sit
at the dais in my place.
Guess you're in a
bad mood today.
But this is amazing...
You give those girls
driving lessons, but...
...they switch partners when
they need a permanent driver.
You know what, the day I
find my kind of girl...
...I swear I will rattle
Panditji's world.
You can say anything
you like out here.
Because you can't say a
word in front of father.
Come, brother. Time to suit up.
Sister-in-law Mallika
beckons you.
"Mallika is all grown up..."
"...like a dairy of milk."
[CHANTING PRAYER]
Come, Sister-in-law.
He's Manglik.
Plus, the planets and stars in
his birth-chart are unfavorable.
Only this Buffalo can
save his life now.
Congratulations.
Finally, there's some hope
for Keshav to get married.
Only when we find someone with
two thumbs on her left hand...
...can he get married?
- I see?
- Yes...
Bless you. Bless you two.
Great...
That's called moving up in life.
From Mallika the Buffalo to
Mallika the sister-in-law.
Congratulations, brother Keshav.
Naru!
- Naru.
- Yes.
- Where are you, you numbskull?
- Coming, father.
Have you got ants
in your pant...
...that you're running
around like this. Huh!
The shipment hasn't arrived yet.
Well, father, we've already
placed an order for cycle chains.
Brother and I will catch a train and
go buy those tubes for the cycles.
The accounts are in a mess.
It's hard to believe
there's a discrepancy...
...on brother Keshav's
watch, father.
Really? Where is your brother?
Enjoying his honeymoon?
- Tell him.
- Yes, father.
This week I will
sit in the shop...
...Chandu will take an off, and
you two will do the cooking.
Okay father...
But father...
- Radhe-Radhe, brother.
- Rad he-Rad he.
Cooking bread, are you?
You know what, I can't see
you in this predicament.
Should I call
sister-in-law instead?
She will cook bread for you.
You're pulling my
leg, aren't you?
You see... your
sister-in-law has solved...
- ...half the problems in my birth-chart.
- Yes.
I've 50% chances of
getting married now.
Now just wait and watch when I bring
a beautiful and smart wife, like me.
I'll even cook bread for her.
And you'll be fuming
with jealousy.
Let's not get so far
ahead of ourselves.
Did you forget about
father's second condition?
Where will you find
someone with two thumbs?
Will she descend from the sky?
Take my advice, brother.
Forsake all hopes
of getting married.
And you should mourn instead.
Even the children of your friends
are now going to school.
And that Kabir Bedi got
married for the fourth time.
And you couldn't even find one.
It's not your cup of tea.
You're going to
die a bachelor...
That's the limit.
Can't we brothers
talk in private?
Why does sister-in-law keep
getting offended all the time?
- Uncle, move aside.
- Yes, dear.
Everyone's standing in the way.
I'll just make a quick
visit to the toilet.
I'm coming too.
- Yuck...
- What happened?
At least let me pee
in peace, madam.
Disgusting people... why
can't they lock the door?
Men think why should
we lock the door?
Real maturity is about
peeing with the doors open.
- No shame at all.
- Right...
They knew the door was open...
...but thought it was against
their pride to knock.
Wouldn't you call
that impolite, Naru?
This isn't your house's main
door that we need to knock?
Of course not, it's a garden...
...where you can take
a stroll freely.
Hey brother, talk to me.
Get it?
What are you staring at?
I am talking to you.
Hey, brother...
Call me rude, but don't
call me brother.
Look at your age.
Are you going to teach
this to your children too?
How can I have kids?
I am still a bachelor-.
I see... no wonder.
No wonder he looks so desperate.
Move.
I said move.
You didn't even wash
your hands. Yuck.
She just publicly
humiliated you.
Doesn't matter, Naru.
It's my fault, so I
must pay the price.
What a big heart?
I washed my hands.
Are you crazy?
He just splashed
water in my eye.
Crazy man.
Hey...
"May no one throw
stones, at my lover.."
Come, the station has
arrived. Let's go.
Great... you're here.
- Here you go, Uncle.
- Get down.
- Your cycle has arrived.
- Okay.
On-time delivery.
Bravo...
Did the blunder. What is this?
What happened, uncle?
I asked for Sunny Leone...
...but you got me
Sunny Deol instead.
Did he ask for a lady's cycle?
I don't remember. Maybe...
What do you mean you
can't remember?
- Check the order again.
- We're checking, again.
Please do.
No need to worry, uncle.
You must have a saw at home.
- Just cut off that middle rod.
- That's right.
- And it will be a lady's cycle.
- Right.
And uncle, you can use that rod
to drive away the monkeys.
Get on...
- That's no way to do business.
- This is how we do it.
Listen... Radhe Cycle,
this isn't right.
- Get lost.
- I will not spare you.
Brother, it's that way.
What are you doing?
What's going on?
Attending to the customer.
Come on... get the saw.
We'll cut off that rod.
What made you change your mind?
- You were leaving.
- What's going on here?
Did you buy a new cycle for me?
I thought I'll give
you a surprise.
But these guys from
Radhe Cycle...
- Listen.
- Yes.
I've found that thief who's
been stealing our clothes.
Coming.
It's amazing.
Well, it was supposed
to be a lady's cycle...
...but we mixed up the order...
Why are you going off-track now?
You?
The rude guy from the bathroom.
No, I'm the cycle guy.
Your father ordered
a lady's cycle...
...but we got a gents
cycle instead.
Doesn't matter.
This one's a gents cycle,
isn't it? I'll keep it.
How can you keep it?
- It's our fault, we'll fix it.
- What do you mean?
I like this design,
I'll keep this one.
This isn't a joke. How are
you going to ride this?
There's a rod in the middle.
- Hey, Radhe Cycle...
- Keshav.
Whatever your name is?
Try to keep an open mind,
not the bathroom's door.
For your kind information...
...what did women wear when
cycles were invented in 1860?
Dresses.
And the rod in the middle was
removed for their safety.
And what do we wear now?
- What?
- Jeans.
So the rod doesn't matter.
Her general knowledge
is better than yours.
Doesn't matter... she's a female.
You spoke really well, madam.
But after 1860, in 1885
came safety cycles...
...which had a chain
and peddle as well.
Ladies got their freedom
of movement after that.
Great...
- Yes, but...
- I'm on your side, madam.
I don't differentiate
between ladies and gents.
That's why I prefer trains.
There are no separate toilets
for ladies and gents.
- But you must lock them.
- Of course.
Whether it's a ladies or gents.
Well, that's enough
lesson for one day.
No... please go on,
I am loving it.
Jaya, what happened?
What's wrong? You're still here.
Well, uncle, I was
just leaving...
Jaya got me talking.
- Shall we go now?
- Yes.
Okay, uncle...
Hold it.
If you ever have a problem,
just give me a call.
Yes.
My personal mobile number is
written behind this cycle.
- Give it to your entire family.
- Yes.
- I forgot to shift gears.
See you... Okay.
Papa“.
Brother... it's falling...
What are you doing? Can't you
see through those glasses?
What happened?
Is that her or am I
imagining things?
That's her alright?
She's a topper.
Don't even think about her.
Do you have the number of
Kanhaiyya, the computer guy?
Yes will get it.
"Since the day we met..."
can't stop smiling."
"I keep telling
everyone... I see."
"Stay away from this fantasy
or life will be doomed."
"Quit smiling, silly.."
- Brother, give me tea.
"..or I'll fall in love."
- Madam, tea.
"Quit smiling, silly,
or I'll fall in love."
Bloody thief.
Hello. How are you, Vasudev?
Where are you?
Madam, what's the time?
- 9:00.
- Thank you.
Yes.
"I used to feel... love's
too far-fetched for me..."
"...because I had no dreams."
"But since we met, I feel
a little unrestrained."
"I feel like I'm
lost in your eyes."
"Like sandalwood gets
dissolved in water."
She has only five fingers.
"The heart's willing
to do anything."
Move.
"Quit smiling, silly,
or I'll fall in love."
- Jaya.
- Yes.
Isn't that you?
Why that...
Where is he?
Where's that bloody Radhe cycle?
Why...
Who do you think you are?
Kuldeep, get a cup
of tea for ma'am.
Yes, ma'am?
With whose permission
did you put that up?
With whose permission did
you take my picture?
You think you're smart?
I'll shut down Radhe
Cycles for good.
Cancel the tea, get a cold drink.
Calm down, madam, calm down.
You're a topper. I really
care about education.
It's just a marketing strategy.
I swear since we put your face on the
hoarding, sales have gone up 8%.
And it's also sending a
message to the girls.
Whatever... I didn't top my
class to increase your sales.
- I know...
- Then know this.
If you don't take all the
posters down by tomorrow...
...you will be in big trouble.
Moron!
Madam, you... forgot your phone.
As well as my mobile
number in it.
Yes, Anu.
Brother, I did exactly
like you said.
But that Jeetu is
terrified of his father.
He says he won't elope with me.
Did he lose a leg?
Why won't he elope with you?
Of course, he will.
Get two tickets for
Gorakhpur Express. Yeah...
Pack your bags and get
to the station tonight.
I'll handle the rest.
- But will Jeetu show up?
- Give me my phone.
Give me my phone.
You're such a disgusting man.
You're advising
someone to run away.
- Who are you talking to, brother?
- Hold on.
She's my cousin.
Whether I give her my advice, or
anything else why does it matter to you?
- Anu.
- Mad.
- Yes, brother.
- From Gorakhpur head straight to Nepal.
Nepal?
Nepal is an amazing place.
Economical, reliable and realistic.
- I'll send you money from my mobile.
- But, brother...
Listen, sis, India is a
lot more advanced now.
Radhe-Radhe... take care.
Very good.
The brother inside you suddenly wakes
up and sacrifices your own sister.
How is it right to run
from your problems?
This is the best
advice right now.
This thinking...
This thinking... has
doomed this country.
If you have the guts
to love someone...
...you should be man enough
to admit it to your family.
Look, madam, their family
only has hatred and anger.
Because it doesn't take
time to hate someone...
...but, takes time
to understand love.
Soon the hatred will resolve until
then, let them enjoy their honeymoon.
Our thinking is so different.
No, it's not.
You're saying 'talk to the
family', I am saying 'run away'..
..but we're both on
the side of love.
Crazy...
You're crazy.
Madam, listen...
It's quite late,
I'll drop you home.
No need for that.
I swear I won't elope with you.
I can go myself.
Oh God, she's so
fluent in English.
Look straight... Stop ogling.
"Just like one needs
to breathe..."
"...to stay alive."
"All I need is a sweetheart..."
"...for falling in love."
"...for a massage."
Hey, brother, you're in
a colorful mood today.
Guess Holi isn't too far.
By the way, brother, it's
your first Holi post wedding.
What color will you
put on sister-in-law?
Every color's going to suit her.
Radhe-Radhe... You're
in love, brother.
Don't get emotional and
pull her on your bike.
Just watch, she will definitely
sit on my Honda some day.
My advice is... load her on a truck and
take her to see Agra's, Taj Mahal.
I can build a Taj Mahal for her.
Oh brother, now
that's happy Holi.
Sister-in-law's grown young.
She's become a dairy...
Are you crazy?
You just ruined my mood.
Get lost.
I only said milk...
No, enough.
Wow, dear...
That's a really cheap ringtone?
Who is calling?
Don't ask, mom.
- My phone fell in the drain.
- I see...
I want to change your
mother's ringtone as well.
Are you listening? He wants
to throw you down the drain.
Pass me the salad.
Hey, brother, you're brushing
your teeth a lot today.
Just refreshing my breath.
I'm washing my underwear and
you're refreshing your breath.
That's what you're good for.
Brother... goggles, deodorant...
- What are you preparing for?
- It's a lover's parade...
Should be grand.
[FOLK SONG]
It should be stopped now.
Who beats their
husband like this?
They are simply venting their
anger on these poor souls.
Look at their condition.
Fine, then you don't
beat your husband.
I will never...
Look, there..
Hold on.. wait.. wait..
Brother, thank God we
didn't get married.
Look at the size
of their sticks.
The men in our country hate
the idea of apologizing.
They certainly deserve this.
Hold on, aunty...
Coming through...
coming through...
- Oh my, God.
- He's flat on the ground.
- Hey.. Radhe.
- Don't beat him.
Look there... there...
So brother... no. 19.
No...
No. 1.
[FOLK SONG]
Listen...
I need to talk to her
today at any cost.
Okay.
[FOLK SONG]
It's Holi!
She will be here...
She will be here soon... She
will be here... be patient.
She's here... she's here.
Happy holi..
She is looking this way.
Even her friend's good looking.
When she comes here,
you guys leave.
She is still standing there.
She's here... she's here.
Tell her everything today.
Are you done yet?
Chasing me around.
Your friends even teased
you taking my name.
You've been staring
at me all this time.
You must be getting a kick
out of it, don't you?
Are you clone ogling at me?
Satisfied now?
You boys think it's
right to ogle at girls?
Huh? Look at me, I
am talking to you!
All this doesn't suit
you. Look at your age.
Don't you get it?
There can never be
anything between us.
- Madam.
- What?
It's already
happened between us.
But you can't see it, or
maybe you're ignoring it.
You're the one
ignoring reality...
There's a big
difference between us.
Do you get it?
I am just a college pass-out but my
GK's better than anyone out here.
I am a Pandit's (PRIEST) son,
but I eat eggs after praying.
I maybe over-age but, no kid in
this village can beat me in a race.
From my sunglasses to my
t-shirt, everything is a fake...
...but I'm still pretty
rustic at heart!
Now you decide whether you
want to tie the knot with..
...some ordinary IAS,
doctor or engineer...
...or are you looking for
some romance in life.
And yes...
Let me tell you one
thing honestly.
Since the day I saw you...
...I decided that I'll stand up
against the whole world for you!
And about following
you around...
Here you go...
I've deleted my number.
From your phone
and mine as well.
Goodbye. Let's go.
Bro, you were great today.
Bro, you were amazing today.
"Feels like these days, I've been
capriciously riding the waves."
"And never leave without watching
my reflection in your eyes."
"How do I stay away from your thoughts
you're the only one I think about."
"Quit smiling, silly,
or I'll fall in love."
Take these tires,
when the customers...
Hey, Radhe Cycle.
Your nameplate's fallen
off. Put it back.
If something's wrong with my
cycle where am I going to call?
If you can take it off, then
you can put it back too.
You didn't have to come all
the way here for that.
Leave.
I may have studied BCA but, my
GK isn't better than yours.
I'm a Joshi's girl, but
I ride gents cycle.
From head to toe, I am
completely rustic..
..but my thinking's
completely modern.
Now you decide...
...whether you want to tie the knot
with some ordinary, homely girl or...
...do you want some
romance in life?
Sudhir... put the radium
nameplate on madam's cycle...
...so that my number
glitters even in the dark.
And see to it that she
has no more trouble.
And take this one down.
I'll do a photoshoot for you.
"Quit smiling, silly,
or I'll fall in love."
or I'll fall in love.
- Listen.
- Huh.
Will you come to topper,
with the marriage proposal?
No.
In fact, my advice is that you
shouldn't either. Just WhatsApp her.
- Aren't you my brother?
- No.
But if you still
insist on going...
...then be honest with them and
tell them about the 'two thumbs'.
They are educated people, you fool. Let
me make an impression on them first.
Otherwise, they will
show me the way out.
Will you come along?
Take me to Syria instead.
I am not coming with you.
How could I say no to
brother, isn't it, aunty?
So I had to come down to talk.
And uncle, I knew
this since the day...
...brother put up huge
hoardings of sister-in-law.
- Can I ask you a question, son?
- Yes.
- I hope you won't mind.
- Not at all.
Guys your age normally
have two kids.
- So why...
- There's Mallika.
I mean he will treat
sister-in-law like a queen.
- I see...
- You see... he's also past that age.
But he has many desires.
You see, aunty, I
never got the time.
In fact, I never came
across anyone like Jaya.
That's true.
- Have some tea, son.
- No...
- I'll get you some cola.
- Get some cola for him, aunty.
But make sure it's sugar-free.
You see, brother likes
to maintain himself.
- I see...
- Right?
- No-no-no...
- I'll go get it for you.
- No need for that.
- Let's get to the point.
Yes.
Do you put the holy thread
over your ear while peeing?
No... not at all, uncle. No
formality in an emergency.
No... not at all.
Mahatma Gandhi has said...
"Be the change you wish
to see in the world."
Because the world...
International knowledge.
Uncle...
I just love wise men.
- Sunny Leone or Mallika Sherawat?
- Huh?
Tell him to stop..
What?
- Sunny Leone or Mallika Sherawat?
- He's at it again.
Sunny Leone.
Give me five.
- Radhe Cycle.
- Yes.
Take a seat.
Well... I completely
trust my daughter Jaya.
I do too.
If she's chosen you, then there
must be something about you.
- Yes.
- All I have to say is...
..just keep her happy.
Uncle, I can shut shop and
take up a government job.
- No-no...
- Just say it...
By the way, son, who else
is there in your family?
There's me, Naru and
Panditji, my father.
All men.
Yes... mother passed
away when I was a kid.
- And our grandma lives in Gorakhpur.
- Okay, okay.
And anyway, aunty,
once he gets married..
..they will carry
forward the lineage.
Children.
So let's take this
one step ahead.
When is Keshav introducing
us to Panditji?
Don't ask him, sister-in-law.
Father will give
him special time.
Isn't that right, brother?
Let's go see father.
He seems to be in a good mood.
I'll go first.
Guess who, father?
Now what trouble is this?
Rascals, never let me
do anything in peace.
Don't just stand there and
stare, say something.
Father, I was saying...
Father...
You want to go to Mumbai to
become a hero at this age.
Is business running in a loss?
Then what else is it?
Speak up.
Father, I... he...
- Brother...
- I want to get married.
Get me married.
Curses.
- I can see that.
- What, father?
The volcano erupting inside you.
What?
You've got some of
father's pee on your cheek.
You numbskulls... I've
told you a thousand times.
Your wife must have two
thumbs on her hand.
We already have a buffalo tied
in our courtyard with two horns.
Let's stop ranting
about two-thumbs.
You fool... that was just to get rid
of his 'Manglik' (INAUSPICIOUS) phase.
What about the faults still
left in his birth-chart?
And why do you think...
...I am insisting on getting
him a wife with two thumbs?
According to the scriptures...
...Water, Earth, Sky, Wind, and
Fire. The thumb... represents fire.
Only double fire can absolve the
final faults in his birth-chart.
So... you must marry
someone..-...
...who has 'double fire'
on her left hand.
Yeah...
This is really
terrible, brother.
I wonder what I did to
deserve this imbecile?
Can I say something, brother?
I think you should shift in the
barn with sister-in-law Mallika.
I've another idea.
Should I ask Hrithik?
Maybe he knows someone.
You know what...
...why don't you put up
posters for this too.
"Wanted! With two thumbs."
I'm in a real tight spot,
and you think it's funny.
Look... on a serious note...
Why don't you tell
father everything?
Hang me upside down father.
You're 36 years old... and
still scared of your father.
Not at all, I'm not
scared of my father.
- Really.
- I am scared of myself...
If I lose my mind, I swear, I
will make father's life hell.
Of course.
Don't you have a solution
on your computer.
For this? No...
Only some quick-fixer can
find a solution to this.
You're right... why move mountains
when we can find a quick-fix for it.
Absolutely right, mister.
It's a question
of our image now.
Brother, two cups of
tea... with ginger.
- Make it good.
- Yes.
- Brother, no ginger in mine.
- Okay.
- Listen.
- Yes.
- Can you knit?
- Yes, why?
- Radhe-Radhe.
Consider it clone.
O benevolent Lord,
get me married.
"There isn't a moment of peace without it."
- Keshav.
- Are you dead?
- "Always keeps you on your toes."
"Spins around like the
wheel of a cycle."
"Anyone in this predicament
is always happy."
"The path of love isn't easy."
"There's nothing more
complicated than love."
"I got cheated by
my own heart..."
"...and started believing you."
"I got cheated by
my own heart..."
"...and started believing you."
"Finally my heart
took the bait..."
"...and sacrificed all
its dreams for you."
"Small issue, lots of pain."
"There's nothing more
complicated than love."
Just remember three things.
Don't try to scratch with it...
or the nail will come off.
Keep it away from fire,
or it will melt.
And don't use it for legal purposes
it doesn't have a fingerprint.
Not at all. Never.
- Congratulations on your wedding, brother.
- Get lost.
Impossible!
Just like Hritika Roshan.
Where did you find her?
Father, last night Goddess
Laxmi came in my dreams.
And in the morning when I
went to the riverside...
...this fell on
me from the roof.
When she came looking for this, I
did the smart thing and hid myself.
I swear father, there was
fire emitting from her.
She was double
fire, take a look.
See, this.. See, father.
Father, get me married.
Father...
Come, Come..
Hey stop please.
Who is it?
- Bless you.
- Careful.
Come here.
[CHANTING PRAYER]
Hurry up. Hurry up.
Bless you, two. Bless you.
- Father... double fire.
- Yes.
Everything's going to
be just delightful now.
Not just delightful, now brother's
going to tango every night.
Am I right, Sister-in-law?
Brother Keshav, come please.
Congratulation Brother Keshav.
Well done..
You are great!
Come dance with me.
Very good.
Brother Keshav, do
the serpent dance.
Well done Father..
Hail to Brother keshav!
Dance with me also.
Come sister-in-law.
Come brother.
Aunty, your
daughter-in-law's here.
Right foot, sister-in-law...
right foot.
Come, sister-in-law.
Welcome, sister-in-law.
This is our courtyard.
Welcome.
Stop-stop-stop.
Let me introduce
you to his first.
You're the second wife, not
the first. She's his first.
Her name is Mallika you must
meet and greet her first.
You can meet her later.
- Come here first.
- This isn't right.
Listen to me...
You're in a lot of hurry today.
Do you always have to
interfere? Get lost.
I am not going anywhere. I'm
going to sleep in the middle.
What is that?
- 'Sande Ka Tel'.
- Shameless.
Here... my mistress sent
this for you. Drink it.
You can't even take
a joke nowadays.
Even you kept me in the dark.
I want a divorce, that's it.
1 see...
Let's get on with the
wedding night...
...and I'll divorce your
entire family in the morning.
Will you come
quietly... or jump?
- Jump.
- Jump!
Sister Mallika...
Sister Mallika, help!
Curse those two.
Sister-in-law.
Get up.
You already woke me up
three times last night.
I am a man, not a machine.
Useless.
Sister-in-law, recognize me?
I am Sana. We met
at your wedding.
Yes, Sana, but...
It's already 4:15.
Everyone's eagerly waiting to
welcome you to our LOTA party.
Sana, is it going to take long?
Get the new daughter-in-law
quickly. It's getting urgent.
You go, Sana. I'll
meet everyone later.
It will be dawn soon.
You go, I am coming.
Hurry up then.
We've a long way to go.
Wake up. Keshav, wake up.
Wake up!
My dear, are you going to
wake me up like this every day?
Why didn't you tell me?
But Naru did tell
you about Mallika?
Stop joking.
Why were these women
calling me out?
Don't you have a
toilet in your home?
Toilet?
No toilet... where?
There's one in my home.
Why didn't you tell me
before our marriage?
Tell you what?
That you don't have a
toilet in your home.
Why are you making
a scene for it?
Where should I go then?
Same place everyone
else is going.
Socialize with everyone, get to
know everyone in the LOTA party.
Be their leader...
Be their leader!
Listen to me. Such
anger for a toilet?
If I had known, I would've
never married you.
Move!
Didn't anyone in the village
build a toilet, Sana?
No, sister-in-law,
there isn't one here.
What's the matter?
Is there a problem?
Don't you think it's a problem...
to defecate out in the open.
But this is important.
How can we do without it?
No walls or doors.
- What if someone sees you?
- Now I get it.
I guess there's been
an incident with you.
Is everyone waiting for
an incident to happen?
Until then, let things
continue the way they are.
Isn't it?
Are you two going
to chatter alone?
We're here too.
You're really beautiful.
Also, you had a love-marriage.
Yes, of course, that's what girls
do when they get educated.
Yes... that's what they
teach us in college.
She's got a sharp
tongue, sister.
He was always so predictable.
We always knew, Keshav will marry
some English-speaking girl.
- How much further?
- Just a little more, sister-in-law.
What if we have to
go during the day.
Control it.
Hurry up, daughter-in-law,
it will be dawn soon.
Will you just stand there and
stare at us, daughter-in-law?
Aren't your in-laws feeding you?
She feels embarrassed.
Forsake all your inhibitions
and get down to business.
I'm not used to it.
Did your parents build
a palace for you?
You are right.
Yes... there was a
toilet in my home.
I can't do this.
- Listen...
- Daughter-in-law.
You'll get in trouble later.
Just watching television.
Come... Father's not at home.
You're still angry with me.
Say something.
Why are you making such a scene?
I can't defecate out
in the open, Keshav.
Do something... or I'm leaving.
Father...
..we delivered Gokul's
consignment yesterday.
Some minor things to do.
I've called a handyman.
The roof was leaking.
And build a small
toilet in the room.
- What did you say?
- The spare parts will arrive from Agra...
- Huh?
- What did you say?
Spare parts...
Before that.
- The roof was leaking.
- After that?
Build a small toilet...
What happened, father?
I can't swallow a
single morsel...
...if anyone mentions a
toilet while eating.
And now our... topper daughter-in-law
wants a loo in our home.
No respect for our culture or knowledge
of our tradition and rituals.
Over-education makes
you a failure in life.
- Give me some bread.
- Yes, me too...
What is this?
Father's share of bread...
Go give this to father.
Come along, father
will like that.
Come.
Father, please eat...
Stop venting your anger
on food, father.
Daughter-in-law cooked this food
without going to the toilet.
I won't eat this.
By the way, father, if we can have
a living room, a dining room...
...then, we can certainly
build a toilet.
Then why take the body
to the crematorium?
You can burn me right
here in our courtyard.
And then build a toilet.
Come Jaya, it's really late.
Jaya...
Jaya, I am trying.
I've already put in a
request with father.
Darling... just a few more days.
Soon we'll find a
solution for this.
What solution?
Build a fake toilet,
like the fake thumb.
- Trying to make quick-fixes.
- Jaya..
No-no-no... look.
Look closely who defecates
out in the open.
There should be some difference.
Here... it's your uncle calling.
Tell him... what you thought
was a smartphone...
...turned out to
be a small pager.
- Radhe-Radhe, uncle.
- Everything okay.
Tell me... how can there be
so much peace in Mandgaon.
We sent a storm from here.
Forget the storm, uncle, I am
preparing for World War 3.
- Have faith in me.
- I do...
Keep a firm grip on
those cycle-sellers.
Hmm...
Why are you sounding so
low? Is everything alright?
Give it to me.
No, uncle.
I was just feeling tired.
Right, I guess you don't
get much sleep these days.
Listen, tell Keshav that
Sunny's new film is releasing.
We'll go watch it together.
- Uncle...
- Let me talk properly...
Dear... is everything fine?
- Yes..
- When are you coming home?
Hello-hello.
- Hello.
- What happened?
There's always a villain
in every love story.
And in my case, it's the toilet.
I must fix this
once and for all.
I have an idea.
Take your problem
to the Pradhan.
Get out of here... the Pradhan.
Pradhan!
[FOLK SONG]
I'm asking you for the fourth time. Why
bring me here at the crack of dawn?
Wait, sweetheart. Be patient.
Everyone must change with time.
I've heard she's well educated.
Are you planning on letting
her take up a job as well?
Oh, no...
It's up to her. She can
do what she wants.
Jaya, go and meet
grandma upstairs.
She's bedridden and can't
move or walk. Go on.
Yes, why not.
That's why they had to build
a toilet in grandma's room.
I'll send her.
No-no, she will manage
herself. Go on.
Don't be hasty.
Haste makes waste.
Right, wifey, right.
- Radhe-Radhe.
What now? What are you
fuming about now?
It's nothing.
What do you want?
What kind of a question is that?
Don't you know what I want?
I felt like a thief
just to go to the loo.
- You've made my life miserable.
- I can say the same for you.
You've done me a big
favor by marrying me.
And now I must tolerate
your educated tantrums.
What?
You really think I am
throwing tantrums.
Isn't a woman even entitled
to a toilet in her home?
For years women have
been adjusting...
...to the methods practiced
in her in-law's home.
It's nothing new.
Education has got to your head.
Chaubey, check the tubes
before you buy them.
Or else we'll get the
defective stuff again.
Brother, did you get
the bike serviced?
Father has to leave for Mathura.
Wouldn't I rather
sabotage the brakes?
Here.
And don't forget to
wash the lunchbox.
Frankly speaking, brother, God has
put you in a really fine mess.
I'm sure he wrote
my fate in the loo.
Yes... and flushed it too.
You know what, brother
why don't you buy...
...sister-in-law her
own personal field?
That way, you can have
your cake and eat it too.
Have you lost your mind?
- Go mind your own business.
- Don't come asking me for advice again.
Keshav. Keshav, wake up.
Keshav, wake up.
- Wake up. Wake up.
- What's wrong? Is it an earthquake?
- Take me to the field quickly.
- Field.
No 'ifs' or 'buts'.
This is not the time for
your tantrums. Let's go.
I am sorry.
I was very rude
to you yesterday.
- I apologize.
- Doesn't matter. Let's go.
By the way, the fields
are very romantic.
- We can romance...
- This is no time to be Shahrukh Khan.
Curses.
Radhe-Radhe.
I'm right here.
Good luck.
Father!
Peel these.
Are you clone with
your work in Mathura?
- First wash my hands.
- Yes.
What's all the racket about?
Clear your throat for good.
Father.
She's just tensed about what
happened today in the field.
You're worried about
what happened to her.
And what about the fact that
I fell in a pile of garbage.
These things happen.
Don't complicate things.
It wasn't so serious.
Daughter-in-law did
cover her face.
- Then.
- I see...
That's a fine example, father.
Then we don't need to cover our
faces anymore in this house!
Jaya.
Father...
Brother... are you planning to
jump in front of the train?
No...
I'm thinking of throwing
you in front of the train.
Why didn't you stop me
from getting married?
That doesn't make sense.
Why would I stop you?
First of all, I am not getting
married because of you.
Father was the hurdle in your
life. And you're in mine.
He's been married twice.
But no one's concerned about me.
My brother, you don't
know how happy you are.
I don't want to be happy.
Even I was overexcited
to get married.
And I did.
You can see how she's
turned my life into hell.
What are you saying, brother?
Your wife's one in a million.
It's better not to have
one..not like her.
She's got my life
trapped in an urn.
Stop discussing our
family problems outside.
What family problems?
When there's a problem at home a man's
going to vent it out somewhere.
Right, Rastogi.
What happened, brother? Be
a little more specific.
How about I tell you in detail?
- Stop provoking brother, you rascal.
- Naru!
Show some respect.
He's 35 years older than you.
Shameless...
It's nothing, Rastogi.
Life's a big mess.
Will you be a little
more specific?
Who made a mess and where?
I am stuck.
Actually, your poor sister-in-law
isn't asking for too much.
One toilet.
I am ready to give her open fields,
the jungle, trees and bushes.
But no...
She insists on a 4x8 toi... let.
Bloody hell.. Where do
I get her a toilet?
So that's the problem.
It's not a problem,
its blasphemy.
And then there's Panditji.
He's like the permanent
problem in my life.
He's like father-in-law
from hell.
I pray no one has to go
through this ordeal.
They have made my life hell.
Look, brother Keshav,
my advice to you is...
...take sister-in-law to
Gorakhpur, to see your grandma.
The train halts for 7
minutes in your village.
So... when do I
book your tickets?
- I don't want to go anywhere.
- Give it to me.
Okay.
What did you say?
- How long will the train halt?
- 7 minutes.
- Will the train halt for 7 minutes?
- Yes.
Remember our first
meeting and climb up.
Go on, you have seven minutes.
"Your love's slowly
growing on me."
"Like ginger blends
with the morning tea."
"Your love's slowly
growing on me."
"Like ginger blends
with the morning tea."
"I eagerly wait for you, like for
the morning rays in winter."
"I'm prepared to ride all
the way to the moon."
"The morning train..."
"Your love's like
the morning train."
"The morning train..."
"Your love's like
the morning train."
"I stay awake all night..."
"Your love's like
the morning train."
"The morning train..."
"Your love's like
the morning train."
It's three...
- Oh, God!
- Yes.
- I won.
- What is this? I don't want to play.
You know what, you go.
Your sister-in-law and
I are going to play.
Where are you taking the game?
Brother's going to play
another games with you now.
How are we going to play now?
Let’s Play-
"We set out before dawn."
"Let the world be envy."
"The heart keeps chugging."
"Keeps stopping on the way."
"And sometimes beats fast
like an express train."
"The morning train..."
"Your love's like
the morning train."
- Keshav.
- Yes, father.
Give this to the Pradhan when you
go out for one of your joyrides.
Yes.
Oh no!
- We're late today.
- No, we're not.
I'll just go deliver this
to the Pradhan. Okay.
- Come back soon.
- I'll be back in a jiffy.
Check the next
compartment, dear.
- You'll find an empty one.
- Thank you.
Move. Move, mister.
Read it.
- Hurry up.
- The train's about to leave.
- Radhe-Radhe, Pradhan.
- Radhe-Radhe, son.
What brings you here so early
in the morning, Keshav.
Father sent these documents
for attestation.
Take a seat... let's have
a cup of tea. Vimla.
No-no-no... not now. I'm
getting late. Maybe next time.
Take a seat, it's not like
you've to catch a train.
What...
- Okay, see you then.
- Okay.
Radhe-Radhe.
- Radhe-Radhe.
I only want the betterment
of this village.
That's true. Anything
for this village...
Open the door!
Quickly. The train's
leaving, Open the door!
- Open the door.
- Yes, we're moving it.
Open the door.
The train's leaving,
Open the door!
Yes, we're moving it.
Get everything aside.
- Move.
- Yes, we're moving it.
Keep it here...
Come... come..
Jaya, get down.
Jaya, pull the chain.
Pull the chain!
Jaya!
Jaya! What are you
doing? Pull the chain.
We're running out of platform.
Pull the chain!
Jaya.
Jaya. Pull the chain!
Shooting.. Shooting..
Even if you call 100 times you'll
get the same answer, Keshav.
I am not coming back.
Think about the rumor
people are going to spread.
Keshav's wife left
him for a toilet.
Will you feel proud if your
wife defecates out in the open?
You're getting it all wrong.
We'll find a way.
You mean another quick-fix.
When in love, the best
solution is to run away.
Fake thumb for marriage and,
using the loo on the train.
Listen carefully, Keshav.
No more quick-fixes.
Find a permanent solution.
You know what, you can take your
demands and sit in your toilet.
Okay. Okay.
See... she's publicly
embarrassed us.
What happened, father?
Read, son. Read.
She's made us Pandit's so proud.
- Your grandma called.
- Yes.
She's coming down from
Gorakhpur next week.
Yes, father.
She just made a big
joke out of us.
Brother.. look..
Tell him, Naru.
Now he must take care
of the household.
Couldn't even take
care of his wife.
She's not some piece of cloth
which needs to be taken care of.
Come on.
He's only good for
cleaning up dung.
Only animals are allowed
to shit in this courtyard.
Which scoundrel
published this news?
We've been betrayed
by one of our own.
Rastogi from Jagran.
- Brother Keshav.
- Bloody traitor...
How dare you!
How dare you
humiliate my family!
- Now he's got the respect he deserved.
- Brother, please...
Come on.
Whatever I did, was
for your own good.
Shut it down. Shut it
down. Go back inside.
You bloody...
Speak up!
- Tell me.
- Listen to me, brother, please...
I'll tell you if you
stop hitting me.
Speak up. Yes, tell me.
Listen to me...
This news would've
been out soon enough.
My newspaper didn't
expose some hidden scam.
Thanks to your newspaper. Those
who didn't know also know.
Just wait and watch...
...sister-in-law will come
back home due to this article.
How?
The bride's family never likes to
see such news in the newspaper.
There must be chaos
in their house.
All of them must be
completely shaken.
'You said...'
Can someone please lower the volume so
we can discuss more important issues?
These so called 'important' issues
are what's ruining the country.
"How long are we going
to mourn and cry."
"Pull up the blanket over
your head and sleep."
Please stay quiet.
I can't hear the
dialogues, mother.
Of course, just listen
to the dialogues.
Did anyone read
today's newspapers?
What is everyone's
opinion about it?
This is Kakka's contribution in 'Swacchta
Abhiyan' (CLEAN INDIA MOVEMENT).
Today's newspaper was fit to
be used as waste and so I did.
Waste should always go into
the wastepaper basket.
- 'They will die for you?
- Yes.'
'But I am not like
them. I am different.'
My thumb.
Daughter-in-law's thumb?
What if Rastogi's
right, brother?
Maybe sister-in-law will come
back after reading this news.
She won't.
I wonder how many times I
will still get humiliated...
Useless!
Both of you are useless!
This...
This fake thumb that you made...
It's not for me or religion.
She left it behind for
you, your topper madam.
And now... even the Lord
can't absolve your troubles.
- But, father, sister-in-law only...
- Shut up.
Don't you dare mention
her name here again?
Yes, father.
They want show
religion the finger.
Stop pretending!
Get up brother.
Field clear.. silence.
Taking.
- Ready, sir.
- Action.
Do I look stupid to you?
- I'm sorry.
- What sorry.
You think I can't see.
You were flirting with her,
I saw it with my own eyes.
You don't trust me.
You trust me right?
I love you.
Cut it.
I see... so these oversized
boxes are toilets.
Your sister-in-law will be
really comfortable in this.
Huh?
Brother, I don't think
your intentions are good.
Careful. Careful.
Pull.. Pull..
How do you feel carrying a loo
on your shoulders, Rastogi?
- I feel like Mother India.
- I see...
Brother Keshav, it looks new.
Don't publish this
in your newspaper.
Brother, after that beating, I'll
only print what you tell me to.
Brother, what if they file a
complaint with the police?
Only if they find it.
Where will we hide it?
We'll hide it in our
courtyard for a day or two.
And cover it.
Later, when father leaves for
Agra we'll shift it in my room.
Come on.
Can't live without me?
There's something I
want to tell you.
That's what phones are for.
Not like this.
Let's meet.
What is it this time?
Some quick-fix again.
No quick-fix... this time
I've come up with an idea.
Can we meet?
Then come home.
I won't come home.
Things will just
get complicated.
Why? Are you feeling
embarrassed?
Fine, let's meet tonight.
Why?
Are you embarrassed to
meet me during the day?
Of course, I am.
I don't want people to
think that I gave in.
So where are we going to
meet my beloved wife?
Near the field with the tower.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Are you enjoying, meeting secretly
like this even though we're married.
Yeah... I've been having
fun for 36 years, madam.
I used all the tricks up my sleeve
to get a wife but she left me too.
We should've eloped instead.
This distance is
taking effect on you.
So tell me... why did
you call me here?
Better prepare yourself
to come back home.
I just solved this
problem permanently.
I see... How?
See for yourself.
Soon I'll take you back home,
like wedding procession.
You could've said
this over the phone.
I wanted to see you.
But not me.
Why are you on-line
last night at 12:30?
Were you watching
my profile picture?
You must have run your fingers
on my photo, like this.
I see... how do you know?
Were you keeping an eye on me?
I have a drone hovering
over your father's home.
And it keeps telling me.
You know, since the day I left, I've
been sleeping embracing your picture.
So... stop doing it until
day-after-tomorrow.
- Why?
- Everyone will think that you gave in.
Your phone's vibrating.
Hold on.
Speak up, bloody jinx.
Now you guys are stealing
toilets as well.
Because of people like you even mugs
have to be chained in train's toilets.
Fine, but I don't want to stand out
in the open like you guys and pee.
Are you listening to his taunts?
You take the necessary
action, Inspector.
He has tainted my religion.
By bringing this sin home?
They have been committing the
sin till now, Inspector.
What did his
daughter-in-law do wrong?
Only animals defecate
out in the open.
1 see...
I raised him into this
37-year-old man that he is now.
And now you think it's wrong
to defecate out in the open.
You're right. You
raised me to be a man.
That's why I never
thought about women.
Let him stay in jail.
Grandma. Grandma,
come in. Please.
- Come in. Please.
- I will never cross this threshold!
I just came here to say..
..that you've raised your
daughter with some great values.
Keshav stole a loo for her.
And now he's locked up
in jail, for stealing.
And this princess...
She's sitting in her
home, over a loo.
Unbelievable, grandma.
You're saying this even
though you're a woman.
I'm saying this because I am a woman.
We've to compromise all the time.
That's the plight of women.
But she left her home.
That's not the way.
This never happened in
our village before.
Out on your joyride again-.
The men can do it right
in their backyard.
But we're women.
We've to work harder
for everything.
Isn't it?
We're expected to make
all the compromises.
Because that's what our
culture teaches us.
Control your urges.
Wait for nightfall.
Men can do it during the clay, but
you got to do it in the dark.
But stay quiet!
If men look at you with lusty
eyes then just cover your faces..
..but stay quiet!
And when some pervert
flashes his torch at you...
...then cover your faces, rather
than covering your backside!
So that he can go to
his friends and say...
"I caught a glimpse, but
don't know who it was."
Every day they kept flashing
their headlights at you...
...but it never struck you.
You're happy because LOTA party
has a new agenda to discuss!
This is okay Neelam.
If you're having periods,
stay out of the temple.
If there's a pyre burning we
stay out of the crematorium.
And if we want to relieve
ourselves go outside the village.
Why?
Why make these rules?
Why only for us?
It was their fault... but
now, it's our fault!
What do you want, Jaya?
Do you expect us to leave
our home like you?
We don't have a toilet
even in our parent's home.
I don't know.
I only found a solution
to my problem.
But the rest of you don't even
realize that you're in trouble!
Someday... Someday you will be
reduced to ashes in these urns.
Even now you're trapped
in it while you're alive!
Serve water to your
husband in this urn...
...and we'll see... whether
they make a scene, or not.
- Come, sir.
- Please.
- Brother.
- Hello, sir.
Yeah...
Jaya.
- Sir...
- Yes, thank you.
This was your solution
to my problem?
Do me a favor, Keshav.
No more quick-fixes for me.
Forgive me.
Don't say that, Jaya.
Strange, you're bailing out
the guy who stole your loo.
No thief in the world will
steal a toilet, Inspector.
1 see...
Okay.
- Let Keshav go.
- Thank you, sir.
Come, brother. I guess
it's going to rain.
Let it rain, Naru.
Even the Lord's taunting me now.
Guess you're drunk...
you're not in your senses.
I am drunk... and even
more determined now.
- Mom.
- Yes.
Where's my silver-waistband?
Wow...
If Keshav sees you today he
will take you back home.
Let him come.
I will break his
head with the stick.
Listen...
He isn't asking for dowry.
Or raised his hand on you?
He loves you, think about it.
End this right here
and go back home.
You've made things more
complicated than it is.
Complicated?
Bravo, Vidya. Bravo.
Do you know what happened
with the kids in Badhai?
Poor kids went out
in the evening.
They were raped and
hung from the tree.
And a 17-year-old girl in
Jharkhand, committed suicide.
Why? Because her father
didn't build a toilet.
God forbid if something like
that happens with our child...
...will you still say that
she's complicating things.
You women are your
own worse enemies.
Like they say, Vidya...
Don't wait till it's too late.
It's a good thing that our
child took this step.
When Keshav shows up today...
...hit him hard on
my behalf as well.
Forget it, grandpa. I am not
even going to look at him.
"I crave for your glimpse..."
"...and finally I realized."
"I want to rub the mud under your feet
on my head and sanctify my sins."
"You didn't invite me... but I
still came down your lane."
"You can punish me for
all unfair treatment."
"You didn't invite me... but I
still came down your lane."
"You can punish me for
all unfair treatment."
"Don't spare your
beloved today..."
"...because he never learns."
"Your beatings feel so sweet."
"Come dear and hit me hard."
"You're the only one I love."
"As my veil fluttered..."
"...you colored it
with your love."
"When I look into your eyes..."
"...my eyes were overwhelmed."
"...they were overwhelmed."
"My tear-filled eyes
couldn't sleep all night."
"They are crazy about to you."
"When I heard your
sweet talks..."
"...my heart was hooked on."
"My heart was hooked on.."
"I came to you leaving
the world behind."
"I severed all ties
just to be with you."
"Chant Radhe-Radhe-Radhe-Radhe."
"I've forsaken everything for you,
now punish me in any way you want."
"We're incomplete
without each other."
"Chant Radhe-Radhe-Radhe-Radhe."
"Pray to your God for me."
"I've let go of this shield."
"Color me red..."
"...only you can set
things right for me."
"Come dear and hit me hard."
"You're the only one I love."
This is really
humiliating, brother.
Stop acting like some Romeo.
Let's go inside.. It's
your in-laws home.
Throw your weight around.
How can I show my face?
I made a big mistake.
Well... you try talking
to sister-in-law.
I'll wait for you
in that corner.
And whoever hurled
that balloon at me...
...I'll show him when
he comes to my village.
I am keeping my mouth shut because
this is my sister-in-law's home.
Otherwise I would've showed
you how we play Holi.
That won't do any good.
Apply some dirt.
Apply some dirt!
Apply some s*** instead.
You're never going to
move ahead of that.
You claim to have the best GK...
...but never use
it in real life.
Will dirt cure your wounds?
But it will definitely
cause infection.
You've all made a fine mess in the
name of tradition and customs.
When in trouble, find
an easy way out.
Change others, but not yourself.
Since the time I was born, I've
always used a toilet, Keshav.
Why should I change
my habit now?
Listen... it's really
painful, isn't it?
You're the one who
got beaten up.
But I gave you the wounds.
Come back home.
I swear I'll change everything.
What will you change?
Everyone's opinion?
I won't die without you.
I am happy-
You didn't go?
You see, brother never leave a patient
in hospital or a lover alone.
What did sister-in-law
say? Is she coming back?
No, Naru. And she
shouldn't either.
I finally realized now.
How can she do something she
never did all her life?
This isn't just about a loo...
It's about everyone's view.
Jhoni... tell me
everything. What happened?
What can I say, grandma...
this is getting uncomfortable?
They're always in the jungle before
us, with their lights and camera.
At first, we thought
its the shooting crew.
But soon we realized
they were after us.
Guess they are from
some news channel.
They record us like we're
indulging in foreplay.
It's entirely Keshav
and his wife's fault.
Laxmi... what did she do now?
Your news was published in the
newspaper and we're paying the price.
Jhoni, you claim to be the
leader of LOTA party...
...then why so embarrassed
to come on TV?
What are you saying, Keshav?
- Are you drunk?
- Yes, grandma, I am drunk.
This is entirely
your fault, Keshav.
Repercussions of getting
an educated wife.
You should be thanking us.
You've become a model at
this age, thanks to us.
Every day you defecate
out in the open.
So how about showing some
skin for TV as well.
It's alright, Panditji. He doesn't
know how to respect women.
The women in this country
can't respect themselves.
Otherwise, they would've never agreed
on defecating out in the open.
He's talking too much.
You don't worry.
To hell with these people.
We'll come up with a solution.
- We'll...
- No, Naru.
We're clone with finding
quick solutions.
It's time to do the impossible.
Today's first agenda.
The shooting is taking place on
the border of both the villages.
The shooting crew
has been warned...
...that they should
stop wasting water.
The matter is under control now.
The next agenda, Keshav's
wife has left him.
And Keshav has put
in a request...
...to build a public toilet
outside the village.
Those who agree can sign or put their
thumb impression on this paper.
I don't know.
We won't give our
thumb impression.
Young man, did you get this
idea from the shooting crew?
People won't forget their values
even if you build loos for them.
And stop defecating
in the fields?
Keep this stupidity
restrained to your home.
Stop joking, village-head.
I've already been arrested once.
If you try to burden us
with your problems...
...then, we'll have
to face the music.
We got freedom from
the British rule...
...do you want us to be
slave to their culture?
That isn't right, village-head.
There are other women
in the village.
And their safety is the village
council's responsibility.
- We're happy with our LOTA party.
- Yes.
And what about openly
humiliating yourself.
Keshav, don't talk
about respect.
Your wife left you.
Show some respect to others.
That's what he wants. That
we s*** in our homes.
Or maybe s*** in our kitchens.
I only want the
village council...
...to put in a request with
the government for a toilet.
Don't try to teach us
our responsibility.
This is an ancestral village.
Our ancestors didn't build
a toilet in our homes...
...and we're not Gods either.
If we build a bathroom in our
homes, won't that dirty our homes.
And what about the stink.
You want us to invite
diseases in our homes.
Don't try to teach the
villagers, Keshav.
- We don't want a bathroom.
- Of course.
We don't need one, so let's
not bother the government.
Let's go. Come on, let's go.
- That's enough social-service for one day.
- Let's go. Come on.
Hey let's go from here.
Son, the Block Committee is
above the Village Council.
Go meet Vasudha
Tiwari at her office.
Pradhan, stop
misleading the boy.
And you.. Don't try to
challenge our culture, son.
[SANSKRIT CHANT]
Manu has written in
the 'Manu-Smriti'.
One must defecate
away from home.
Tell me, people, did Ram-Sita
build a bathroom in the jungle?
See this..
Who's going to complete that
'Shlok' (VERSE), headman?
Did you overlook the next page?
[SANSKRIT CHANT]
The 'Shloka' also states that...
...one must not defecate near
a river or any water body.
And wash their hands afterward.
Forget about washing your hands. You
even clean your ass in the river.
People like you use religion
according to your own convenience.
What did you think?
Just because no one
knows Sanskrit...
...you can say anything
you like and get away.
Don't try to teach me the
Scriptures, Village-head.
And remember...
Whether my wife comes back or not, I
will build a bathroom in this village.
Radhe-Radhe.
- Look, uncle..
- What happened?
Look at our country's
plight. See here.
Keshav doesn't know who
he's going up against.
Thirty Cr scam.
There are no records.
All these scams are
four years old.
Everyone's involved. Read this.
And all these ministers are
involved in this scam.
Not just the ministers.
Everyone's involved.
What should I send Keshav?
Look at these scams.
Wonderful, sister-in-law.
Read it carefully.
- Thank you.
- Welcome.
Listen.
If you go to the toilet, don't
forget to lock the door.
- Do that later.. Don't be crazy.
- Go.
You're too much.
- Give me the file.
- Take it.
Careful.
Bye, sister-in-law.
- Bye.
- Love you.
- Mister, where's DM Mathur's room?
- It's this one.
- Hold on...
- Wait..
- It's urgent.
- You can't go inside like this.
Keshav from Mandgaon.
I see... so you're Keshav.
- Yes, that's me.
- I read in the newspapers.
First of all, all that money that
you swindle from the poor...
...where do you take it out?
- Brother...
- Hold on.
Where are these... Thirty Cr
toilets. Can you show me?
I see... the public's awakening.
Well, finally after
all these years...
...someone came asking
for an explanation.
What do you want from me?
Toilets... which the
government promised us.
Actually... I am
going to expose you.
1 see...
See that you don't
expose yourselves.
Take a good look, guys.
This is a barber shop,
horse-stable...
...and this one's a tailor shop.
So what does that prove?
All these are public toilets...
...which you guys are using
for your personal benefits.
The government makes
toilet schemes...
...but you guys reject it.
And you guys don't care.
To hell with the funds.
We won't build a
toilet in our homes.
Look at this Keshav, the
plan for your home.
Few of the homes
in your village...
...were built under the
government rehabilitation scheme.
But the rest are
ancestral homes.
So there was never any facility
for toilets in our home.
The government installed
sewage lines in your homes.
But you guys shut it down.
That's not done.
The government made
arrangements...
...but connecting the sewage
with your toilet is your job.
So who's the villain now?
You mean we don't
have an option now.
Do you know what's a PIL?
Public Interest Litigation.
Go see a lawyer.
Register a PIL against
the Village Council...
...that you want a
toilet in your village.
Well, finally after
all these years...
...at least someone thought
that toilet is a problem.
Actually sir, until the problem
doesn't get personal...
...no one's prepared to
fight... or find a solution.
- Sir, can I come in?
- Come.
- Uncle, show me your face.
- Yes.
- Uncle.
- Taking my picture. Wait...
I took this picture at the turn.
This is a barber-shop,
this one is a tailor-shop.
This one is a cowshed, Isn't
this what the lawyer said?
Sir, I've brought all the
proof. What should we do next?
This will get the job done.
I'll get a sanction from the government
get a toilet built in Mandgaon.
- Okay?
- Yes.
It will take 11 months.
Well, that's almost a year.
It's the government...
...works at its own pace.
All these years you
lived without a toilet.
Another year. Right.
I can live without a toilet
but without my wife.
Remember who's the villain,
in this case, Keshav.
You're challenging our culture.
Understood!
And it's not easy to
win over culture.
This is a difficult trial.
In this country, fighting against
culture is not an easy task.
Brother, I have an idea now...
...what this culture is
everyone's ranting about.
Who is it?
Culture is something no
one's seen or heard of...
...yet, everyone's
clinging on to it.
Culture is what makes us put donation
boxes in temples and mosques...
...but makes humans defecate
out in the open like animals.
That's culture.
[CHANTING PRAYER]
What is he doing?
This is a pandit's
home after all.
So veneration is a must before
starting any good deed.
For the sake of your happiness.
What good deed, son?
Laying the foundation
stone, grandma.
I'm building a
toilet in our home.
Now, change your
thinking, father.
And stop peeing out
in the gutter.
Okay, son.
You've crossed all limits.
Do as you please.
I won't eat a
morsel of food now.
Great, no food, no stress.
Radhe-Radhe.
What... What's he...
"The world's preparing
to land on Mars..."
"...while the moon's
being sold on earth."
"From black/white to color..."
"...and now everything's in 3D."
"Thousands have climbed...
the Everest..."
"Mister... better
build a toilet now."
"How long are you going to keep
doing it around the bush?"
"Mister... better
build a toilet now."
- Can I give you an idea?
- What?
Leave the bathroom uncovered.
Why?
Are you going to bury
Anarkali in here?
Go on... hurry up.
Father...
Father, your meal..
Please eat your meal.
"Defecating in the open
is humiliating..."
"...that's what
culture tells us."
"Cover yourself
till your waist..."
"...and sit out in the open."
"Sister-in-law sets out
at crack of dawn..."
"...while the boys are
waiting on the way to ogle."
"Sit back and watch
what happens."
"Mister... better
build a toilet now."
"How long are you going to
keep beating around the bush?"
"Mister... better
build a toilet now."
"Every lane of the country is stinking,
it's difficult to even breathe."
"India will be clean again look
at the condition of your home."
"If you sit next
to the river..."
"...the water will
wash it all away."
"And that water will flow
through the taps..."
"...and you'll be
forced to drink that."
"Stop going to defecation
in the field."
"Stop other people
from going too."
"If defecating in the open is a matter
of pride then stop wearing clothes."
"Not everything is a tradition,
stop hiding behind it."
"Stop hiding behind it."
"Don't blame culture
for your faults."
"Mister... better
build a toilet now."
"How long are you going to
keep beating around the bush?"
"Mister... better
build a toilet now."
Hey...
Stop!
Keshav, stop. Stop.. Keshav.
Leave him Keshav. What
are you doing? Leave me.
Keshav. Leave me.
Get lost...
Don't come in front of me.
- What happened, brother?
- Naru, the calamity's been averted.
A Brahmin's home was saved
from getting tainted.
Nothing is ever going
to change here.
If you get hurt, apply dirt.
If you get a sprain, apply s***
If shitting and toilets
are such a bad thing...
...then why did God
give us a stomach?
No stomach, no loo.
Headman, open your
scriptures and tell me...
Is it our moral obligation to make
a spectacle out of our wife...
...or does shit out in the
open give us salvation?
Tell me!
Savri... you don't feel
embarrassed having six kids.
But you feel embarrassed
to talk about toilets.
People like them associate
shame with religion.
You people.
You should be ashamed.
Panditji... you were
so embarrassed...
...to read about your
daughter-in-law in the newspaper.
But no shame in peeing
out in the gutter.
It's quite obvious that
the women are fleeing.
We're stuck in this
blind game of religion.
Pretty soon... no one will ever give
you their daughter's hand again.
Everyone will die as bachelors.
Go on...
Go home... celebrate.
Tell stories to your children...
About how we brave-hearts
broke Keshav's Taj Mahal!
Go on... tell them!
Grandma...
Grandma... set the
plate for your son.
He'll break his fast today.
He just broke the entire house.
He broke everything.
"I feel so unfortunate."
"I don't deserve you."
"Nothing's more..."
"complicated than love."
Yeah, Jaya. I tried everything.
We must wait for 11 months.
No, Keshav.
Don't call me again.
And if you think I am joking,
then don't be mistaken.
I have an idea.
I'll get the Goswami Road fixed.
I'll get it fixed from my quota.
Look what's published in the
newspaper, village-head.
Calamity has befallen
on our village.
Divorce for a toilet.
Our village has been jinxed.
This is a complete disaster.
Our village will be disgraced
in the entire district.
Too much education
isn't good either.
This is really bad.
Brother Keshav is doomed.
Where can he go? He can't
stay in this village anymore.
There's been no divorce in our
village for the last 1700 years.
This is really
terrible, Panditji.
What can I say?
I never imagined I'll ever
hear this word in my life.
She wants a divorce.
Does she think it's a joke?
Sir, isn't he the same
Keshav who came to meet you?
No, he's the same 'Keshav'
who started 'Mahabharata’.
That 'Keshav' matter is
getting a lot of attention.
We're here to
interview his wife.
I'll tell you once I get there.
Keep the bathroom
in the background.
This story is about Jaya
from Sabrana village...
...who is going to divorce her husband
just 6 months after their wedding.
Reason; toilet.
Jaya, are you actually divorcing
your husband for a toilet?
Don't you think this
reason is good enough?
You've been here since morning.
You came all the way from Delhi.
Did you use the bathroom?
Actually, we have a vanity
van, which has a...
That's why you think this
is not an actual problem.
I advise you to stay here one
night. Go out with LOTA party.
Sit out in the open amongst snakes,
scorpions and other animals.
And then you'll
realize my problem.
See... she's openly describing
her deeds on television.
Keshav, do you think that the
government is responsible?
Honestly, we're to
be blamed first.
The scam happened because
we didn't want a toilet.
We love our fields.
And the government distributed
free notebooks to the children...
...but didn't tell them
what to write in them.
They built toilets, but didn't
teach anyone how to use it.
This is the government's
responsibility as well.
They only carried out
half of their tasks.
But the government has been
promoting this campaign a lot.
And built around 6 million
toilets in the last three years.
They built toilets..
..but it's high time the government
made certain laws as well.
What laws?
Use toilets for defecating.
Keshav, you built a
toilet in your home.
Who broke that?
The men of our country feel really
proud to do it out in the open.
Some narrow-minded
guy broke my toilet.
- So...
- Actually, it was my father.
So you mean to say you'll never
do it out in the open again.
Well, back in the days I
would stand anywhere.
But now I'll only stand
up for a bathroom.
You must have faced a lot of
humiliation for this divorce.
If I make a mistake, I'm
bound to get insulted.
There must be a
toilet in the house.
There must be a toilet in
the house for the women.
So that, men can stop them
from wandering outside.
Wonderful, madam. Such a twisted
question for such a simple answer.
Are you from foreign channel?
Real freedom isn't about
going out to defecate.
It's about going out
on your own free will.
But who will explain
to these idiots?
Our fight is against...
this. Their views.
Their views.
But if you lose this fight,
you can lose your wife too.
I can lose her in the
open jungle as well.
[would rather lose
her like this.
It's quite simple, madam.
If you want your wife, you
got to have a toilet.
Jaya, who do you think is
responsible for this divorce.
The government or our tradition.
The women... who'll set out
again tomorrow at dawn.
Jaya from Sabrana village is still
steadfast on her decision of a divorce.
Will this affect the government
officials in anyway?
There's going to be a war.
All our past scams will
get exposed, Yadav.
Do you get it?
I guess even we'll have to
bathe out in the open now.
I can see stars
in daylight, sir.
I told you before...
You should've carried
out a part of the work.
Now the CM's called
for a meeting.
This is wrong, Swamiji.
This country will
never progress.
What was the result
of this movement?
Build toilets! Build toilets!
Calm down!
Our country is going backwards.
Well, there's been some
activity within the government.
From 11 months, its
come down to 10 months.
If the government functions any faster
then it will definitely collapse.
I'm a Brahmin too.
I'll have water as well as tea.
Yes, I'll get it.
Tell me something, Pandit.
Do you watch Sunny
Leone's movies?
Radhe-Radhe.
Is this what you wanted to ask?
You've been living alone
for so many years.
I'm sure you watch it secretly.
This was expected from you.
One can see your values
reflecting in your daughter.
That's true.
We taught her to speak up,
instead of staying quiet.
Your values about entering this
house with the help of a lie.
The values of maligning the family honor
by giving an interview on television.
And complicating a simple
issue like a toilet.
Even you admit it's an
uncomplicated issue.
So build a toilet at home too.
1 see...
So you want us to
build a toilet...
...in the same courtyard
where we Pray to 'Tulsi'.
Unbelievable, Panditji.
You Pray to the Ganga as well.
But don't you wash
your sins in it too?
You won't build a
toilet in your home...
...but, you've turned the
entire country into a big loo.
You can open your zipper, or untie
your draw-strings wherever you like.
Change with time.
Change?
And forget our culture.
People like you have reduced
culture to just 'Sanskrit.'
Joshi... we live
for our culture...
...and we Pandits can
even die for our culture.
I know you got
Japanese degrees...
...but, have you ever
read the holy scriptures?
Lord Krishna addressed a
grave problem in Gita.
The world fights with each other but
only the brave fights with himself.
If you can conquer over
yourself, Pandit...
...then, you can save the children's
world from falling apart.
And remember...
If you change nothing,
nothing will chance.
Radhe-Radhe.
There's nothing more
we can do, Keshav.
We failed to rattle the government
or change father's opinion.
All our plans backfired.
Even our plans of getting
a 'divorce' failed-.
So what?
Tomorrow morning we'll go to the court
and withdraw our divorce petition.
We'll leave our home...
...and build our
own little abode.
I cannot break
your home, Keshav.
But I can break this marriage.
This isn't just my fight alone.
Every daughter, every
woman has her eyes on me.
If I give up now...
...no woman will ever fight
for her right again.
See... now you sound
like a leader.
Sorry...
I couldn't be your wife.
You became my wife the day you served
father dinner after the entire fiasco...
...and even went
out to the fields.
And today... when you're
prepared to leave me...
...to bring a change
in this country.
That's more like Keshav's wife.
And as far as our
divorce is concerned...
Give me your phone.
Here...
I've deleted your number.
I can even walk the
gallows for you.
Divorce is a very small step.
See you tomorrow at
the family court.
Radhe-Radhe.
Come on... I'll drop you home.
I swear I won't elope
with you. Come on.
"Quit smiling, silly,
or I'll fall in love."
"I used to feel... love's
too far-fetched for me..."
"...because I have no dreams."
"I am completely
lost in your eyes."
"Like sandalwood
dissolves in water."
"The heart's willing
to do anything."
"Quit smiling, silly,
or I'll fall in love."
These days if there's an
argument the wife quits home.
Even if the husband's
Hrithik Roshan.
You're absolutely right.
That Joshi's daughter
didn't give up.
She's going to the court...
They might even get divorced.
Honestly speaking, her
husband really loved her.
Yes.
Didn't you see... he
tried his level best.
But to what avail?
Just another charade
without a reason.
For such small things who creates
an issue. She only made a scene.
Who runs away from home and demands
divorce for such trivial issues?
I thought her demand was valid.
What did she ask for?
Poor thing wasn't used to
going out in the open...
...what else could
she have done?
So now she can sit in
her toilet proudly.
And us?
We'll keep going
out... like we do.
You know... what would've happened
if we had made the same demand?
Don't talk to me in Jaya's tone.
What happened?
She only brought
disgrace to our village.
- Come on... serve dinner.
- I didn't cook dinner.
What do you mean you
didn't cook dinner?
If we eat, we'll have to go.
No food, no going out.
Have you lost your mind?
Actually, it all
makes sense now.
- Vimu...
- Who?
- Oh, my...
- Mother!
What happened?
- What happened?
- I think I broke a bone.
But how did you fall down?
- Someone spilled oil here.
- Oil?
I was going towards the field.
Quickly, take me to the field.
Hurry up... quickly. Pick me up.
Mother...
No.. I don't think I can
walk all the way to the field.
- And I can't control it any longer either.
- Mother..
- Quickly... lift me up.
Can I go in there?
What are you thinking?
Your mother is dying!
Quickly... lift me up.
Mother, no.. No..
Lift me up.
Lift me up. Oh, God! Oh, God!
Careful.
Quickly, take me. Take me, son.
Take me quickly. Oh, God!
We can't defecate
out in the open!
if Jaya Joshi gets a divorce...
...then, we'll all
get a divorce.
We can't defecate
out in the open!
We'll fight. Take
down our request.
This is not the way.
Why don't you understand? This
is not how you get a divorce.
I request you, please go away.
- We also want a divorce.
- Just go from here.
We've all heard about
mass marriages...
...but never about mass
divorce before today.
One reason; toilet.
This is a challenge
to the government.
- Verma.
- Yes, sir.
What is this?
Bureaucracy, sir.
From society welfare
committee to the village...
...the files have to go
through seven offices.
And they all have their...
Understood!
Verma, do one thing today.
Then buy seven locks...
...and lock all the
toilets in those offices.
Sir..
No one will go to the
toilet for seven days.
Those who want to go will have
to find a solution himself.
But, sir..
Only the wounded knows the
pain, and no one else.
But, sir, how is that possible?
If our Prime Minister can ban notes
for the country's benefit...
...then we can
close toilets too.
Yes, sir.
Jaya Joshi left her husband's
home on 15th February.
And today they are meeting
directly in the court.
And the reason for their separation
is the 3000 Cr toilet scam.
We've never had a divorce
in the last 1700 years.
If Lord Krishna
returns to Radha...
...will Rukmini divorce Him?
Quarrels should be
solved at home.
- And not made a public spectacle.
- You're right.
No one's ever said that
we should use a toilet...
...then what is this
feud all about?
I wish Keshav had understood
the chapter on Manusmriti...
...then he wouldn't be
facing this problem.
Seems like people are
against building toilets.
They believe it's
against their culture.
You tell me...
What about the Prime Minister's
'Cleanliness Drive'?
If we build a toilet at home then
how can we keep our homes clean?
So that's their opinion about
the 'Cleanliness Drive'.
A village where toilets
are deemed unhygienic...
...are bound to
have such divorces.
Hello.
Madam, sign on this urgently.
- Madam... madam...
- Hold on.
- Jaya...
- What is it?
Will it be easy for your daughter to
live in the village after this divorce?
Why?
Is she causing
floods or doomsday?
No, I...
Did anyone in your family
ever have a divorce before?
Forget my family, let's
talk about the country.
Did anyone ever have a
divorce for a toilet?
My daughter will set an
example. Come along.
Do you think divorce is the
solution to this problem?
It is the solution
to my problems.
- One more question...
- That's enough... Come on, move aside.
Sir-sir... you tried your level
best to save your marriage.
But, if this is only
about a toilet then..
..why didn't you go
live with your wife?
Yes, that's a nice idea.
But I don't know how to
run from my problems.
Sir, it's not that sunny...
...yet you're
wearing sunglasses.
Are you trying to
hide your tears?
Look, madam, everyone's
blinded by fake pride.
And anyway, these
are fake Raybans.
But the world has a
real one on their eyes.
Are you going to challenge
the government after this?
It's your job to blame the
government for everything.
You should take some
responsibilities yourself.
Keshav, are you sad that
your wife's leaving you?
No, I love it.
Now I'll get a new
wife for myself.
- Come on, that's enough.
- Sir, just one more question.
- Sir.. Sir.. Please sir.
- That's enough.
I feel that everything
will be fine.
They don't know how to talk.
I mean...
These people are getting
divorced as well.
I don't know.
- Radhe-Radhe.
- Greetings. Greetings.
We didn't have so many
guests even at our wedding.
I haven't seen our
wedding video yet.
But our divorce is being broadcast
live on national television.
Fix your hair, sweetheart.
Quit smiling silly,
I'll fall in love.
Time now for a small break.
On the other side of the break we'll
show you Jaya and Keshav's signatures.
Stay with us on Abhi
Tak Channel, live.
After this divorce, the people are
going to divorce this government.
Because this is their
biggest failure.
Judging by the size of this issue, this
was a controversy waiting to happen.
If what Keshav and
Jaya are doing...
...ushers in a change
then it's always welcome.
You see, I was the first one to
report this news in my newspaper.
But I never thought it
would escalate to divorce.
It's all due to the narrow-mindedness
of these ignorant.
But brother Keshav
tried his best.
Jaya and Keshav.
Do you two still stand
firm on your decision?
Yes...
No toilet, no marriage.
Sir, this letter has arrived
from the CM's office.
The court rejects Jaya and
Keshav's plea for divorce.
The government has accepted
Keshav's request...
...for building a
toilet in his village.
The construction begins tomorrow morning
on the ground outside the village.
Until then... the villagers will
be facilitated with porta-loo.
- Why are you sulking?
- Nothing.
Congratulations, brother.
The file which went nowhere in 12
months got sanctioned in 12 minutes.
And do you know what the
Chief Minister did?
He locked all the toilets
in every government office.
That's when these officers
learned their lesson.
Remember what you said
at Mr. Mathur's office.
"Until the problem
doesn't get personal..."
"...no one's willing to
fight, find a solution."
You were absolutely
right, brother.
What's wrong now, Keshav.
We found a solution and
did the impossible.
We got the toilet.
Jaya, I promised to give
you your personal toilet.
I couldn't do it.
Maybe not personal, but at
least there's a toilet.
- I am happy.
- I couldn't change father's view either.
I can't take you
back in that house.
Keshav!
You'll always be a numbskull.
You fought against
the entire world...
...and now you say you
won't take her home.
Daughter-in-law, let this be.
The fake charades, fake
thumb, fake pride.
Leave all this behind and
then step inside the house.
- Is he sick?
- I think so.
I am not sick, son.
In fact, I am better now.
You see...
It's time to take the
blind off our eyes...
...and put it on the toilet.
That's wonderful, father.
- That's wonderful.
- Sorry, daughter-in-law. Sorry.
For the first time, I've
done something good.
So only daughter-in-law
will inaugurate my toilet.
- My toilet, father?
- Yes.
But brother sold his
bike to pay for this..
- ..you didn't spend a penny.
- Get lost... shut up.
- Just a thought, father.
- Let it be.
- This isn't right.
- Quiet.
No.. No.. Come on.
- What happened?
- Sister-in-law, look here.
Brother Keshav... Group
photo. Yes. Yes.
Ready.
Written in scriptures.
Humans should not perform daily
action in front of the sun or moon.
Then the use of the toilet
should be made mandatory.
I had already told Keshav.
This sacrifice has to be done in the
interest of cleanliness of the people.
Children get used to going to
the toilet since childhood.
If you defecation in the
open, you will beat.
Getting big pleasure.
My life has changed.
Father did not approve of this.
But said no. Toilets
will be definitely made.
Why do sister-in-law
go out to toilet.
Or why should any woman
go out? This is wrong.
Congratulations to
Keshav and Jaya.
Now the women of the house do not
have to go away in the open.
Keshav is right. 'If you want your
wife, you got to have a toilet.'
The money that the government
gave us to make toilets...
...we returned them.
Do we take money from the
government to buy TVs and freeze?
Then why take money
to make toilet.
The toilets will be
made by our own money.
Remember....
'If you want your wife, you
got to have a toilet.'