'That's life...'
'One moment, they were cruising
through the beautiful valleys.'
'And now...'
'They are hanging on the wall.'
'But, what will you
call these identical twins?'
'Lucky...or Unlucky?'
'Unlucky because their
parents are no more.'
'And lucky, because these twins...'
'...didn't fall apart
like the 'Twin Towers.'
'Presenting their bachelor
uncle Kartar Singh.'
'It took him a day and a half...'
'...to realize that raising
them is not his cup of tea.
'And so...he estranged the children,
like himself.'
'He gave the child on his left...'
'...to his sister Jeeto
who lived in London.'
'And, the kid on his right...'
'...to his brother Baldev.'
'Who in the world gives
children like this?'
'Thing's got complicated.'
'They were brother's...'
'...but now, they became cousins.'
Jeeto was their aunt...'
...but now,
she's a mother to one of the kids.'
'Baldev was their uncle...'
'...but now he's the
father of the other.'
'Kartar is still their uncle,
but it's complicated.'
'A single accident
changed everything.'
'But there's one thing
that hasn't changed.'
'These two were identical twins...'
...and they still look...identical.'
"O Lord... Almighty."
"We begin every task with thy name."
"We wield your sacred bracelet."
"We never hear no
evil...or speak no evil."
"We set examples for others."
"There's none like us..."
"Our gait's like a lion!"
"Our swag's trend-setting."
"We're perfect in every field."
"We look handsome in suit and shoes."
"And wet tresses."
"Collars straight..."
"...but we're rustic at heart."
"Don't try to mess with us."
"Jatt arrives riding a Jaguar.."
"...with gorgeous girls in tow."
"We're Sardars after all..."
"...we spend our lives having fun."
"We get high and party all night."
"And next morning wakeup late."
"Girls say...be my babe."
"And steal my heart."
"Our car flies...in the air."
"Our car flies in the air."
"We always say to the world."
"Jatt arrives riding a Jaguar.."
"...with gorgeous girls in tow."
"We respect one and all."
"We love everyone, big and small."
"We belong to a brave community."
"Never stab anyone in the back."
"Its quite simple..."
"...don't waste your time."
"...don't waste your
time in useless things."
"We're Sardars after all..."
"...we spend our lives having fun."
"Jatt arrives riding a Jaguar.."
"...with gorgeous girls in tow."
What? Are you in the same mall?
Yeah...what to do.
I came here shopping with my mom.
Who does shopping with his mom?
Mama's boy!
Are you okay?
Hey...what are you giggling about?
- Excuse me!
Excuse you? Why?
- Here's your bag.
Hello.
- They just flock here from India.
Hello... you're not
exactly chinese either.
Huh...
Sweety, who are you arguing with now?
This old lady slipped on her own...
...and now she's yelling at me.
Old...! You called me 'old'.
What else should I call you? Baby?
Oh, my...lil' sweet baby...
did you fall down?
Did you get hurt, baby?
Which old lady are
you s***ng with now?
Wait... Wait and
watch what I do to you.
What can you do?
My son's in this mall too.
- So is my boyfriend.
So call him... and we'll
let them fight it out.
Karan!
She's my mom!
Mom! Mom! Mom!
Right... I get it... Mom!
Now call your boyfriend.
And watch Karan beat
the crap out of him.
How can I beat the crap out of myself?
- Huh?
I mean... where's your boyfriend?
I'll beat the crap out of him!
Where is he? Where is he?
No-no-no-no-no, aunty...
I am very sorry.
It was completely my fault...
my mistake. Please forgive me.
She's genuinely apologizing mom,
let her go.
Not even if she apologizes
a thousand times.
After all, I am 'Old'.
Old?
- Oh, my...lil' sweety...did you fall down?
She called me 'Old'.
- No...
What now? What now?
I'll get coffee for you.
- Yeah...
... without sugar.
- No-no-no...
She will slip poison into it.
Never.
Her boyfriend must be blind...
that's why he's still with her.
She will treat him like a servant.
I pity her father-in-law.
Aunty...
- And no respect for her mother-in-law.
Who is this Binkle?
I had no clue that mom...
I knew that 'old'...
I mean, your mom was definitely
going to cause trouble.
And how did this Binkle
suddenly come in the picture.
No, actually, we already knew...
- I see...
So, you were already planning this.
Sweety, Binkle is Mr. Sandhu's daughter.
Sandhu sir helped dad
in setting up business.
He's our Godfather.
- I see...
And now you're planning
on making him your Father...
...and repay that favor.
I was only time-pass for you.
- Time-pass?
Sweety, as soon as
you finished your course...
...I followed you all the way here.
I've been stirring ladies all day...
You think I like
this restaurant and all.
Who am I doing it for? You of course.
But what's the point?
You've been saying for the last six
months that you'll talk to your uncle.
Then, your uncle will
talk to your mother.
Everything will be rocking.
But what actually happened?
You should talk to your mom directly.
Did you leave me a choice?
I told you I will introduce you to
my mom when the time is right.
But, no. You went and
introduced yourself to her.
"That Old lady slipped.
That Old lady slipped."
All moms are old.
But you don't call them 'Old'.
Fine, but what do we do next?
Sandhu's are interested in our family.
- Yeah, so?
So Binkle will get married...
...and in our family.
So...
You promised you'll talk.
Father was in a bad mood yesterday.
The fritters were burnt.
Now our future depends on fritters.
Look Nafisa,
papa's flying to London tomorrow...
...to discuss Karan's wedding.
So, in his absence
I'll talk with aunt Jeeto.
So you're not angry anymore?
- No...
You said 'absence'.
It's the effect of your company.
Charan, you'll have to
talk to your father someday.
So aunt Jeeto will talk to him.
Father reveres her like God.
He can never say no to her.
And anyway, aunt Jeeto doesn't
have a problem with you guys.
'You guys'?
You mean Muslim angle.
Doesn't matter if its Muslim,
Christian or Gujarati.
They are all outsiders for father.
He wants a proper,
Sikh, daughter-in-law.
I can't do this anymore.
Hello.
Tittu...
- Hello.
Keep stirring the lentil.
But only I will temper it.
Hello, uncle.
- Hello, son.
Bless you...
Have you finished packing?
- Uncle, do I have to go?
Of course not, I'll go marry her.
"Uncle, do I have to go."
We're talking about
your marriage, stupid!
But uncle,
I don't want to get married right now.
Why?
I still have to learn
so much from you.
And, I still have to open a chain
of 'Purani Haveli' (Restaurants)!
chain?
- Yeah...
New York, London, Paris, Switzerland.
International?
- Uncle...
Uncle! We haven't opened up yet...
It's still work in progress.
But how are you going to do it?
You hardly come to the restaurant.
Maybe once in a couple of weeks.
But I always finish my work.
Right, Tittu?
- Yes.
It's a talent, uncle. God gift.
You see, even in my
school and college days...
...I would study a day or two
before the exams and top my class.
A guy should be smart-working,
not hard-working.
Fine, son, but...
- You know, uncle.
I love you the most.
- I do, son.
But sister Jeeto insists
we cannot miss this proposal.
Binkle is a great girl.
Even our boy is nothing
short than best.
Boy?
- charan.
I know his name starts with C...
...but he's the best.
charan?
- charan!
Charan.
What happened, Dad?
Why did you make so many calls?
My shift is over.
I'm coming back to home.
Hello, mom.
- Bless you, son.
Ready? - It's all coincidence, sister.
- That's true.
And Charan is a lucky boy.
- Yes.
Hello, aunty.
Bless you! Are you happy?
Huh!
- Happy?
Why wouldn't he be happy?
- Charan, where's your black sweater?
My black sweater?
- It's cold out there.
Baldev, did you speak with Charan?
What's to ask?
Whatever I saw is final.
Brother, which one should I pack?
- Fine... see you tomorrow.
I'll pack all three.
- Kartar will receive you at the airport.
Okay, sister. Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
Why are you packing my stuff?
Now your going to see the girl.
But Karan was supposed to see the girl...
- Now, it's going to be you.
He's going to open a chain.
chain?
- Aunty, Charan's black sweater.
I don't want to get married.
Why don't you want to get married?
Any girlfriend angle?
No... no...
- So what's the problem?
Why are you saying no?
- I never said no.
Congratulations, uncle.
He said 'yes'.
I never said 'yes'.
Are you stupid?
You're neither saying yes nor no.
Uncle, I think he's embarrassed.
I'm sure his heart's
jumping with glee.
We've to wake up
early morning tomorrow.
So get some sleep.
Minto... is dinner ready?
I always heard that
brother sc*** brother.
But now I've seen it.
What are you saying?
I'm your elder brother.
And you know, I love you the most.
And listen,
I planned everything carefully.
Binkle is a very good girl.
If she's such a good girl,
why don't you marry her?
She's not my type,
she's too simple and well-behaved.
What do you mean by well-behaved?
Do you want a naughty wife?
No, I want Sweety... I mean,
someone sweet, sexy and happening.
And what's all this
talk about a 'chain'?
Fine, I'll take it off.
Can't seem to open it.
And anyway,
no one gets any peace after marriage.
I am not going to London.
Brother Baldev has landed.
Where do I park?
I am coming, brother.
No Smoking's fine...
...but, I don't see a
'No Parking' board anywhere.
Let's park here.
Good old 'No Parking'.
Papa, Uncle Kartar's here.
- Brother.
He's here?
Greetings, brother.
Greetings.
Feels so nice.
How are you, Kartar?
It's the grace of God.
Greetings, uncle. - Oh, no-no-no,
don't touch my feet, my lad.
Turban looks good on you.
come on, my boy.
Where's your car, Kartar?
- There it is, brother.
Uncle...you're being fined.
Hello, sir... you under the car.
The London Police isn't smart enough
to get money out of Kartar.
Come on.
Sir, I am talking to you.
- Excuse me, officer.
Any problem? - You know you have
parked in a No Parking zone.
What to do?
The car broke down, sir.
And why isn't your
mechanic talking to me?
Oh, he's deaf and dumb I see.
- Yes officer.
Right... Get your car
fixed as soon as possible.
Thanks, officer.
- And be on your way
come on, boy...come out!
You've grown heavy.
- What the...
What's this, Kartar?
- Indian style, brother.
Let's move, shall we?
Get in the truck.
So young man,
you're finally taking the leap.
You must be really happy.
- Why not?
Not like you...
Wasting your whole
life for one person?
Forget it, brother. Forget it...
Only old whiskey tastes nice,
not old memories.
Where are we going?
I built a second home in London.
My very own Mini Punjab.
Wow... this is amazing.
Mini Punjab in London.
Here guys, have some buttermilk.
Bring it on...man.
You've turned Jolly
into a complete Punjabi.
He's still learning, brother.
When he starts swearing...
...that's when he'll
be a complete Punjabi.
I've been calling for so long, Charan.
Why weren't you answering my calls?
- I've planted vegetables.
I was with Papa and Kartar uncle.
- Potatoes...
Kartar uncle? Where are you?
London!
- London?
What the hell are you doing in London?
Oh yes, Kartar.
Here's your stuff you asked for.
Oh my, my, my... the soil of Punjab.
Jolly, my bro, come here.
- Yeah.
Sprinkle this soil of
Punjab all over the farm.
It should smell like home.
Go on, scatter it around.
But Nafisa,
I don't want to marry her either.
Good! So no need to
go over to the Sandhus. - Yes.
And, let me know if
you're still going over.
So I can My tell father...
...to find a real man for me
Charan!
You've been glued to the phone.
Come here.
Yes...coming.
- Brother, you're a grown up now...
...but, still no
change in your temper.
Shoots up like BP suddenly.
Charan, we're getting late.
Jolly, my bro...
- Yeah.
Sprinkle some of the soil in the backyard.
- Okay.
Sister.
Mom-Dad, uncle's here.
- They are.
Brother...
- Greetings, uncle. - Bless you...
Hello, brother-in-law.
What took you so long?
- Come here, my Sunshine.
Baldev!
Sister.
Hello, sister.
- Bless you.
My brother.
Don't you miss your sister?
- You're crying, sister.
Of course,
we're meeting after 5 years.
We just had a video-chat yesterday
Isn't there a difference between chatting
on video and meeting face-to-face?
Can I slap you on screen?
Look at him.
- Hello, sister.
Bless you.
He's all grown up now.
Just like Karan.
Naughty...
Feels just like yesterday.
You used to prance around
in the courtyard naked.
"Aunty, Karan hit me.
Aunty, I am hungry."
And look at him now.
The young man's off to get married.
The lad's grown up, huh!
If only brother and
sister-in-law were alive.
They would've been so happy
to see their son get married.
No, sister.
Don't cry, Let's go.
One must not shed tears
on joyous occasions.
Yes.. - Let's go inside.
Come on. - Come inside.
Go easy on the drink, Kartar.
There's no such thing as 'Easy'
or 'Gentle' in Kartar's dictionary.
He's right.
- He'll never learn.
Mr. Singh.
- Yes.
It's 1 am.
- But my brother's here from India.
So for the next three days...
"Do not Disturb"!
Yes... go sleep, my lovely neighbor.
Look at them.
- They love there family so much.
Nice Jolly.
Tell me something, sister...
Is Mr. Sandhu happy
with this alliance?
Why wouldn't he be happy?
He's more interested in
a relationship with our family.
Doesn't matter if its Karan or charan.
In fact, he was saying that...
...post wedding he'll have an excuse
to visit Punjab more frequently.
But Ballu, are you happy?
Sister...
For us, it's God up there
and down here it's you.
You said it... end of story.
So is brother-in-law's bottle.
Come, Charan, let's get another
bottle for brother-in-law.
come, my boy. come.
Yes, uncle. - charan, go. - Brother-in-law,
don't you think you're drinking too much.
Yeah... All thanks to Kartar.
What's the matter?
- And now charan's going with Kartar.
God save that boy.
- What's the problem?
What?
- Uncle...
Then why come here?
Why didn't you tell your father?
You know him...
Is your girlfriend
from a decent family?
She's from a great family.
Her father's a doctor, mother is cA.
And Nafisa is a lawyer herself.
Then what's the problem?
What did you say her name was?
Nafisa...
Nafisa. And...
- Yes.
Qureshi.
- Qureshi!
Nafisa Qureshi!
Your father doesn't even
allow Mughlai dishes on his menu.
And you fell for a Mughlai girl?
Mughlai?
You make it sound like
she's Akbar's niece.
She has no association or connection
with the Mughals, uncle.
Association'... 'Connection'...
Such big words.
I hope you've not forgotten Punjabi.
Hey, Kartar.
- High...
Stupid...
Bloody drug addict.
Look, charan.
- Yes.
We could've handled anyone else.
But, we cannot say no to Sandhu sir.
- Correct.
Only he can reject you.
But why will he reject me?
Yeah...you don't have
any bad habits or vices.
What happened, uncle?
I found a vice.
- You did.
I know one of your bad habits.
- You do.
If Sandhu finds out that
you're a drug addict, then...
But who will believe
that I am a drug addict?
You just landed from Punjab.
Haven't you seen 'Udta Punjab.'
If has a small doubt...
...then this wedding
will get cancelled.
Let's think of another idea, uncle.
You think I am Bernard Shaw.
I came up with this
idea after watching him.
Another idea?
This one's good.
Come... come, my lad.
Good morning, Ma'am.
Did you see their house?
- Welcome.
Come on, let's start. Udta Punjab.
How is it?
Are you okay, my lad?
Are you okay?
What's wrong with him?
- What happened?
What happened?
- He was feeling sick in the car.
He's going to see the girl,
so he's just scared.
Be brave my boy.
come.
- Sandhu sir. Sandhu sir.
Hello, Sandhu sir.
- Welcome. Greetings. - Hello.
Sister-in-law was telling me...
...that, you own a
big restaurant in Punjab
It's the grace of God.
Enough to make a living.
Is it a vegetarian restaurant?
No, son. We make meat and fish too.
Except for Mughlai.
What..
- It's called 'Purani Haveli'.
Purani Haveli.
- It's a really nice name, very nice.
Yes, very nice name.
Charan, do you work
at the restaurant...
...or do you do something else?
He's a car dealer.
- Yes.
He's a got a big showroom.
Is he dumb?
- Why?
Why?
Let him speak. Come on, bro.
I have a car dealership.
Renault. Renault Showroom.
Is everything okay, charan?
Yes, uncle.
Go get Binkle.
- Yeah...that's good.
Yes... go get her.
His face turned red
like a monkey's bum...
...on hearing Binkle's name.
He's always been a shy kid.
Stays away from girls.
- I see...
Meaning?
- I mean... he's got more guy friends.
Take Facebook for instance.
He has 609 friends.
All boys.
No females, only male.
He's a very friendly guy.
Kartar.
Dad, could he be one of those?
You know, too-friendly.
- Like you know everything.
Aah... that's Binkle.
Hello.
- Hello, dear. Bless you.
- Hello.
Binkle dear, won't you
show Charan around the house?
Go on, son.
- Go, son.
Go, boy. It's your day.
Rock...
Rock!
Go.
What happened?
- Careful, son.
charan, are you feeling okay?
Be careful.
What are you saying, Kartar?
He's feeling okay. Looks absolutely fine.
- I don't think so, brother.
He was puking all the way.
- I see...
He was sweating,
shaking, his hands were shivering.
No-no-no...maybe it's jet lag.
Since when did 'Jatts'
start getting jetlag?
I think there is a problem.
Very worrying.
Well, you can ask anything you want.
What can I ask?
It's my first time.
Mine too...
Well, I'll ask then...
Do you have a...
What happened?
- Nothing.
I was asking...
Do you have a girlfriend?
I...
- You can take it if it's important.
It is important.
Hello... Hello...
It got disconnected.
Strange... we don't
have a network issue.
So... why can't you get a connection?
'Don't worry. I'll break this allience.'
Are you okay?
My throat... Water...
- Yeah, sure...
Thank you.
Wait, Uncle, let me first
decide what I want in life.
Manpreet,
you had a friend called Happy.
His hands would shiver,
he would sweat...
What was his problem?
No problem...
He used to do drugs.
Have some more, uncle.
Drugs?
- You're right.
So drugs lead to these problems?
He really respects his elders.
Does charan...
No-no-no, he's a good boy.
- It's hard to find kids like him.
IN fact, he's old school.
Excuse me.
So is Binkle...
- Hello.
Hello, uncle.
I think they make a good pair.
There's definitely
a network problem here.
Hello.
- Can't hear anything.
Hello. Hello...
Good Lord, someone has fallen.
Oh no.
- Who is it?
Who fell down? Charan fell down!
How did he fall down?
Charan.
- Get some water.
Son, call the doctor.
He's breathing. He's still breathing.
- Get some water.
Get some water. - Sandhu sir,
does this house have some water?
Someone get water.
- He's still breathing.
He's breathing.
- Someone get water.
You okay, my boy.
Get up, Tiger. Get up.
Get up.
He's okay.
- Get up.
But...how did this happen?
- Everything's okay...it's all okay.
Everything's okay...
it's all okay.
Sandhu sir,
now let's fix a wedding date.
come on, let's go inside.
come. - Come on.
- One minute!
Tell me honestly...
you do drugs, don't you?
Hey...
He's my son... My son!
He will never do anything wrong,
understand.
Uncle, this is a question
of Binkle's life.
My question is absolutely justified.
And yes, please don't shout.
I'm showing respect to your age...
Otherwise, I can yell louder than you.
Mani... behave yourself,
he's my father okay.
Hey... won't take me a
minute to set you straight.
Lower your eyes.
Mani, this is no way
to talk to the groom's family.
He's your future brother-in-law.
- What brother-in-law?
We haven't said yes...
Mani, you children are taking
this in the wrong direction.
You want me to let my sister marry
a drug addict. - Hold on... please...
Please-please-please...
Uncle wants to say something.
Please go ahead, uncle.
Sister-in-law...
- Yes.
Forgive me.
We don't want any kind
of relationship with such people.
Sandhu sir... what are you saying?
Hey... What do you
mean by 'such people'?
Baldev...
- Brother-in-law.
So... what did you
mean by 'such people'?
People like you...
...who don't have any manners?
I see... and your son's
very well behaved, isn't he?
Shameless...
Ballu, enough... stop it.
- What are you?
What are you?
Are you going to teach us manners?
Nonsense...
People like you...
wait over a month...
...for an appointment with me.
customers wait outside
my restaurant for over an hour.
Purani Haveli is famous
all over Chandigarh.
Purabi Haveli...
Sounds like the name
of some old horror film.
Beware... don't you dare
insult my business! Understand!
Do you know what we
call businessmen like you?
Hawkers!
- Sandhu.
Someone shut up that dog.
Sandhu sir, what are you saying?
Dog and all... it's appalling.
I would've left.
He's talking about shutting
up that dog. - Yeah!
Have you lost your mind, Kartar?
- Sorry, sister...
I thought...
- What did you think?
Who can dare to call me a dog?
Anyone who calls me a dog is a dog himself.
- Baldev!
Sister-in-law... take him away.
Sandhu sir.
Or there's no telling
what will happen here.
What will happen?
Will you seize our passports...
...or have us thrown behind bars.
Baldev, be quiet.
Did you come out here to build
a relationship or create a scene?
Blurting nonsense...
No respect for your
brother-in-law or your sister.
Apologize.
Sister, you want me to apologize.
Baldev...come,
apologize to Sandhu sir.
I said apologize.
Come, Charan. Come on.
- Don't go, Baldev.
I said don't go, Baldev.
- Uncle...
If you humiliate me...
- Baldev, Wait..
Wait, brother, I am coming too.
- Baldev...
Take me along too... I'm coming too.
Brother...
- Sandhu sir.
Hello.
- Hello, brother-in-law.
Yeah, Kuldeep.
Did you go see the girl?
Did charan like her?
Hello... Brother-in-law?
Hello.
Hello. Hello, sister-in-law.
Did you get the soil?
- Yes, I did.
But you didn't send
any pickles this time.
I will bring it along when I come
for the wedding. - Great...
Uncle, what you are doing?
Hello. What happened?
Yes, mom.
- Hello, son.
How's the girl? Did you like her?
Hello... charan?
Hello.
Hello. - What's wrong?
Why isn't anyone talking?
Kuldeep, I'll call you later.
Why later? Tell her now.
How you humiliated us.
Did I humiliate you?
And you didn't see what they did?
You were asking me to apologize...
...and you didn't say
a word to them, sister.
We would if it had been their fault.
No...why would it be their fault?
They are big people after all.
I am the hawker!
Did you buy a stall out there?
What?
Karan's planning to
open a chain of restaurants...
...so why did papa buy a stall?
- Quiet.
Forget it, brother.
He'll get married to
whoever is destined for him.
You shut up.
Destiny...
First, go find your destiny.
Let it be.
Sandhu Sir was right.
What was Sandhu sir right about?
Father...
- Shut up
Brother-in-law, tell me...
...what was Sandhu sir right about?
Listen...
A pauper can never become a prince.
Brother-in-law!
- Lower your voice.
I said to lower your voice.
This isn't Punjab, it's my home.
I know it's your home.
And I also know you built it...
...because of Sandhu sir's favors.
You're indebted to him,
so you go lick his feet.
Baldev!
- Baldev!
Brother's can do anything
for their sister's husband.
And you're taunting him...
insulting him.
Trying to intimidate
him... aren't you ashamed?
Aunty, please...
What please?
He was just a kid, when our parents...
He never had to ask
for anything twice.
I raised your father...like a mother.
And he says please...
Mom!
Sister...what was my fault?
No-no...if's entirely our fault.
You didn't do anything.
Now let's see how you get him married.
What do you mean?
I mean...
You can never find anyone
who can matchup to Binkle.
Enough! Enough, sister!
What do you think?
My son won't get married without you.
What's the date today?
Here, or in India?
- Here.
It's the 25th.
- What?
25th...
- 25th...
Next month on the 25th...
...I will get charan married!
I swear to God!
Oh, God!
Mom!
Did this get out of hand?
I told you...let's think
of a different idea.
Lonely...
I am Mr. Lonely...
I've no body...
For my own.
Follow me if you want a drink.
Lonely...
Nafisa? I can't believe
you have a girlfriend.
Why? Am I only fit to be a brother?
Good joke. Good joke.
Things got really messy here.
And you're laughing...
you think it's funny.
You know, dad and aunty...
- chill, man.
With a temper like that
he's bound to blow his top.
What did happen?
Everyone spoke loudly
in the heat of the moment.
And now...
Uncle will go meet
aunty while flying back.
And they will be back to normal.
The usual "My sister...my brother..."
You don't get it.
Papa has challenged aunt...
...that he'll get
me married in a month.
Relax bro, nothing is going to happen.
You don't get it.
Looking at papa's mood...
...he'll get me married to the
first girl he sees when he lands.
Even better.
The first girl he sees will be Nafisa.
Just tell uncle about her, okay.
Nafisa...
When are you going
to tell him about us?
Sweety, let me handle this first.
- Karan...
Then I'll bring Uncle straight to your
house to discuss our marriage. - Hello.
Where are you? Hello.
Hello. Stop biting your nails.
How did you know?
Because I am your elder brother.
And you know...
I love you the most.
- I know...I know.
You love me the most.
- So chill.
I'll bring Nafisa to the airport.
Just text me her number.
Bye...
- Hello... listen...
Nafisa at the airport?
See you...
Where are my glasses, dear?
It's alright, you sit. I'll go get it.
Forgive me, aunty.
Your father should be apologizing.
What happened?
Uncle and aunty are very upset.
It as unfair for poor Binkle as well.
Poor...
What did we do to poor Binkle?
In fact,
we're in trouble because of her.
What's her fault...
what's her mistake in all this, uncle?
Mistake.
Are you coming or not?
Yes.
Left without meeting me!
Who's that girl with Karan?
Don't know.
Papa, I think I forgot
my handkerchief in the airplane.
I'll go get it.
- Handkerchief... come along!
Stupid.
Hello, uncle.
- Bless you.
She is Nafisa.
- Greetings.
Hello.
Uncle, she's your daughter-in-law...
Didn't charan tell you?
charan?
I forgot my handkerchief...
I'll go get it.
Is it studded with diamonds?
Uncle, Nafisa is from Punjab.
Malerkotla.
She's a lawyer.
Let's talk later.
Did you get the car or
did you leave it in Malerkotla?
I did.
Let's go.
- Come.
What?
So, you didn't come
to London because of Nafisa?
No, uncle...
- The entire family thinks I am stupid!
I don't say 'chochi' for 'bread'!
No one says that for bread...
You fool, I meant I didn't
grow old under the sun.
Your mother will be really happy...
...to know that her son
is playing love games out here.
Uncle, I...
- Love her.
You should learn from Charan.
One holler...and he can't dare to
say anything instead of 'Yes Father'.
Uncle, Nafisa and I...
I don't care how old
your relationship is with her.
Uncle...
- Quiet, if you say another word, I...
I will jump out of this moving car.
- Uncle... - Papa...Papa...
Shut up!
Your papa thought I was his girlfriend,
and yet you didn't say anything.
You're never going
to tell your dad about me...
...and I can give that
to you in writing.
That's not true, Nafisa, I...
- Then what is it, Charan.
Will you please explain me in detail.
I want to tell...
- You know what I think.
You don't want us to get married.
This is disgusting.
Nafisa...Nafisa...
- You just forget me now.
Nafisa, at least listen to me.
Nafisa...
Bid her goodbye.
And...why didn't you tell uncle?
Father would've made
the aircraft land in midair.
I am thinking about
running away from home.
End of my troubles.
This is life, not some
Olympic race where you've to run.
Have you ever thought about uncle?
Get up.
Why? - You should've
asked 'why' before getting up.
charan, you're a Jatt.
Take God's name and
tell uncle everything.
When men dare, God helps.
I treated sister like God.
She even said...
...that I can never find
anyone who'll match up to Binkle.
Isn't Charan her son too?
That's the way she is.
Remember, she once gave us
an empty envelope on Baby's birthday.
The money fell out
of the open envelope.
You're too much.
Hawker... they called me a hawker.
Why that...
- Listen...
Hey, ice-cream!
People don't buy anything
from hawkers here.
If I ever catch you here again...
...I'll teach you a lesson
you'll never forget.
Please...
- Now get lost!
Didn't you hear? Keep moving.
- Listen...
I've heard that Binkle
is a really cute girl.
Even I like her, but...
Father, I've something to say.
She's a nice girl, father.
I was just saying that.
She's a nice girl, but her father...
Father?
When did you meet him?
Hey... Do you remember
that we went to London?
Yes, I do.
Then how could you
forget meeting her father?
No, I was talking
about a different father...
That father was abusing me.
This father was getting abused.
Which other father
are you talking about?
No, I...
- Son, be honest with me.
Do you do drugs?
- I don't, father.
Then why did the Sandhus
call you a druggie?
They must have noticed something!
Okay, tell me how you fell down.
Oh, God! Did you fall down?
Did you get hurt?
- He fell down two days ago.
Can I talk to him now?
But how did he fall down?
- Ask him.
Ask him... ask him.
What happened?
I wasn't getting any signal on
the phone, so... - I don't either...
What should I do?
Should I fall down? Tell me...
Should I fall down too?
No signal.
Son.
- What a mess.
He's definitely a druggie.
He's definitely doing drugs.
- No.
Charan can never do such a thing.
- Don't know.
I've already challenged
them for charan's marriage.
But fixing him is a challenge as well.
You know,
druggies look normal on the outside.
But they are completely
abnormal on the inside.
Lord...have mercy.
O Benevolent One...
I've everything one can ask for.
Fame, fortune, respect...
4000 trucks.
All I seek now is a decent
suitor for my daughter.
Praise the Lord.
Lord, I am grateful.
Help me.
Where did he go?
Papa...
- Sir...
Yes, dear.
Hello.
- Hello.
Papa, please tell
us who are these people.
They are really great people.
I already made it very clear.
The wedding must happen this month.
And what a sweet girl. Proper Sikhni.
And not from a different community.
Charan.
- Yes.
Jwar Nagar. Do you know?
- No, I don't.
I do, uncle. Take a right.
'I can't find anyone
who will matchup to Binkle.'
Kuldeep,
she's a really beautiful girl.
You'll see for yourself.
Ask someone for directions
to New Market, Mata's Temple.
Take a left. Take the next left.
Son...
- Yes.
You seem to know a lot in six months.
Does Nafisa live here?
No, papa, Nafisa lives in Sector 17.
Karan was telling me.
Karan, left or right? Left or right?
- Right!
18... 17...
We're here... no. 16.
We've arrived.
Take it in... yeah, in...
Is it this one with the tractor?
- Why?
Don't you like the tractor's color?
- No, it's a great color. Red.
Danger...
- Huh!
Nothing, let's go.
Pick it up! Pick it up! Pick it up!
Sweety, pick up your phone.
"My beloved's come home, O Lord."
He's here! He's here! He's here!
I hope you didn't have
trouble finding my place.
Not at all.
He brought us straight to your home.
He's from London but knows
chandigarh better than us.
I see...so the boy's from London.
No, Karan is from London. My nephew.
My boy's a homegrown lad. Charan.
I see... Charan-Karan.
They have similar names,
like their face.
In fact, you two look
like identical twins.
They are identical twins.
I see... very good.
I don't see sister-in-law.
- And you never will.
Huh?
- It's God's will after all.
Sorry.
Baldev, I can't remember
when I got independence.
Actually,
on the 15th of August, she...
You see,
now I am Sweety's mom and dad.
But she doesn't listen to anyone.
Actually,
there's nothing to hide from you.
She has already rejected
12 marriage proposals.
Yours is the unlucky no. 13.
Sweety dear.
She's really nice.
You think she's nice.
You even liked Binkle.
Do you love Nafisa at all?
Is he feeling okay?
- That's what I am trying to find out?
Lord, have Mercy on us.
She's my sweet,
loveable, the apple of my eye...
Sweety.
Hello.
- Hello, dear.
Bless you, dear.
I am sure your papa must
have told you everything.
He's...
- Yes!
Dear, if you would
like to speak with the boy...
I mean, if there's something
you want to ask... - No.
No, please do.
Let them talk.
It's a yes from my side, papa.
Really?
After all, your choice can't be wrong.
Did you hear? This is unbelievable.
She said yes.
She has never even bought
shampoo of my choice.
And today, she said yes to my choice.
Have some sweets.
congratulations. Congratulations.
This is unbelievable, Baldev.
congratulations to you too.
Congratulations.
I just realized...
how much you love me, brother.
Since my marriage got fixed,
you're more worried than I am.
Yeah... I am really tensed.
You know what...run away.
Run away?
But you were saying
that I shouldn't run away.
Run away now.
- What are you saying?
What else can I say?
Uncle's never going to say yes...
...and, you're never
going to tell him.
There's no other choice.
- No, I won't run away.
You were right yesterday.
Then go...tell uncle about Nafisa.
I will when the time is right.
Tell him on your wedding day.
"Uncle, I like a girl... Nafisa!"
"I love her a lot."
"With your permission..."
"...can we head to her home instead."
Duffer!
Isn't that her? Sweety.
Don't hit me. Let's talk first...
Sweety, listen to me.
Sweety... listen to me.
- Have you lost your mind?
That hurts... Sweety, that hurts.
Sweety, listen to me...
- What are you?
You came over to
my house with your uncle...
...with a marriage proposal
for your brother.
I didn't know that was your house.
I only realized when
I saw the red tractor.
I even tried calling you...
but you don't even answer my call.
I...
- No, please...don't...
Beat him... give him a few
blows on my behalf too, Sweety.
He's so shameless.
Now I get the entire story.
Listen to him first.
Now I know what he's been
doing here for the last six months.
"When men dare, even God helps."
Now you run, son.
Sweety, I think you
should go tell your dad...
My father!
First time in my life
I have listened to him.
He's so happy...like that
smile's stuck to his face.
And you want me to
take that away from him.
Karan, I think you
should do something.
Hey, keep your opinion
to yourself, okay.
Please, help us, Sweety.
- I can't do anything.
Now you must do something,
otherwise...
Otherwise...
Otherwise what?
Charan is also good.
- What?
What are you saying?
You're his sister-in-law.
I'll be your sister-in-law
once I'm married to him.
What rubbish? What are you saying?
Angry young man!
Hey...
Now you must handle this
situation with the same zest.
And until this problem isn't solved...
...marriage is not on the cards.
I am not your girlfriend,
and you're not my boyfriend.
You're in big trouble.
- Sweety!
"I am your king..."
"I brought you a ring..."
"...be my queen today."
"I am gonna propose today."
"Praise you every day."
"can't say how beautiful you are."
"Get lost...don't lock horns in love."
"Bury your feelings in your heart."
"O breeze... sweep me away."
"Come...and steal my heart."
"Write my name...on your heart."
"I'm stuck in the middle...
come closer dear."
"Make me your boyfriend."
"Go woo someone else?
- "Make me your boyfriend."
"Take your eyes off me."
"Trap me in your love.
"Go woo someone else?
- "Make me your boyfriend."
"Take your eyes off me."
"I am yours...you're mine."
"I am yours...you're
mine...that's for sure."
"Your hand in mine...that's for sure."
"Don't stare in my eyes..."
"...but I am sure to
come in your dreams."
"Day dreaming all day..."
"...why are you still stuck on me."
"Better find someone
else to lose your heart."
"O breeze... sweep me away."
"Come...and steal my heart."
"Write my name...
on the card of love."
"I'm stuck in the middle...
come closer dear."
"Make me your boyfriend."
"Go woo someone else?
- "Make me your boyfriend."
"Take your eyes off me."
"Trap me in your love.
"Go woo someone else?
- "Make me your boyfriend."
"Take your eyes off me."
"My eyes always dreamt about you."
"I cooked up new ideas to woo you."
"You're the most beautiful...
I keep hitting on you."
"If you talk to me...
I'll be fine again."
"One more time..."
"Love's sweeter than honey...
taste it my sweetheart."
"Your youth's getting wasted slowly."
"I am your king,
baby, why don't you understand."
"If you say yes...
I'll get the wedding band."
"Get lost...
don't lock horns in love."
"Bury your feelings in your heart."
"O breeze... sweep me away."
"Come...and steal my heart."
"Write my name...
on the card of love."
"I haven't locked eyes
yet... come closer dear."
"Make me your boyfriend."
"Go woo someone else?
- "Make me your boyfriend."
"Take your eyes off me."
"Make me your boyfriend."
"Go woo someone else?
"Take your eyes off me."
"Trap me in your love.
"Go woo someone else?
"Make me your boyfriend."
"Take your eyes off me."
Enjoy your meal.
So Sandhu sir, what is your opinion?
Paramjeet, I haven't...
- Look, brother...
If you don't agree to this alliance...
...then we'll be forced to think
that you haven't forgiven us yet.
Don't embarrass me, sister-in-law.
We always wanted
Binkle to marry Karan.
You brought that Charan instead.
Forget the past...
just say the word...
...when should we call Karan?
- Yeah...
What do you say, Binkle dear?
- Papa, I...
What will Binkle say?
Karan is better.
And, he's also 5 minutes
older than Charan.
So, on which date should we fix it?
Well, Christmas is on the 25th, so...
Is Christmas on the 25th this year?
You get drunk on the 21st-22nd.
How would you know when is Christmas?
As I was saying,
let's set the wedding on the 25th.
It's christmas as well.
Double the celebrations.
- Yes.
Congratulations.
cheers. Cheers.
congratulations. Congratulations.
Who is it?
Brother Baldev.
Answer it.
Hello. Hello.
There's definitely a
network issue in this house.
Hello.
Hello, brother.
- Kartar. Start packing.
charan is getting married.
charan's marriage? So you agreed?
What do you mean?
I mean...you don't like them.
Are you crazy?
They are such great people.
I am really proud of you, brother.
Really proud.
Leave that.
You must get here by 20th-22nd.
The wedding's on the 25th.
25th?
25th is such a lame date, brother.
Fix another date...
like 26th, 27th, 28th.
Kartar, this is about my promise.
I challenged her for the 25th...
...so the wedding will
take place on the 25th.
But it's christmas
in England on the 25th.
The day of the Lord, brother.
Are you planning on dressing up like
Santa Clause and give out sweets?
Brother...
Karan's wedding on the 25th as well.
Karat's wedding is also on the 25th.
- Yes, brother.
But I challenged her for the 25th.
But Sandhu sir has already
fixed 25th for the wedding.
I see... so Karan's
marriage has been fixed...
...with Sandhu's daughter Binkle.
Your mother's doing
this to torment me!
Listen, Kartar,
you have a brother as well.
You're coming here... that's it!
And if you don't show up...
...then our relationship
is over for good, understand!
Sister, I...
- Don't even think about it.
Is Baldev now more
important to you than me?
Poor boy's got only one uncle now.
And even he won't attend the wedding.
You must stay here, end of discussion.
And if you don't... then
that's the end of this relation.
Why did you call Sweety here, charan?
- Don't get mad at me.
You were in the bathroom...
...and Sweety was calling you.
I just picked up her
call and gave her an update.
She's a smart girl, she will help us.
She won't help us...
she'll beat me to a pulp.
Everyone's conspiring against me.
The Sandhus threw us out,
uncle gave challenge...
...and mom-dad fixed my wedding.
And all this because of you.
If only you had said yes for Binkle...
- And what about Nafisa.
Make her my sister.
Don't you have a better example?
You could've told me about Nafisa.
Duffer. - You didn't tell me
about Sweety, either.
You look so restless.
Here's your chain.
And anyway...you can't open
a chain of Purani Haveli anymore.
Wait... sorry, man.
Forget it, don't worry.
What else should I do?
- Take advice?
From who?
- Kartar uncle.
Kartar uncle?
He'll fix everything.
Like he fixed things for you.
He made everyone believe
you're a drug addict.
But he solved my problem.
God, I am in a mess.
- He's a genius.
That man can cook
up an idea from anything.
Any other option?
My life's become hell.
Sister's pulling my legs
while brother's pulling my hair.
They are making new relations...
...and ending their old ties with me.
What to do, Jolly. What should I do?
First finish your drink, dude.
- That's right.
Karan's calling on Skype.
He will definitely help me.
- Of course, he will.
Today's youth, Jolly.
Smart and intelligent.
Karan-Charan...what's up my boys?
Karan uncle, we're in big trouble.
Please help us.
Uncle...please come up
with an idea... find a solution.
Just get my wedding canceled.
You fool...I came up
with an idea for charan...
...and our entire family broke up.
If I come up with another idea...
...then the Sandhus will sc*** me.
Binkle is his daughter...
...not a tennis ball, which you can toss
over to first charan and then Karan.
charan had a reason, Nafisa.
What is your reason? Najma?
Sweety...please...
- I was only joking.
Kartar uncle is on Skype...
- He felt offended.
Karan...
- I'll close this matter once and for all.
Charan.
- Just meet my uncle Kartar.
Call Karan, he felt bad.
Hello.
- Hello.
Uncle, she's...
- I got it.
Greetings, dear.
Kartar uncle, I am not who you think.
Huh?
I mean I am not Nafisa, I am Supreet.
Sweety.
- Sweety?
My girlfriend?
- No... charan's future wife.
Did Nafisa go on a pilgrimage?
What can I say, uncle Kartar?
He hasn't told uncle
Baldev about Nafisa yet.
And of all the people in Chandigarh...
...uncle had to choose
her for Charan, Sweety.
Sweety is hard to miss.
curses...
what kind of a family is this?
No one has any kind of
communication with anyone.
Their families are
fixing their wedding...
...and these guys have girlfriends.
While we're getting tensed.
Are you tensed?
- Of course.
What is this?
- Whiskey?
Brother Baldev.
What is this?
- Definitely not soda.
correct answer.
Sister Jeeto.
And this is me... Ice.
Whiskey wants the ice in his glass...
...and soda wants
the ice in his glass.
How can I be in two
places at the same time?
Jolly...what an idea.
- Me?
Of course...
I know what you want to say.
If we mix whiskey with soda...
...then the ice can
be with both of them.
Isn't it?
- See... genius.
Like I said...he can come
up with an idea anywhere.
He's so humble too.
It's his idea but giving
the credit to Jolly.
He's not humble, he's a big jumble.
He's only giving
credit to Jolly because...
...if things go sideways tomorrow,
he can blame Jolly for it.
I didn't say a word,
and you understood the idea.
Dude, that's my quality.
And when I keep telling
you to increase my salary...
...don't you understand that?
There are something's
I don't understand.
Problem solved... no more worrying.
Call brother Baldev.
Uncle Baldev is at my home,
drinking with papa.
Kartar, did you book a ticket.
Why did you challenge her...
...if you wanted to secretly
get Charan married?
What rubbish?
Why will it be a secret wedding?
charan's going to have
a grand wedding here.
But who's going to see it there?
Neither sister Jeeto,
nor brother-in-law, nor Sandhu sir.
So?
- So what?
Opt for a destination wedding instead,
in London.
London?
Where did you get humiliated?
- In London.
Where were you called a hawker?
So where should you
show your grandeur?
London?
- So where should the wedding be?
But...
- In London.
Gill Sir is right there...
ask him.
How do you know Gill sir's right here?
Brother...who else would
you be sitting with?
Don't think too much, brother.
You must show sister Jeeto...
...that an honorable man
never forgets his humiliation.
But in a foreign country...
- Foreign.
With the grace of God...
you have a home...
...your Kartar...
your Jolly...your Mini Punjab.
Bring everyone along.
Bring entire Punjab.
It's your London.
- Yeah...
But so many people...
so much work.
London will be very expensive.
It will be expensive,
but people will talk too.
You were insulted in London...
...so, the wedding should
take place there too.
Don't worry... with the grace of God,
I'm blessed with quite a lot.
But the Sandhus have everything.
Doesn't matter...
we'll deal with it.
I've 400 tractors,
when will they come in handy?
I've only one daughter.
Don't worry...we'll manage.
So Kartar, it's final.
Destination Wedding, in London.
That's more like it.
Goodbye.
Well...my problem is solved.
What about our problem?
You fools...what does the
air-hostess tell us in the flight?
Wear your oxygen mask
before helping others.
If I'm out of breath myself...
...who's going to help
you wear the oxygen mask?
When are you going to help
us wear the mask? After we're dead?
If we come over to London for
the wedding, then she will kill me.
And Nafisa will strangle me.
And you'll lose...
- Both your nephews.
Oh man...I thought
my problem was large.
But your problem is larger than life.
We'll see what to do.
Just come to London.
The flight has landed,
but Karan hasn't come out yet.
Isn't this unbelievable, sister?
- It's landed.
The entire family
is here to welcome Karan.
But only I am here to welcome the
entire family coming from Punjab.
That's what I am asking you?
Why is Baldev getting
charan married in London?
Destination Wedding, sister!
You know, like the snooty white people.
It was his idea.
Stupid!
They are here.
- Look...my son has arrived.
Karan!
Where's Kartar?
I don't see anyone.
Hi, my boy...
Your joys will be
pretty short-lived...
...if you don't sort out all this son.
Mum...
Looking good, uncle Kartar.
Fresh... Fit!
Hi!
Kartar. Give me a hug.
- Welcome to London, brother.
Greetings.
How are you, Binkle?
- Manni, how are you?
Bro, how are you?
- Yeah, let's go.
come on....
- come on.
Uncle Kartar.
Is charan getting married to her?
You have a great memory, mom.
Yes-Yes... Yes!
Oh, my...
Sweety, greet your uncle too.
Greetings.
- Greetings.
She is characterless.
Characterless?
- Hmmmm
She has a boyfriend too.
Poor Charan is trapped.
Sister Jeeto...
Can I go meet her?
- Yes...
Come, let's go meet your aunt.
- Go on...
come, Sweety.
- Yes...
Mr. Gill,
at least someone stay with me.
Am I going to stay alone?
I get it...
Is it them we're not speaking with?
Yes.
- Indeed... Indeed, brother.
Kuldeep. All okay?
Greetings.
- Bless you, son.
And she's your new
daughter-in-law... Sweety.
Hello.
Let's go now?
Are you planning
on settling down here?
Let's go.
Okay...okay.
come, dear.
Bye.
- Bye, see you later.
- We were just talking.
Are you still angry, aunty?
Aunty?
Aunty, who?
- You?
I'm an old lady.
- No-no-no...
No-no-no?
Oh yes, little baby.
Oh my...baby, did you fall down?
She even remembers the dialogue.
Yeah... dad wanted to come,
but he was busy.
Really, man, he as busy.
It was my mistake.
What is Sweety doing there?
Call her.
Charan!
- charan!
Yeah... Yes...
- Where are you lost?
Jet lag.
Lord...
Brother's saying call Sweety here.
Call her.
Sweety.
Sweety!
Sweety, dear.
Everyone makes mistakes.
- Sweety, come on, let's go.
It was just a mistake.
- Sweety...
They are calling you, please go.
I heard it.
What an ill-mannered girl.
It's a really grand hotel.
The rooms are even better.
And we've booked
a penthouse for Sweety
I see...
Very good...
You see, we must show our enemies...
...that Mr.
Gill is not some ordinary guy.
Absolutely right.
- Any problem, Mr. Gill?
Not at all. I must book tickets for
my relatives coming from Punjab.
Don't worry...I'll get
it done on Make My Trip.
I see...
- Please give me your card?
The card is the real problem.
We'll have to get new ones made
because of this destination wedding.
Papa, he's asking for your credit card.
- Credit card?
I need to pay them as well.
- Oh...I see.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
It's too grand even for my taste.
- Jolly, don't just stand there.
Take everyone inside.
Shall we?
- Let's go. Come on...
Come, brother.
come, my Lad,
Kartar Villa welcomes you.
Wow!
"I am not good. No one is bad."
"Prays Nanak, He alone saves us!"
Bro...both the parties
are giving pretty angry looks.
Jolly, take anything you get
in the House of Lord as His blessings.
"No one is bad."
25th... 25th...
The hall's been already
booked for the 25th.
Please do something.
I can give you a booking
for 24th or the 26th.
24th...
- What are you saying?
How can the 25th be booked?
I already spoke with the priest.
- Yeah...
Words just don't cut it, Mr. Gill.
I think we should go
and book a music band as well.
The deal's sealed only
when you have a receipt.
Kartar, tell him...
...to book a different Gurdwara.
Brother, get your booking
done in a different Gurdwara.
Reason?
Reason? We're older...
he's younger to us.
Sister is older...than you.
No one's big or small
in the Lord's House.
But one must always
respect their elders.
Look Baldev...
Just a minute, mister...
Madam...
Please don't break the
sanctity of the Gurdwara.
With your permission...
...we can have both the weddings
on the same day, on the 25th.
11 o'clock is fine.
What an incredible idea?
Same date...same place...
and the same family.
That solves the problem.
You'll get us in trouble, uncle.
Is that fine?
You and your ideas?
Okay...
Okay?
It's all settled now...thank you.
- Goodbye.
Swee...
I'll have to cajole her again.
It was the same date...
Now, uncle Kartar has fixed
the same place and time.
And we're depending on him?
I don't think your so called 'talented,
Kartar uncle can do anything.
Now, he can... he can...
You can, can't you?
Uncle, only you can
save their love now.
Why don't you talk to aunt now?
Yes.
- Baby dear...
...sister Jeeto severed
ties with her own brother...
...because of Sandhu sir.
With his father.
If I tell her about
Karan and Sweety...
Then she will shoot Sweety.
Bang...
Loose character...
Uncle, why don't you talk to dad?
Then your secret
will be out of the bag.
Then Nafisa will get
involved... Akbar, Mughlai...
Swords will be drawn...
there will be bloodshed.
You know what...
shoot these old folks.
Let's keep this between us.
The youth.
Youth?
- Then think of something.
Think what?
I got an idea.
come, boys and girls, come...
Why is he taking us
to the vegetable market now?
Come on...
- Hurry up.
What is this?
Radish? - It's a radish...
but, not an ordinary one.
Because...this is Binkle.
Binkle.
And this one?
- Potatoes.
This is you.
And this is sweet potatoes...
which is you.
My favorite vegetable...
what is this?
Is that me?
No... this is a cauliflower.
Oh...
The potato will try
to convince radish...
...to tell her dad she doesn't
want to marry sweet potato.
Reason... because sweet-potato
is seeing cauliflower.
Then the cauliflower
will tell her dear watermelon...
I mean, she will tell Gill sir...
...that I don't want to marry potato.
Reason... because the
potato is a drug addict.
Sweet potato was already free...
Now cauliflower will be free too.
They will get busy
with each other. Simple.
Uncle...mind-blowing idea.
And I am sure you've also thought...
...where I will meet radish...
I mean Binkle.
Of course my boy, of course.
After all, I am a... Punjabi!
Wow!
- That's the one.
Hey look, it's beautiful.
- Look at that.
Isn't it nice?
And look at this one.
- Yes...
What do you say?
Binkle, have a look.
What do you say to that one?
- It's really nice.
Yeah.
May be...
Anyway, let's go have a look...
- What about that?
Let's go inside...
- I... I'll be back from the washroom.
It's that way.
Why did you bring me here?
- Why?
This is where I had that
argument with your... mother.
I've some bitter
memories with this mall.
Forget it, Sweety.
I had to talk to you.
Tell me...
- No...not here.
Let's go up...to the coffee shop?
- Sure.
Are you crazy?
Are you blind?
Have patience.
Hello.
- Hello.
I'll be right back.
I am terribly sorry for...everything
that happened at your home that day.
Even I am sorry.
Manpreet actually said too much.
I see... so that's why
I get this 'Coffee with charan'.
No, actually...
I wanted to show you this.
Papa!
Is this what you wanted to show me?
- No...no...
Run! Run! Run! Run!
Where is Binkle?
Call her.
- That way! That way.
I don't know where she is.
That way! come on.
Kartar, this looks like the
most expensive section of the mall.
Yeah...but there's a sale everywhere.
That shop looks perfect,
give me your card.
Yeah.
Stupid!
- Sweety...
You left me alone.
Sorry...
- What?
Come on...
- What Sweety?
This is what I wanted to show you.
Karan, your future husband,
and Sweety, my future wife...
It's all a mess, Binkle.
Please, say no to this wedding.
Maybe something's wrong with me.
Don't say that.
You're really very nice.
No... I mean,
you'll get many more proposals.
After getting rejected twice...
from the same family?
I know you'll handle...
If Karan doesn't want to get married,
let him say no.
I wish we could say no...
...then things wouldn't
have been the way they are.
But charan, it's their problem...
...why are we getting involved?
Sweety...
Now I've put my faith in God's hand.
Whatever the Lord decides for me...
...will be good enough for me.
He's the One who
makes matches in Heaven.
I am sure...
He's chosen someone for me too.
Anyway...
Charan, I can't explain it, but...
...I thought maybe you came
here to say something else.
"We were holding hands but..."
"...our destinies were far away."
"Was it our fate that separated us..."
"...or is this the fate of love?
"I haven't lost you
yet... nor are you with me."
"So why do I still miss you?"
"Without you...
it's even hard to breathe."
"Because...I can't stop
thinking about you."
"Your memories keep tormenting me."
"Because...I can't stop
thinking about you."
"Your memories keep tormenting me."
"You're right in front of me..."
"...yet we're miles apart."
"The heart has lots to say..."
"....but unfortunately
my lips are sealed."
"Whether you were
akin or a stranger..."
"...the heart couldn't discriminate."
"Why does my heart
keep skipping a beat."
"Without you...
it's even hard to breathe."
"Because...I can't stop
thinking about you."
"Your memories keep tormenting me."
"Because...I can't stop
thinking about you."
"Your memories keep tormenting me."
Are your radish,
carrots, and potatoes cooked yet?
carrots?
There was no carrot in the plan ever!
Uncle...Charan claims you're a genius.
That I am.
So think of a new idea, please.
I got it...
This is Binkle...and
she's going to melt.
This isn't Binkle...and
never should be!
Oh, God...fine...
this is Binkle.
Now! - What now?
Let's target her.
- Why?
This is our problem... why are
you dragging that poor soul in this?
Poor? She's Sandhu sir's daughter.
Uncle...you got my wedding
canceled with her...
...and now, we're canceling
Karan's wedding with her too.
Have you ever wondered
what she's going through?
Are you her uncle? Huh, Charan.
Do you have a better idea?
Speak up...
Now I've put my faith in God's hand.
Whatever the Lord decides
for me...will be good enough for me.
He's the One who makes
matches in Heaven.
So be it.
If he's chosen Sweety for me,
then I am fine.
What?
What's he saying, Karan?
- I want to know that too.
Have you lost your mind?
What are you driveling?
I am just saying that
one must fight his own battle.
If Sweety and you
really love each other...
...then fight your own battle.
He took my ice-cream.
Hello, sister?
Kartar.
Sister...at the crack of dawn?
Wedding card.
The first card goes to the uncle.
Uncle? I see...
And this too... sweets,
gold chain, diamond ring...
...suit piece and cash too.
- 11,000 Pounds.
11,000 Pounds?
But sister...these gifts
are given on the wedding day.
Yes... this is just
the invitation gift.
From Sandhu sir.
Only for our close relatives.
Just wait and watch...
...all the gifts that Sandhu
sir will give on the wedding day.
Sandhu sir is a really great guy.
He's so wealthy...but doesn't
have an ounce of arrogance.
Otherwise, people these days...
...forget their place after
acquiring little wealth.
Relationships...
manners, all of it.
Sister... greetings.
- Bless you.
Greetings.
Kuldeep, this is your invitation card.
Be there...
- You don't have to say it twice.
We're family after all.
But you must come first...
You see...Charan's engagement
is before Karan's.
Shall we?
- Yes.
At least have a cup of tea,
brother-in-law.
Jolly...
- Yes, bro...
No, let it be.
Otherwise,
he'll get another one of his ideas.
And anyway...we've to
go invite certain people...
...we don't want to.
What to do...
that's courtesy after all.
We must go.
We'll make it clear...
come only if you're really
happy...otherwise stay at home.
And stop asking us for tea...
Instead, you should be asking
whether you can lend a hand.
You're my brother after all.
come home and help me through.
You see sister, I am divided myself.
Let's go.
- Yes, come.
Come, sister.
"My cute charan...
My naive Charan..."
"My love's stuck in a cyclone..."
"...take it across."
"Take it across now."
- Sorry, are you okay?
Everyone must fight their own battle.
But how can a brother
fight with his own brother?
But my brother has this habit...of
inviting trouble for himself.
Look...here comes the trouble.
Hi, Nafisa.
Where is charan?
How about some coffee?
I'm thirsty for his blood!
Well...that's only possible
at his engagement.
Come on.
"O Nafisa.. fiery..."
"The black thread gets
stuck in the latch."
"Fights with the sister-in-law,
little brother-in-law is a brat."
"The black thread gets
stuck in the latch."
"It's an auspicious night.
With henna clad hands..."
"You look beautiful tonight."
"Music plays loud..."
- Card uncle.
"It's time to dance and shout."
Sorry, Gill uncle, card.
For making payment?
- Yes.
"Twelve years..."
"He'd gone out for 12 years."
"He brought back powder."
"When you dance,
my heart beats louder!"
Darling, shall we dance?
- Dance?
"Maternal uncle dances with wife."
"Paternal aunt dances with her husband."
Sister Jeeto's here.
- "Grandma dances with grandpa."
"Holding a glass in the hand."
Listen, sister Jeeto's here.
But not brother-in-law.
At least our sister's here.
- "Twelve years..."
"He'd gone out for 12 years."
"He brought back stuff."
"It will be fun when rocking the
dance floor with uncle."
coming, Gill sir.
coming.
Hello.
- Hi...
I thought I should congratulate you.
Congrats for what...
You know this is just a charade.
"It's an auspicious night.
With henna clad hands..."
"You look beautiful tonight."
"Music plays loud."
"It's time to dance and shout."
"This is a joyous occasion..."
"We've all be been
so eagerly waiting for."
"He'd gone out for 12 years."
"He brought back a Harley."
"It will be fun when rocking the
dance floor is the whole family."
Everyone has to fight
their own battle, don't they?
Go fight...
"Twelve years..."
Nafisa.
Nafisa?
Is she Qureshi?
Nafisa Qureshi. Karan's friend.
She's from Punjab...
and staying with us.
I see...
come, sister...
and bless the children.
Nafisa Qureshi.
come.
You're looking so handsome, son.
You fool...you just
sc*** your own brother.
Uncle...you know
how much I love music.
I can see that my boy.
I can see that.
Give the engagement gift.
Easy, tiger, easy.
My poor boy.
Congratulations.
Thanks for coming, aunty...
- Thank you.
May God save you...
Come, let's take a picture together.
Come on.
Photo.
Unbelievable Charan,
I never imagined that...
...I'll be a guest in your engagement.
"He'd gone out for 12 years."
"He brought back a Harley."
Smile, please. - "It will be fun when
rocking the dance floor is the whole family."
"It will be fun when rocking the
dance floor is the whole family."
Kuldeep.
- Yes.
Hello. - Greetings.
"I'll talk to my aunt,
introduce you to my mother."
"Everything will be fine."
"Is this what you call fine?"
"Didn't you feel ashamed?"
You didn't even think about me...
...before going ahead and
doing something like this.
Thanks to Karan for
informing me of time.
Otherwise, you would've gone
ahead with the wedding as well.
It's impossible to understand.
Getting engaged to
Sweety was just a plan...
I didn't make any plans this time.
I swear on the queen.
What was your plan?
- Well, I thought...
...if I act casual, then these two
will feel the pressure and run away.
And that would solve the problem.
That would've solved your problem,
not ours.
Loser!
- You're not the winner too.
You haven't told your parents either.
Oh hello...
At least he didn't get
engaged to his sister-in-law.
Please ladies, quiet.
If you guys fight amongst yourselves
then, you'll definitely lose.
Have team spirit.
You see in situations like these...
What is this?
- Uncle, why don't you just tell us?
But, I am...
These are shoes...
you're a Singh.
Wear these...
and run like Milkha Singh.
Run away?
- Run...
You'll be happy...and even
your families will calm down.
Your parents will curse you...
...saying that you were
a bunch of selfish fools.
They humiliated their
families and ran away.
They will cry and wail
for few days... that's all.
Simple.
Look, guys,
you're out of time and options.
If you don't run...then Karan
will get engaged to Binkle.
charan?
Yeah... Yes...
Are you ready, my boy?
Yes... Ready!
Are you sure?
- Sure.
Good...
You must leave early
morning...at 10'.25 sharp!
10'.25? What's the plan?
There's no plan.
I wake up at 10 am...
And takes me around
20-25 minutes to get ready.
At least I can see you guys run away.
Nafisa... keep my stuff
in your bag as well.
Why?
Don't you have your own bag?
If I take my bag,
what am I going to tell mom and dad?
"Bye, mom...Bye dad,
I am running away."
"Take care."
Point.
Kartar uncle's getting to everyone.
Thank you so much,
Aunty, for everything.
No need to thank me.
You must attend the wedding.
- Definitely.
She's here for the wedding...
of course, she will come.
And Selfridges...
That's the place to go.
- Sandhu sir?
Sandhu sir?
- Sandhu sir...
Why are they here?
- Sandhu sir.
I had to meet Karan.
Hello, Uncle.
Uncle!
Dad, I think they are going somewhere.
Uncle, this is Nafisa.
- Hi.
Manpreet, she's Nafisa.
From India.
She's my friend.
Uncle, get up!
What happened?
- Look...
What happened my lad.
- Take a look.
Good Lord, who invited Sandhu Sir?
Is he and Manpreet
eloping with you guys too?
They are here on their own.
We're here for Karan.
- Me? Where?
For the wedding suit, son.
- Oh no, Uncle...I've plenty of them.
Son... it's a tradition.
The father-in-law takes
his son-in-law personally...
...to buy the wedding suit.
I'm tattered here...
and she's worried about the suit.
Is everything alright, son?
Yes, uncle. It's great.
You know what uncle,
our choices are quite similar.
So why don't you get one for me?
I am a bit busy today.
- Busy with what?
You don't work, bro...
Actually...I had to take Nafisa for
sight-seeing around Central London.
So...
- Yeah!
I was thinking that he can take
me shopping around central London...
...and help me with
the hotel check-in too.
We have a big house out there, dear.
Doesn't look nice if you
check-in into a hotel.
Oh, no uncle...
- Doesn't look nice. Ask them.
You're right, dad.
She will stay with me.
Huh?
I mean she will stay with us.
And anyway, I am free...
...I'll show her
around Central London.
Dad, I'll pick her up.
Excuse me.
Great then.
- Okay.
come, Karan. Let's go.
- Go on.
You too, dear.
- Go, dear.
Oh, God! What now?
You were supposed to get up at 10 am.
I did set an alarm,
but why didn't it ring?
Oh, it's not working.
How could you set an alarm
in a watch that's not working?
The watch is fine...
but the alarm's turned off.
Jolly.
- Coming.
Yes, bro...
Get it fixed?
- Okay.
Careful, you fool...
that one's fine.
Everything's fine...
except for my time.
Stupid...
Come here!
Bravo...
I...
And you...
Who stares at a girl like this?
Funny... you're too funny.
What's wrong, charan?
Nafisa isn't answering my calls!
What?
Did Nafisa come here to elope
with charan, or for sight-seeing?
Relax, Sweety.
- Relax!
You're going to get
engaged to Binkle...
...and you want me
to relax and rejoice.
Even you got engaged to Charan.
Doesn't matter...
You only have to pour the
drink into the glass, not drink it.
I don't care if Nafisa
shows up or not...
...but we are eloping, and that's it.
Stand up!
- Let them finish...
I mean...I can't leave Charan alone.
He's such a duffer...
I mean, he's not smart like me.
So when are we going to run away?
After your engagement?
What's your problem in
eloping after the engagement?
Silly, girl...
Fine...go wear it...
Sandhu's wedding suit,
Binkle's ring...
Sweety, don't worry...
We're already married.
You're my wife.
You scold me, curse me, abuse me...
beat me so lovingly.
That's what wives do,
not girlfriends.
"Sweety...Sweety...
I want your love."
Crazy boy...
Who is it?
It's Binkle... not Nafisa.
Binkle?
Binkle's calling him?
Hi, Binkle. How are you?
- How could I be...
...when I don't know what's
going to happen at my wedding.
Binkle...
- Yes, papa.
We're leaving.
Get ready and come with your aunty.
Okay, papa.
- Bye, dear.
Is Karan coming?
- Yes,...he has to.
I mean...he is coming.
But Binkle...
Karan and Sweety are planning
to run away after the engagement.
Good...
...at least someone's
getting their love.
But...I'm feeling really bad for you.
And what hurts me is that
you're hiding something from me.
What is it? Tell me...
can we meet...
Sister-in-law, hurry up.
Or I'll start dancing right here.
- Coming.
I...wish you would come along too.
Why?
Did brother-in-law
attend Charan's wedding?
He didn't...
He sent his wife and children.
So I am sending my
wife and children too.
Go on.
Listen...
Yes?
Give my love to Karan.
Charan!
Are you okay?
- Yeah...
Hi...
- Hi.
You're looking really nice.
Thank you.
If you don't mind,
can I ask you a question?
Please do...
How long have you been taking drugs?
Binkle, I swear to God...
...I've never even touched
drugs in my whole life.
Then, how did you fall down that day?
Actually...back then,
I didn't want to get in this relation.
Because of my girlfriend Nafisa.
The so-called 'drugs'
was uncle's idea...
...so that you guys reject me.
But when I saw you...
Remember,
we were standing right here...
...when I got a text on my mobile.
It was from Uncle.
I sent you out to get water...
...because,
I wanted to call uncle and stop him...
And tell him that I...
like...Binkle...
But I wasn't getting
any network, and...
...I was trying to call uncle.
I was trying to call him and wasn't
getting any signal on my phone...
I tried getting some network...
Then, I was finally started
getting some network, when...
Watch it. You'll fall down.
There was no one to stop me that day,
and I fell.
And it things turned south after that.
After that,
when I saw you at the airport...
And then at the mall...
The truth is Binkle, I don't
love Nafisa...in fact, I love you.
The other day,
when you bowed before the Lord...
...I thought that Lord's telling me...
"Binkle...I've chosen
a suitor for you."
I love you, Charan.
I love you.
Sandhu sir,
the arrangements are really amazing.
Paramjeet's done everything...
How are you?
- Thank you.
Hurry up.
Father-in-law. Sandhu sir...
I mean Sandhu uncle.
Goggle...theme...
Kartar uncle.
Thank you.
"I'm in love with your eyes..."
"...take your lovely goggles off."
"You're so beautiful...like the moon."
"Shining bright...are
your up-to-date jewels."
"You're so beautiful...like the moon."
"Shining bright...are
your up-to-date jewels."
"You chase me for no reason..."
"...keep raising the matter of love."
"Don't think too much, sweetheart..."
"...sway to the beat with me."
"When you dance wearing goggles..."
"...boys can't take their eyes off."
"...boys can't..."
"Beloved...my attitude's
sweeter than honey."
"If I take my goggles off..."
"...there's chaos around."
"Baby, your sway to
the beat is all wrong..."
"...but when you repeat,
it makes my heart skip a beat."
"Don't try to feel..."
"Don't let your heart loose..."
"Don't think too much, sweetheart..."
"...sway to the beat with me."
"When you dance wearing goggles..."
"...boys can't take their eyes off."
"...boys can't..."
"I don't need to praise you..."
"...because,
you have an average face."
"But I must say..."
"...your grace is mind-blowing."
"Why are you jealous of my beauty..."
"...my beauty is what gets you high."
"I'll read your eyes..."
"...make your heart beat faster."
"Don't think too much, sweetheart..."
"...sway to the beat with me."
"When I dance wearing goggles..."
"...boys can't..."
"...boys can't take their eyes off."
"When you dance wearing goggles..."
"...boys can't..."
"...boys can't take their eyes off."
"When you dance wearing goggles..."
"...boys can't...take their eyes off."
Who could that be?
What's the matter, Kartar?
You've been dancing
a lot wearing goggles?
Brother, you?
I had to...because of your stupidity.
You idiot...what are you doing?
Letting the children elope.
And what about my reputation?
Your reputation?
Why?
Don't dead guys get humiliated?
Brother, I am only doing this
for the happiness of our children.
Which children are you talking about?
Children these days...
...think it's cool
to hurt their parents.
Cool.
Even you're looking cool, brother.
No change at all.
You look like my younger brother.
cardio?
- Curse you.
Once you're dead...you stop aging.
You'll find out later.
- Don't say that, brother.
I don't want to know.
- But you must know one thing.
Jeeto and Baldev raised
my children as their own.
They never treated them as an orphan.
If these children hurt them...
...then, I swear to God,
I'll never forgive you Kartar.
The tractor's here too.
So is the mannequin.
Good morning.
It's so cold outside.
What's wrong?
Nothing, sister.
- Bless you.
What brings you to the
farm at this early hour?
Yes, I came here for a horseshoe.
I'll put it on my door.
God save me from anymore evil-eye...
I don't want any more mess-ups.
Give it.
This is the first time
Your 'Ideas-man' did a job right.
Get lost.
Sister...I have a request.
Please cancel this wedding.
Have you been drinking in the morning?
I'll make coffee for
you... pass me the sugar.
Karan and Sweety...
- Sweety?
What did that
'loose-character' do now?
Forget Sweety.
charan and Nafisa love each other.
What are you driveling?
- I swear, sister.
How did you know?
- I always knew.
So why didn't you say something?
You know brother's temper.
charan is my boy.
I won't let his life get ruined.
Fine... I'll do something.
Hurry up.
- Let's go.
Kul, tell her Kartar isn't at home.
I'm here to see you.
We must talk...
it's about Charan.
I...don't love Nafisa anymore.
What?
- What?
I... Sweety..
What Sweety?
Karan, I... - Why don't you
clearly say that you love Sweety?
Are you crazy?
I'm in love with Binkle.
My Fiance.
- Fiance?
I mean...we did get engaged?
- Yes, even I got engaged to him.
Should I call him my fianc?
You two finish fighting first,
then we'll talk. - Shut up.
Fine, tell me.
If we're running away,
I'm running away with Binkle.
Outstanding...end of all troubles.
Your fiance with me,
and my fiance with you.
Simple.
It's not that simple.
How am I going to tell Nafisa?
It will be really harsh on her.
She will be heartbroken.
Wow Nafisa,
you're going to live a thousand years.
Charan was just talking about you.
Nafisa, actually...
charan...I don't think
we're made for each other.
What?
After coming here, I realized...
...that Manpreet is my true love, not you.
- What?
Manpreet?
How can Manpreet be your true love?
You didn't think about me?
About my feelings?
- Listen...
No... you broke my heart...
You broke my heart...
You can't do this to me.
No!
Mad! He's completely mad.
How can you be so stupid...
Just a minute ago, you and Nafisa...
Forget what I was saying
and listen to what she is saying.
What are you saying?
How can you do this to me?
Everything under control.
I fixed everything.
What did you do now?
No need to elope now...
I've told sister Jeeto everything.
That Charan and Nafisa
love each other.
And she must have told
brother Baldev by now.
Father...
Father knows...
What do I do?
Suicide!
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
- Have you lost your mind?
What's wrong with him?
Is he actually doing drugs now?
Charan!
Uncle...
Sit.
This is brother Charan,
this is Nafisa.
This...
- Karan.
No, Manpreet.
And this is Binkle.
So now...it's charan and Binkle...
...Nafisa and Manpreet!
He's here...
Come, Kartar...
- come...
You guys called me.
- Yes.
Tell him...
- What?
That Charan loves Nafisa.
Isn't that what you said?
Yes, sister, I did.
My charan wants to marry Nafisa.
No, not at all.
Are you satisfied now?
- What are you saying?
Why are you lying?
Sister...my information was wrong.
- What?
Then give us the right information.
Tell her...that Nafisa
is Karan's girlfriend.
What's this new twist now?
Nafisa is Karan's girlfriend?
Not yet...
but let me confirm first.
But one thing's confirmed, brother.
Charan wants to marry Binkle.
- I see...
Why don't you also say...
that Karan wants to marry Sweety?
How did you know?
Binkle is my would-be daughter-in-law.
That hurts, brother.
- Sweety is my would-be daughter-in-law.
Kids, you know...
they can't make up their mind.
This is too much...
All that alcohol has
messed up your brain.
You never did understand
what marriage is all about...
...and, you never will.
We're looking forward
to two wedding...
...and he's creating
rifts between families.
Sister...
- That's the limit.
Listen to me...
- I don't want to hear anything.
Honestly, brother...
you can ask the kids.
Let it be...there's no need.
Nonsense...
- Brother, I am telling the truth.
Brother... - All that alcohol
has messed up your mind.
Listen to me, sister-in-law.
We've been through a lot already.
All these years I've been sending
you pickles, jams, and snacks.
And this is how you repay me.
Dear.
- Sister-in-law.
Someone believe me.
Hi.
I am scared to think that...
...after you guys run away,
father might just get me married.
What are you doing here?
I brought her here.
- I saw that...
That's why I followed you guys.
What are you doing here?
Binkle and I love each other.
Since when?
Because I dumped you this morning...
...and if you're already
in love with her, then...
...isn't that too soon?
And, if this has been
going on for a while now...
Manpreet hit him!
Hit him!
What is that?
I don't know... I don't
know any judo or karate.
I don't...
- I don't either.
can't guys fight even
if they don't know judo?
Are you running away too?
Why will they run, uncle?
We're running away.
No one's going anywhere now.
- Why?
Did you come up with a new idea now?
I don't need any more ideas.
Let things proceed the way they are.
Take whatever you are getting.
Take what? Radish?
Potato... no, sweet-potato.
Radish, carrot...
Take what?
Father had 4000 tractors.
Now he's got only 2800.
From Gill uncle,
he's turned into 'card uncle.'
The wedding is tomorrow.
What else can we do
other than running away?
You couldn't do anything, and now...
Karan, tell her about
all that I did...
Will you please tell me what you did?
What did you do?
Whose idea was it to target Binkle?
So what?
This duffer fell in
love with her instead.
And what about running away?
Milkha Singh?
10'.25?
If only we had run away on time...
...we wouldn't have
ran into Sandhu sir.
And what about my idea of having
both the wedding at the same place?
So that you can attend
both the weddings.
And this... this is
no way to handover kids.
If only you had done
things properly that day...
...then, we wouldn't
be in this trouble, uncle.
I would've been in Punjab,
he would've been in London.
He would be getting
married to Binkle...
...and I would be getting
married to Sweety.
And our love...
- What love?
The current generation
treats love more like a game.
It's either on that side...or on this.
Hello, Mr. Kartar Singh Bajwa.
Karan and I have been on the
same side for the past two years.
You should be taunting him.
That duffer. - That one.
- How is it my fault now?
Love cannot be planned.
It just happened...
I fell in love...with Binkle.
Excuse me, huh...
You two started this game, remember?
Yeah, so I only did a good thing.
Otherwise,...you wouldn't
be with Binkle today.
What kind of a brother is he?
Are you going to take
credit for that too?
Karan, you can only hatch schemes.
You can fool people, lie to them.
And open 'chains'!
You're selfish. Selfish.
And why do you keep
calling me a duffer?
Could you muster the courage
to tell aunty about Sweety?
coward.
Bravo, Charan.
You really showed
him the mirror today.
Bravo.
Uncle...what is this?
This is Binkle, my boy.
No... this is a phone,
and that's what it should be.
You turn living people into phones,
vegetables or shoes.
And your so-called
'Bernard Shaw' ideas...
Anyone who believes
in it...cannot be saved.
"Charan my boy, 'I have an idea."
"High... drugs..."
"We'll put a doubt in their mind."
Father's doubts have
turned into reality.
You know... he keeps
spying on me all day.
He keeps tasting powder...
talcum powder.
And my mom...
Just don't ask.
She's folded her hands
in front of God so many times...
...that she can't fold them
anymore even to greet someone!
Yes, Kartar uncle.
Because of you,
this decent boy became a druggy...
...and his father, into a hawker.
Wow, Kartar uncle, fantastic.
I know your nephews.
But now I know you pretty well too.
Your family's filled with lunatics.
Thank God I am saved.
I am going back.
Manpreet, let me know whenever
you want to get married.
What are we waiting for?
We should leave too.
Manpreet, will you take Binkle home...
...or should I call Sandhu sir?
And I've brother Baldev and
sister Jeeto's number on speed-dial.
No one's going anywhere.
Everyone's going home.
What's wrong with you uncle?
I finally see the reality...
thanks to a dream.
If your love is true,
then He will help you?
He who doesn't let sleeping
birds fall from trees...
...can never leave
his devotees stranded.
come on...let's go home.
Girls, you have to dance...
You'll be the star of the event.
- Of course...
Mom, my necklace.
- Must be somewhere around here.
Kul.
- Yes.
Where's charan?
He's over at sister Jeeto's home...
...to tie Karan's turban.
Found it.
- I see... Okay.
Karan...look at our turbans.
- It's fine.
Look at it again... look closely.
Can anyone say who's
Karan and who's Charan?
Let's exchange our clothes.
You can marry Sweety
and I'll marry Binkle.
charan, why didn't
I think of this idea?
You never wore a turban before this.
You just proved that we're
not cousins, but brothers.
Come on, take off your suit.
I'll give Sweety this good news.
Why doesn't she answer her phone?
I'll text her instead.
Sweety...
Karan, are we doing the right thing?
Absolutely right.
This way we'll be happy,
and also our families.
My Charan looks so happy today.
Look at him. He is dance like Karan.
He is excited.
What happened, Karan?
Why the long face?
Smile. That's more like it.
Lord...you're the omniscient One.
The happiness of my family
lies at Your threshold.
Have mercy...
congratulations! Congratulations!
Congratulations!
- Congratulations!
Kartar. come here...
greet everyone.
This way, Kartar.
Aren't you going to greet charan?
come here...
- Just a minute.
Kartar.
Kartar...come here.
Greet Sandhu sir.
- Sandhu sir...
congratulations! Congratulations!
- Kartar...
Who's going to welcome Gill sir?
Gill sir...
Kartar...come here.
- Here.
come here first.
Sister... Brother,
let's not make a scene here.
I'll meet everyone once we're inside.
Don't waste time...
please, let's go inside.
Let's go inside, please.
- Yes...he's right.
Come on.
Come...
- come on.
Everyone's let's go inside.
Come...
Upstairs...
Sweety, what are you doing down here?
Papa, I can't go
ahead with this wedding.
What?
What did she say?
God answered my prayers.
Finally, it will all be over.
Does she know about
his drugs... - Be quiet.
Sweety, what are you doing?
- Be quiet, Charan.
Papa...I love Karan.
Sister-in-law.
- Oh, God! - Aunty...
And even he...
- Are you okay, Jeeto?
I think her blood
pressure's low again.
Someone get some
sugared water for her.
I'll get it. - Where are you going?
You're the groom.
But she's my mom.
I didn't know that,
that my son's wedding day...
...would be my last.
What are you saying?
- About this being her last day.
You fool, not me...I meant her.
What is she saying?
Do you want to marry her?
- No-no-no...
Why would I?
I don't want to marry her?
Son.
Just a minute...
Okay.
It will be 11 o'clock soon.
- Yes.
Is everything alright?
Does everything look okay to you?
Didn't I tell you before...
she has a loose character?
First, she wooed Charan...
...and now, she's eyeing my Karan.
Hello, mom...
- What?
Your Karan's been in a relationship
with me for two years now.
Aunty...
My boyfriend in the mall...
that's him.
Your son, Karan...
- Tell your mom.
Sweety, be quiet.
Quiet! Quiet! Quiet!
Why are you telling me?
Why don't you tell your father?
Uncle, your son Charan...
...wants to marry Binkle, and not me.
No papa.
She's wrong...no-no...
Oh, God. - Sandhu uncle,
you can ask Binkle yourself.
What is she saying, dear?
Is it true?
It's a lie...lie...lies...
I will only marry the girl
my mom and dad wants me to.
Yes... see?
Have you two lost your minds?
Kartar uncle, you know everything.
Why don't you say something?
What can I say, Sweety?
I've already told them everything,
but they don't believe me.
Sister...these two are lying.
Sweety isn't crazy
to refuse getting married...
...in front of the entire community.
And, can't you understand
Binkle's silence, Sandhu sir.
She loves Charan.
Kartar. Don't try to be a judge...
Stay if you like, or else...
Or else?
Or else what?
You'll break ties with me, won't you?
Of course, you can do that.
You two are an expert
in breaking relationships.
And these children
are not telling the truth...
...because they fear that you
might break ties with them too.
Kartar! Get lost from here...
get lost.
This is our family matter...
you don't have to interfere.
Our family matter?
Aren't they my children too?
Don't I have any right to them?
Forget it, uncle.
- Forget it, uncle.
Quiet!
Absolutely quiet.
Son...
It's close to 11 o'clock.
When will this end?
It's just getting started.
Have you lost your mind, brother?
Always yelling at me!
You did the right thing, sister...
...by severing all ties with him!
A brother who can humiliate
his sister, challenge her...
...a cheap man like that
isn't worthy... - Shut up!
Kartar...if you say another
word about Baldev... - Enough!
He can say anything...
you can do anything...
Do you have any idea...
how arrogant you are?
How stubborn are you?
And you've such a
small heart and thinking.
I wish God doesn't bless
anyone with a sister like you.
How dare you misbehave
with our sister...
...who raised us like her children.
See Sandhu sir...
Yell at the sister,
and the brother slaps you.
Yell at the brother,
and the sister hits back.
Why?
Because they are each other's life...
...but they are not
ready to accept it.
Because they have erected
a wall of ego between them.
We used to fight when we were kids.
For books, toys...
It was either for this or for that.
But we never went separated like this.
It's better to be a kid
for the rest of our lives...
...then growing up like this.
Brother, you revered sister like God.
But you turned your back
on your God over a trivial thing.
No...
And sister...
...you raised brother
Baldev like a mother.
So how can any mother
severe ties with her children?
Life is too short.
Too short.
And we develop such
big egos in this small life.
You can slap me 100 times more...
You're my elders, you can.
- No.
But forsake this stubbornness,
this ego...
End this war... or it will
be the end of your Kartar.
Forgive me, sister.
- Ballu...
No...
Forgive me.
You forgive me. You're my brother...
Come here, Kartar.
Forgive me...
Fantastic, uncle...
You're doing such a great time...
But your timing is so bad!
Sandhu sir...
Charan doesn't do drugs.
I made everyone believe he did drugs.
Daddy, he's right.
charan doesn't take drugs.
He's not like Happy.
Baldev...
I misbehaved due to
all this misconception.
Forgive me.
I called you a hawker.
Sandhu sir...I forgive you...
let's not get into details.
Everything's fine...
charan. Come stand next
to your Binkle. - come on.
Come, my boy.
Karan, Sweety's waiting. Come on.
Go on...
Now what's the problem?
It's almost 11 o' clock.
They have patched up.
How can we patch up?
How can Papa just patch up like this?
There's been no patch up.
You idiot,
they have patched up for good...
...and you're making a mess again.
There's been no patch up,
he called... my father a hawker.
Hey...don't keep repeating that.
Why are you going in flashback?
I want to marry Sweety, that's all.
What?
What do you say, Karan?
Karan?
Karan.
- Yeah...Karan...
I am Karan.
And I want to marry Binkle.
Why are you creating
a new problem now?
We've patched up now, so why...
- Son, please.
It's almost 11 o'clock.
Who's booking is it first?
These are the only two weddings today.
Then what's the hurry?
- I am free...
Just settle this quickly and be there.
Uncle...we need to talk to you.
- Then say it.
Alone.
- Alone?
What?
- I'll be right back. - Go...
Brother.
Come on...
Follow me...follow me.
Give way, give way, move-move-move.
Sister, what is it now?
Speak up, what's the problem?
Karan? You were dressed as charan.
What were you two going to do?
Such a big deceit.
Are you mad, Karan?
Uncle, aren't you tired yet?
You gave such a big speech out there.
And anyway...this isn't my idea...
...it was your beloved Charan's idea.
Take your clothes off.
Exchange your suits.
- Yes.
And don't ever tell
your wife's about this.
A wife...even doubts her own husband.
You fools...if you had
gone ahead with this lie...
Then for the rest of your lives...
...she will never
believe a word you say.
come on, change your dresses.
congratulations! Congratulations!
The children are ready to get married.
- Are they ready...Thank God.
Give way to my boy, move-move-move.
Is the wedding still on?
- Yes.
But who's marrying whom?
Karan's marrying Sweety, and
Charan's marrying Binkle. - I see...
You all asked Sandhu sir,
but no one asked me.
We will after the wedding.
Give me your card.
- Take it...
If the children are happy, I am happy.
crazy boy, couldn't you
tell us before that you like her?
Come on...
Time for the wedding.
Why did you say no?
- No, I didn't...
A guy who can sacrifice
his love for his family...
He must be really special.
Sweet...I love you...
I love you, I love you, I love you.
- Gill sir.
Let's get married first.
Start cameras.
Action.
Clap. It's clap.
- So much energy.
So much energy we'll collapse on sets.
Yes.
"It's Party night... cheers..."
"Drop the beat..."
Everybody is very happy
and work is doing great.
Sweety is like superb. Hot.
Take sir. Take sir.
No, no. He is a salesman.
"Let's go."
You love me so much, dude.
He knows everything.
" cheers...to this great evening..."
"cheers...for this joy."
"Cheers to my friends..."
"cheers... Cheers to them all..."
" cheers...to this great evening..."
"cheers...for this joy."
"Cheers to my friends..."
"cheers... Cheers to them all..."
He is not even told about Charan...
No, that's not right.
Nafisha. No.
We have to many charecters.
"We're going to celebrate tonight."
"We're not going to wait."
"We're going to dance
the old-fashioned way..."
"...and create a new step."
Stop asking.
"Come and dance with me..."
"come and ask...how I am..."
"Dance and sway with me..."
"...with my hands around your waist."
It's called 'Purani Haveli'.
Sorry. You have done good job.
"congratulations..."
"It's Party night... cheers..."
Recognise the man.
Do you know me?
"I don't know how to...
dance and sway."
"I don't touch alcohol either."
"But after two pegs down...
and no one can dance like me.
"I am Badshah...by my queen."
"Your attitude...is very mean, baby."
"Do you understand...what
I mean baby..."
"Let me make your night awesome."
"Increase the speed of your sway."
"Because the beat is fantastic."
"Watching me sway my hips..."
"...blows their minds away."
"Your gait's...enthralling."
"I'm getting some bad...intentions."
"I want to spend all night with you."
"Don't mind...sweetheart."
"congratulations..."
"It's Party night... Cheers..."
My dad...
"It's Party night..."
"Let's go."
"Whoever utters shall be happy,
shall be fulfilled,"
"Great Timeless Lord"
"congratulations..."