Extracted by NARACHI
Stop the game.
This is our pitch.
Hey!
Stop!
- Hello?
- Kabir?
Yes? My little boy
doesn't recognize my voice?
Uncle Hameed?
As-salaam-alaykum.
Wa-alaykum as-salam.
It's been ages since
I have heard you.
Son, I would like
you to come to Srinagar.
Is everything alright?
I've something important to discuss.
It would be nice if you
could come and meet me.
Of course.
Khuda hafiz.
What are you in search of, my friend?
You were meant to wander.
Continue with your journey.
Till you reach your destination.
Strive on ahead.
Everybody is with you.
You just need to see it.
Live life to the fullest.
I am as determined as the wind.
The birds have taught me how to fly
I travel through these unknown roads.
My journey continues... I am not lost.
In my journey.
I have learnt the truth.
About these questions.
What is the meaning of life?
Who am I? I know now.
I have found the answers.
Listen to the whispers of the wind.
Dust to dust.
Will return one day.
Enjoy your life in this world.
No one knows the future.
I am as determined as the wind.
The birds have taught me how to fly
I travel through these unknown roads.
My journey continues... I am not lost.
I am not lost.
Lost.
My journey continues... I am not lost.
- We want...
- Freedom!
- God grant us...
- Our beloved...
- Freedom!
- In the name of Shahdad...
- In the name of Farhaan...
- Freedom!
- We will get...
- From India, we'll get...
- Freedom!
Stop the game.
This is our pitch.
Now we'll play here!
Get out! Go away!
Do I need to repeat myself?
This is our pitch as well.
We are also playing here.
- What did you say?
- This pitch...
What are you looking at?
Will you hit me?
But I won't leave either!
Really?
Okay, then let's play.
Kabir!
Uncle Hameed.
My child...
how are you?
Good.
What were you looking at?
My childhood treasure.
Do you remember this?
Your father used to
be so upset with your marks.
This couldn't be the grades of
a teacher's son he was bound to be upset.
He'd be upset because
he knew you could do better.
Uncle Hameed,
what about father's school?
It has been taken
over by the government.
It's in a sorry state.
Why?
It's difficult to find teachers.
There was one lady teacher last year...
She has left as well.
If this continues,
the government might shut it down.
How can they shut it down?
What about the children then?
Exactly.
Pandit ji started this school because he believed
that if the children can't reach school...
The school should reach
out to the children.
If only someone like
you could teach there...
Is that why you called me here?
How can I teach?
Fine then... the poor children
will have to give up studies.
Uncle Hameed!
You were in the army?
Yes, sir.
Why did you leave?
And now you want to teach?
Yes.
Why Wular School?
I heard the school
doesn't have a teacher.
And I can teach the younger children.
Hmm...
Can you cook?
What?
Do you know how to mop?
Excuse me?
Can you swim?
Sir, isn't Firdaus teacher coming?
Who's Firdaus?
She's the one who taught last year.
Is it?
Yes.
Isn't there any network?
There is,
when good weather and peace prevails.
But good weather and peace is a rarity.
Open your notebooks
and write today's date.
Let me know when you're done talking.
What's so funny?
Do I look like a joker?
Forgot your book?
Do you forget to eat?
You know what,
we'll have a surprise test today.
You, stand up.
Kneel down. Catch your ears.
Hands straight up. Hey!
16th March, 2007.
When I was a little girl,
Dad often took me for
star gazing on the terrace.
The Pole Star was my favorite.
After I lost my parents,
I got the Stars tattooed on my hand.
These stars guided
me whenever I was lost.
But I had no clue that
it would bring me here.
Ms. Firdaus, we're teachers.
We need to set an
example for the children.
As a principal, aren't you
giving this too much importance, sir?
I'm sure there are other important
matters that need your attention.
Apart from how I dress, my tattoo...
You have to get the tattoo removed.
Sorry sir, I won't.
- Yes, you will.
- No, I won't.
Okay.
If you don't,
I'll be forced to transfer you to Wular.
Alright.
Can I get a couple
of days to pack my things?
On getting here I realised why
the principal threatened
to transfer teachers here.
There's no one for miles around.
It's like being exiled.
But there's always a
response to your hi-hello...
Hello...
In form of your echo.
Now try delivering a
Pizza here in 30 minutes!!!
This place is so far away...
that one can only
wait for Hope to reach.
Hello!
Remember Jaya Bachchan
in the film "Sholay"?
It feels the same.
Just that I don't have
"Jai" and "Veeru" for company.
All I have is...
"Gabbar".
It was my decision to come here.
Sometimes our decisions backfire...
and our hopes crumble.
I didn't know that there would
be no water, power or gas here.
I wish you were here with me, Junaid.
I miss you.
Brother! Brother!!
Hello..Brother!
Brother!
Hello! Brother... Hello...
As-salaamu-alaykum, I'm the new teacher.
I've been here for two days.
It's terrible.
There's no water,
power, gas or network here.
There's no one to talk to either.
I've hurt my hand.
Everything's a mess, I tell you.
I've come to teach but
none of the children have come.
It's been two days,
not even one child has showed up.
None of the children have come..
Do they even know there's
a new teacher here?
Two ones are two.
Two twos are four.
Your new teacher is here.
Show up at the door.
Why are you saying it like this?
Be it vegetables or a teacher,
this is how we need to sell...
Two ones are two.
Two twos are four.
Your new teacher is here.
Show up at the door.
I have fresh green vegetables...
and a school teacher too.
Madam, do you have children?
- Yes.
- Call them.
Son! Son!
Do you go to Wular School?
Yes.
Teacher... your school begins.
Good morning.
Good morning, teacher.
Do you know my name?
No, teacher.
I will act it out and you have to guess.
Okay, teacher.
Quickly!
Circle!
Again!
Round!
[HINDI FOR AGAIN]... Fir?
Fir-bus?
Fir-dus?
Firdaus.
Correct.
My name is Firdaus.
Unlike words, we don't forget actions.
I want you to act out your names.
Ready?
Who will go first?
What are you doing? This is how
we introduce ourselves in class.
Firdaus teacher taught us,
we don't forget actions.
Really?
Okay, tell me.
Jeep?
Car?
My name is... Wow! Car!
My name is Waqar and I study in Grade 2.
One finger?
Three fingers?
(HINDI FOR DATE)... Tariq.
Tariq.
I get it.
Grade 4.
One river?
My name is Iqrah. Grade 2.
I am Shama, this is Dingu.
We're in grade 3.
And you are?
(HINDI FOR PRAYER)... Dua!
I study in grade 1.
Are you all in different grades?
Sir, what's your name?
I am Kabir.
Let's start.
Sir, won't Firdaus teacher come?
No.
Dua, start with the alphabets.
A for apple, B for baby, C for cat...
Waqar, what is 27 plus 13?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7...
- Do you know your tables?
- Yes.
- Say them.
- Which one?
The two times table.
Two ones are two.
Two twos are four...
Iqrah...
Hello, Dolly?
Where are you?
You haven't paid my phone bill!
Right, Dolly...
Hello, I can't hear...
The network... Dolly?
Hello..I can't hear you Dolly..
Dolly this place has network issues
Dolly your voice is not clear.
Silence!
Sir, 40.
Shut up!
Stay here!
I'll make a call and be back.
Tariq, come.
Why is there no signal?
Sir, should we go back?
Wait a minute.
Sir, let's go.
Two minutes.
- What happened?
- Diesel.
Has it run out?
Not yet, but will soon.
Tariq, there's no one here.
Where are they?
Hey, what are you doing there?
Fishing, sir!
Come here, right now!
Waqar, Shama, Dua, Iqrah...
I'm also coming!
Quiet!
Just come here right now!
Why did you go in the
water without my permission?
I can't monitor you all the time.
We wanted to catch fish.
We're very hungry.
What if something had happened?
You could have drowned!
We know how to swim.
Okay, but what if something went wrong?
We've been swimming here forever,
nothing has happened.
What could've gone wrong?
Don't argue with me.
Come on, crouch like a chicken.
Chicken? We don't know how.
You don't how to crouch like a chicken?
What do you guys know then?
See, spread your legs,
crouch, bend your hands
like this and hold your ears.
Now, that's a good-looking chicken!
Does he doodle?
Let's eat him... I'm so hungry.
Hold out your hands!
I said, hold out your hands!
Can't you hear me?
Sir, why did you hit me? I was with you.
No, you're with them.
All of you are a team.
Firdaus teacher never hit us.
Enough about your Firdaus teacher.
Tell me if you don't want me here,
I'll leave.
Then leave.
Tomorrow being a weekend,
it's a holiday.
I hope he doesn't return on Monday.
Are you a lefty or a righty?
Lefty.
Start doing everything
with your right hand.
We'll have to amputate this hand.
What?
Just kidding.
Nurse?
Doctor, please take a look,
I hope it's nothing serious.
- I'm very concerned.
- Show me.
I had told her, if she went there...
Junaid, relax.
It's an allergic reaction
to something in the water.
I'll prescribe some
medicines and an ointment.
Apply that.
It'll fine soon.
Yes, it will be fine,
but then she will return to that school.
She can't even swim properly
but will still jump in the water
and get the rash back.
I'll send the medicines.
Come on Firdaus,
despite me not approving of it,
why do you have to
return to that school?
What if I want to meet you?
We can only meet on weekends.
That too, after traveling for 6 hours.
Tell me... God forbid...
what if something happens to you?
What'll we do, wait for the weekend?
Junaid what do you want?
I want you to take a transfer back.
You know that's not possible.
Why not?
Oh, because of this tattoo?
I'd not approved this too.
But you never listen to me.
You just want to prove
that principal wrong.
Why are you doing this?
For those 4-5 children You've left everything
and gone to that godforsaken place.
What will you gain from all this?
What will I gain?
There are seven children there, Junaid.
And stop telling me,
that you don't approve.
I'm tired of hearing that.
So am I.
I can't do this anymore.
Then let's break up.
Break up?
It's very simple for you, right?
How do you manage to
find excuses to break up?
I've a feeling, you took this
transfer just to get away from me.
Really?
Is that how you feel?
Then I think you should leave.
I probably should.
Stop right here.
Okay.
- How much?
- Rs. 35.
Here.
Don't you have change?
Please hurry up.
I am doing it bro..
Your girl?
Please hurry.
Fine, 4, 5...
Here.
Should I follow them?
Love is delusion, don't fall for it...
A delusion.
It happened to me as well.
All girls are the same.
A delusion.
Since the time I have seen you, my love.
Something that shouldn't
happen is happening, my love.
A delusion.
Since the time I have seen you, my love.
Something that shouldn't
happen is happening, my love
Mark my words - he'll go
to her room through the window.
A delusion.
And then... lights out!
Love is delusion, don't fall for it...
Do you have a light?
There's one in the bike's toolbox.
How did you know?
Because it's my matchbox, my bike...
And my girlfriend.
Thank you, my friend.
Okay.
He's right here.
I'll call you back.
Are you a kid?
Why don't you grow up?
Show some maturity.
Now you'll ask me,
'how long has this been going on?'
'I had just left.'
It's not about that.
The word is 'security'
Have you ever thought about our future?
You had a good job in the army,
but you left it.
And now you're teaching
in some godforsaken school.
What if you don't have a job next year?
One of us has to be mature.
My bike...
What?
How could you give my bike to him?
Bike?
You're about to lose your girl
and you're worried about the bike?
Since childhood Junaid
loved flying kites.
And I always held the reel for him.
He'd be very happy
when the kite soared high.
Though I felt that the
kite wanted to soar higher.
But Junaid was holding it back.
The time kite thread
broke it made me very happy.
I felt... though it was short lived
it was the kite's flight of freedom.
How strange-A childhood
friendship ends in a matter of days!
Why are relationships so fragile?
Why do we need a relationship
to feel complete?
I've been a daughter to my father, a girlfriend
to my boyfriend, a friend to a friend...
But, what am I to myself?
For myself.
I'm whole by myself.
I am enough.
And I want to thank the
universe for making me enough.
STATUTORY WARNING:
You must try this,
at least once in your life.
Thank you!
Thank you.
Time and apologies are free...
Give them when they are due.
Please pick me up at 4 o'clock.
Firdaus, I'm sorry for that day.
It's okay.
You know that I worry about you.
I tend to say things that
I don't mean when I'm angry.
It's because of my love for you.
I know, Junaid.
I am fine here.
In fact, I like it here.
But I don't...
like to see you here, all alone.
I'm not alone,
the children are here with me.
What's wrong?
Go.
You too?
These children will never let you leave.
So you stay here on weekdays,
with the children.
And spend the weekends with me.
And I mean, only with me.
Why're you being so sweet?
Because you may break
up with me again...
Firdaus teacher!
What happened, Tariq!
What's wrong? Why'd you shout?
Tell me. Tell me, what happened.
Over there.
Thank you for informing us.
There was firing in the mountains,
a few days ago.
The body must have floated here.
Everything is under control now.
There's nothing to worry about.
Let us know if you need anything.
Definitely, officer.
Thank you very much.
Goodbye.
Boys, is lunch ready?
We're very hungry, isn't it?
Imran, be careful.
Tariq is the masala ready?
Tariq...
Nothing will happen.
Firdaus, I've packed your bag, let's go.
Where?
Back home.
Come on, hurry up.
Junaid, I understand your concern.
Good, then let's go.
Please listen.
There's nothing more to discuss.
Junaid, if I leave,
the principal will shut the school.
Be it...
Junaid, I can't leave the school.
School?
You call this a school, Firdaus?
There's no water, power or network here.
And now the dead body!
I can't leave you alone.
It's not safe here.
- But it's not that I...
- Please, Firdaus.
Give me one reason to stay.
Not one... I have seven reasons.
Maybe, I came here because
I wanted to prove myself right.
But now these children need me.
I will not leave them alone.
I don't believe that
I chose to stay back.
Today I understand, during difficult times,
where my parents got their strength from.
Because they knew I was watching them.
The way these children
are watching me today.
I could have not set an
example of not facing the problem.
By quitting.
Now I know why parents
are called the first teachers.
And that's why a teacher
needs to become a parent.
Tomorrow will be a new day,
a new chapter
with a stronger me and a better me.
Good morning!
That teacher hit him, very hard... my little
fish is not feeling well... has headache...
Good morning, Waqar!
Good morning.
Loser!
You know what, we don't need this.
No cane, no pain.
We will solve a new problem today.
Whoever solves these
first will get a star.
Wait...
Ready?
1, 2, 3, go!
Come on.
Dua, let's read the alphabets.
Teacher, I'm done.
Very good, Imran.
Give me your hand.
Well done.
Tell me, A for?
Apple.
B for?
Ball.
C for?
Snake.
No my child, it's C for cat.
Snake!
Cat!
I won't spare it...
Tariq don't.. What are you doing? Stop!
All snakes don't bite.
Even if it does,
all snakes are not poisonous.
Sir, the snake?
Wait, I'll do something.
Sir... careful, it may bite.
Okay.
See, no damage done!
I told you, all snakes don't bite.
It bit me!
The snake bit me!
Sir got bitten by a snake!
I got bitten.
Quickly tie the hand.
Not yours,
tie my hand with a piece of cloth.
Don't worry sir, I'm here.
Hurry up, I'm blacking out.
You will be fine, sir.
Don't let me sleep.
Slap me!
I'm dying! I'm dying!
Take me to the hospital...
take me to the hospital.
Let's go, hurry up.
I'm turning blue.
It's not a snake bite... it's a
nail bite... These nails have hurt you.
'I told you, all snakes don't bite.'
I'm going to die.
'Take me to the hospital!'
'I'm blacking out.'
'I'm turning blue.'
It's not snake bite... it's a
nail bite.."These nails have hurt you.'
What happened?
I don't have time for all this!
But, I have all the time
in the world for you guys.
You speak Kashmiri?
Bye, Kabir sir!
Bye, khuda hafiz!
Bye!
'I got bitten by a snake!'
Hey!
Sir... what's up?
Nothing.
Coochie coo, coochie coo!
Hey!
I can't get the stars for you.
They're out of my reach.
I'm just another guy.
There's nothing special about me.
Nevertheless, my heart.
Asks you...
Will you fall in love with me?
Nevertheless, my heart.
Asks you...
Will you fall in love with me?
Children,
we'll have a memory test today.
I want you to draw somebody's
picture from memory.
Okay?
Whose picture do we draw?
Firdaus teacher, who else?
Why don't you visit me.
In my dreams...
Your story is known far and wide.
The trees...
And the mountains.
Echo your name.
To make this dream come true.
I will not be able.
I'm just another guy.
There's nothing special about me.
Nevertheless, my heart.
Asks you...
Will you fall in love with me?
I've found a photograph
of Firdaus teacher!
Asks you...
Will you fall in love with me?
Nevertheless, my heart.
Asks you...
Will you fall in love with me?
Tariq, shut the windows.
My Dingu...
Kabir sir.. Shama...
My Dingu!
Shama!
Kabir sir, my Dingu!
Kabir sir!
I can't take this off.
Dingu!
Why're you so sad?
Our school is destroyed.
What'll we do now?
We'll build it again.
Friends, come down.
We will go to see Dal.
Friends, come down...
We will sing songs of fun.
And be happy.
And create a melody.
Shaped with our broken dreams.
Come... let us dance.
Bumbro(BUMBLEBEE)...Bumbro.
O dark-hued Bumbro.
Why are you making such a din?
Spread colour everywhere...
Like the butterflies do.
Spread the fragrance of flowers.
Far and wide.
Spread colour everywhere...
Like the butterflies do.
Spread the fragrance of flowers.
Far and wide.
You dance and spread
happiness everywhere.
You can change the world.
Let the sparkle in your eyes.
Light up the world.
Come on... let us dance.
Bumbro... Bumbro.
O dark-hued Bumbro.
Why are you making such a din?
Friends, come down.
We will go to see Dal.
Bumbro... Bumbro...
Friends, come down.
We will go to see Dal.
Bumbro... Bumbro...
O dark-hued Bumbro.
Bumbro.
Bye!
Khuda hafiz, Kabir sir!
Bye, Dua!
- Bye...
- Khuda hafiz!
Khuda hafiz!
Bye, bye.
Shama, why don't you
stay back with me today?
I can't, my mother's waiting for me.
Dingu's mother must
be waiting for him too.
The father is 20 years
older than his son.
And the father's age
is 3 times the age of the son.
So, how old is the father?
Imran?
Teacher, the father's age is 30.
Very good, Imran.
Well done, Imran.
Imran, you're a good student.
If you continue like this, you'll
do very well in your semester exams.
Only if father allows
me to appear for the exams.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
Imran, why didn't
you come to school today?
You knew there'd be an exam today.
Don't you know how
important these exams are?
You think these exams
won't make a difference?
You'll fail, Imran.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Why didn't you come to school?
I told him not to.
As-salaam-alaykum.
Wa-alaykum as-salam.
Imran had his first exam today.
If he misses these exams,
he'll lose a year.
He has a very promising future.
He's capable of topping
these exams in the state.
The lives of Kashmiri
children are bound by...
their debt and their duty.
He will fulfill his duties...
he doesn't need your school.
We have our ways of teaching him.
How can we decide his fate?
He'll decide for himself.
Imran, do you want to go to school?
Do you want to go to school?
No.
I've seen many boys like
Imran walk down the wrong path...
never to return.
Darkness can't be driven by darkness
It can only be conquered by light.
I'm familiar with the
darkness that surrounds Imran.
Education was the light
that helped me conquer darkness.
I hope the light that I was unable to provide
to Imran finds a way to reach him...
Excuse me?
As-salaam-alaykum.
Wa-alaykum as-salam.
I am Kabir,
I'm the new teacher at Wular School.
I wanted to talk to you.
Yes?
I wanted Imran to rejoin the school.
Oh...
His father won't agree to it.
Please call him, I'll talk to him.
He's not at home.
No problem, I'll wait here.
No, what I mean to say is he'll
be back only after a few months.
Why don't you send
Imran to school till then?
I'll speak to his father when he returns.
I know he won't agree.
You don't understand...
No, you don't understand,
I can't go against my husband.
Look, I...
He's the new school teacher.
As-salaam-alaykum.
Wa-alaykum as-salam.
Children wait to be
rewarded with this star.
Ever since you've left,
this star has been lonely.
I've heard, darkness can't be driven by
darkness It can only be conquered by light.
Please reconsider.
I'll leave now.
Khuda hafiz.
So, the father's age
is 3 times the age of the son.
Son's age is equal to X.
Father's age is equal to 3X.
So, 3X=20+X.
Make this a fraction.
Switch the variables.
3=20+X upon X.
Cancel the two Xs.
So, 3 = 20.
Simple.
- Understand?
- Sir,
X = 10 and 3X = 30.
So, father's age is 30.
Sir, can she get admission too?
What is this, Kabir?
I'm trying my best, sir.
If the marks don't improve
in the second semester,
then I'm sorry,
we can't continue with you.
Sir?
The teacher who taught last year...
Do you know where she is?
Why?
I wanted to discuss few
issues about the children.
She's been around teaching
at DPS along with her fianc.
She's getting married,
that's why you were hired.
Rohan!
Deepak!
Raahil, you have to
lift your friend Sameer.
What did you see?
Raahil could not lift Sameer.
Because Sameer is heavier than Raahil.
Okay.
Raahil and Sameer, get into the water.
Come on, hurry up.
Try and lift him now.
Did you see that?
When we put something in water,
the force of the water pushes it up.
This is known as buoyancy, okay?
Ms. Firdaus?
We need to talk.
Yes, sir?
Why do children need to come
to the pool for a science class?
Who will be responsible
if someone drowns?
Junaid, this is not the first time!
I've repeatedly told her,
but she refuses to listen.
Sir, the students need
practical experience too.
I've also taught science,
that too inside a classroom.
And the children still understand.
Sir, mugging up is not
the same as understanding.
Ms. Firdaus, every teacher
has their own way to teach.
Exactly, and this is my way.
And if the children can understand..
Where's the problem?
Junaid, please explain to her.
What's there to explain? Enough.
But Junaid, if I...
I said enough, Ms. Firdaus.
You will not get the
children to the pool again.
Stop Firdaus.
Firdaus, listen to me.
Firdaus, work is work,
don't mix it with personal matters.
I'm not mixing anything Junaid.
You got promoted at the right time.
You know exactly how
much the principal likes me!
Firdaus, you need to learn to adjust.
Don't you think I'm trying?
I even got rid of my
tattoo because you insisted.
How much more should I change?
It's not about changing!
This isn't like your remote
school with 4-5 children.
This school follows strict
rules and regulations.
Junaid, I know how difficult
it was for you to get me a job here.
Honestly, I was happier in
that school with 4-5 children...
I wish I could go back there.
Well then,
you should do what you feel is right.
Just remember,
we're getting married in 3 months.
Your name glistens like a dewdrop.
You are what I dream of.
I see you everywhere.
My restless heart says.
Without you...
Without you, I am lost.
My heart is adrift
I'm lost without you, my love.
Without you, I am lost.
My heart is adrift
I'm lost without you, my love.
I call out to you.
In vain.
You're all that I want.
My heart can't be swayed.
Come, be a part of my world.
And fulfill all my desires.
Without you...
Without you, I am lost.
My heart is adrift
I'm lost without you, my love.
Without you, I am lost.
My heart is adrift
I'm lost without you, my love.
What are you doing here?
Junaid, do you think this is joke?
You can't get married.
Somebody might see us, please leave.
Leave from here?
But I'm carrying your baby...
Where should I go?
We will discuss about this later.
Please leave for now.
I'm not going anywhere...
And when will we talk?
You are getting married TODAY!
That's why I want you to leave,
before someone...
I am shattered and broken.
What is this bond we share?
I remain entangled in desire.
I don't know why.
Be my shade in the scorching sun.
Wipe my tears and bring me solace.
Come to me, my darling.
Firdaus, please listen to me.
It was a mistake.
You're the one I love.
If she had not come here today,
would you have ever cared to tell me?
Without you, I am lost.
My heart is adrift
I'm lost without you, my love.
Without you, I am lost.
My heart is adrift
I'm lost without you, my love.
You ignored me all the while but finally
removed the tattoo for the wedding!
Sir?
Congratulations!
The wedding was called off.
Have some tea.
Thank you.
Sir, I'm sorry for that day.
Why?
Rather I'm happy that
you went to Wular School.
The children got an opportunity
to learn from a good teacher like you.
Actually, I learnt a lot from them.
I really miss them.
Why don't you start teaching them again?
Don't they have a teacher?
They do. But he's not good.
Anyway, they'll need a
new teacher for the next term.
Would you like to go back?
You can even get your tattoo redone.
Let's teach Kabir sir that song today.
Yes.
Firdaus teacher! Yay!
I missed you so much!
Me too.
So did I.
How are you all?
You've grown so much in one year.
Kabir sir won't be coming?
Who is Kabir sir?
He was our teacher last year.
Have I grown taller?
Yes, quite a bit.
Go.
Come.
My superhero.
Soon you'll be as tall as me.
I want to be taller than you.
Okay!
I'm so happy to see
you back in school, Imran.
But, how did this happen?
Darkness cannot be conquered with light,
you need...
You mean darkness can't be driven by darkness
it can only be conquered with light.
How do you know this?
Kabir sir often mentioned.
Firdaus teacher, do you look like this?
Or may be like this?
Or this?
However you may look,
I love you, Firdaus.
People believe in love at first sight.
But I fell in love with
a girl I've never seen.
I've found a friend
in you that I have never had.
Firdaus, it's just not you.
I'm in love with your pole star,
your childhood,
your stubbornness, your anger,
Your a square plus b square In fact,
I love Junaid too.
By the way,
I've tried your statutory warning.
Thank you!
Though it was a lot of fun,
but the water was too cold!
You said thank the universe...
Well then, thank you Firdaus.
Because 'You' are my universe.
Firdaus, just like you, I too want to
pen down all my feelings in this notebook.
We may never meet,
but we will always be
together in this notebook.
I've loved chinar trees since childhood.
I had carried a leaf with
me when I had to leave Kashmir,
but I couldn't get
the leaf to grow in Jammu.
Sorry but I was too young to
know that leaves don't grow into trees.
"Where have these bloody.
"Kashmiris come from?" (TEASE)
"Where have these bloody"
I was teased so much at school
that I became the 'angry young man'.
I was filled with angry
for being thrown out of my home,
and hence I joined the
army to let out my anger.
But I was a misfit there as well.
Gunnu!
Hey Gunnu!!
One day a boy, running after his sheep,
crossed the border.
That day, my life changed!
Kabir sir, look, see what I found!
I've found a ball, made of metal.
Hey, what're you doing there?
Where have you come from?
Reply!!
Waqar! Throw it to me!
Towards me!
I won't give this to anyone!
Waqar!!!
Don't go!
Don't go there!!!
There are landmines.
Stop!
Waqar!
Don't go there!
There are landmines.
I won't give this to anyone!
What's wrong, Kabir sir?
Kabir sir?
Thankfully nothing happened that day.
It was a diffused grenade.
I don't know what made me jump on it.
Maybe I wanted to overcome my guilt.
That boy ran not fearing
me but fearing my gun.
That day I put down
my gun and left the army.
What's up, Firdaus teacher?
Nothing.
Coochie coo, coochie coo...
Tariq!
Why haven't you solved these?
I have a stomach ache.
Me too.
Same here.
As the exams got closer,
it wasn't just the children...
The math problems
made me nervous as well.
I had grown up watching
Mahesh Bhatt films,
far away from the world of Aryabhatta.
When the children were writing their final
exam I felt it was my examination as well.
The day the results were declared...
I have passed the examination!
Imran...
What are you doing?
Listen to me.
Imran...
What are doing?
Imran.
Stop, Imran!
Isn't this what you had taught?
Sir, How did I fail then?
How did I fail?
I can't fail, sir.
I can't fail..
If I fail, my father will send me away.
I don't want to go, sir.
I don't want to go..
You don't have to go anywhere.
I promise!
We can't continue like this.
Imran is so intelligent;
How could he fail?
I'm responsible for Imran's failure.
I taught him the wrong thing.
Good that you realise that.
I believe,
you need to learn before you teach.
Anyway, Firdaus teacher
will be back next term.
So, I think you should take a break.
What?
Sorry, I think you should take a break.
No sir, What did you say before that?
Before what?
Is Firdaus teacher coming back?
Yes.
Why are you smiling?
Nothing.
I can't believe that you'll be back.
The children will be very happy.
Though they even accepted
a bad teacher like me,
It's someone like you that they need.
I'm keeping your notebook...
I mean, our notebook, right here.
Welcome back, Firdaus.
Kabir.
If you want to know more about me,
you can ask the school bell.
Every time I missed you.
I would hold the rope of the bell.
It made me feel as
if I was holding your hand.
Love makes you do crazy things.
Ms. Firdaus, there's been an
improvement in the children's marks.
Thank you.
No sir, thank you.
May I ask you something?
The teacher who taught last year,
Kabir sir...
Do you know where he is?
Why?
I need to discuss some issues
about the children with him.
Of course.
I don't know where he is now, but he
planned to enroll for a teaching course.
I have his application form here,
if you want to take a look.
Can I help you?
Does Kabir Kaul live here?
No.
It is his house,
but he doesn't live here anymore.
He has moved to Jammu.
He'd written this address
on the school's application form.
That's why I'm here.
And you are?
I am Firdaus.
I teach at Wular School.
So you are Firdaus!
Yes.
And you are?
Just like you're managing
Pandit ji's school,
I'm looking after his house.
Would you like some tea?
Thank you.
This house has its own story.
I've seen it being built and
fall into ruins with my own eyes.
Times were such that.
Pandit ji had to move
out with his family.
Strangely, this house
has been ravaged by locals...
And also been looked after by locals...
Especially Pandit ji's friend Mr.
Ahmed Qadri.
Open the gate!
Brother, open the gate.
This gate won't open.
What you're doing is wrong.
Support us in the name of God.
God supports my actions.
You worry about yourselves.
The Pandits have left.
But you... have to live here.
Decide if you want
to be our friend or...
Think what you will.
I won't let you enter Pandit
ji's house as long as I'm here.
Go from here.
Ahmed, open the gate!
Mr. Qadri was one of a kind.
God doesn't make men like him anymore.
Did you know him?
He is my father.
Firdaus teacher?
Hi.
May I come in?
Huh! Yes..
Uncle Hameed said that
you were looking for me.
That's why I've come.
I can't believe you're here.
Me neither.
I've been waiting
for so long to meet you.
But, we've already met.
When?
Look...
6 in the head, 7, 8, 9...
Don't you know it? It's 11, stupid.
I'm weak in math.
But, how do you calculate so fast?
Pandit ji taught me to.
You'll be on my mind.
Like I will be on yours.
You will be as proud of me.
As I am of you.
We will be known as Romeo and Juliet.
There will one such day.
- Brother...
- Yes?
The battery has run out in the school.
Can you send another one, please?
I'm facing a lot of problems.
Sure. It'll be done today.
Thank you.
There's a letter for you.
I've given it to Waqar.
Who is it from?
Kabir sir.
To Firdaus teacher...
Waqar, there's no water inside.
Now what will you do without water?
Waqar!
Were you given a letter?
Where is it?
I dropped it.
In the toilet?
But, I have read it.
What did it say?
I am coming...
Is Kabir sir coming?
When?
I dropped it before...
Night will turn to day.
When we'll get together.
Heaven and earth will come alive.
This yearning for each other,
This longing...
Will be all around,
You'll see.
You will make some mistakes.
And so will I.
You will be as proud of me.
As I am of you.
We will be known as Romeo and Juliet.
Go.
Imran, turn right.
Keep going straight.
Firdaus teacher, which way now?
Let's go, Imran.
Brother, please...
I've already told you
not to give them false hope.
Stay away from them.
This is your last warning.
Let's go, Imran.
I don't want to go.
Sir, you'd said that you
wouldn't let me go anywhere.
Father has come to take me away.
Let's go, Imran.
As-salaam-alaykum,
I'm Imran's teacher, Kabir.
Sir, please let him study.
Let go of my hand.
It's important for him to study.
If he doesn't study...
Let go of my hand.
Sir...
Please don't hit him.
- Father, please.
- Let go of my hand teacher!
Sir, I...
- Father, don't...
- Let go of my hand.
Don't hit him.
Sir, please let Imran stay.
- Don't hit him.
- Leave my hand.
Father... No.
I've promised Imran...
Leave my hand.
Don't, father...
- Please...
- Stay away!
Please don't hit him.
Sir,
I won't let you take him away.
No father...
Will you stop me? You?
Father, don't...
Please don't hit him.
I said leave my hand.
Don't hit him, father.
- Give me the gun.
- No.
Give me the gun, Imran!
Give me the gun...
What's this?
What're you doing, Imran?
Put the gun down.
If I put it down, he will kill you.
Let him!
But you will not shoot.
Imran...
If there's anything
that you've learnt from me,
if you think I'm your teacher,
put the gun down.
Don't make the same mistake
your father had made.
If you don't put the gun down,
then I will fail.
Firdaus teacher will fail.
Our teaching will fail.
Please put the gun down.
For us.
Hi.
Kabir sir.
Firdaus teacher.
Nice to finally meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Why did you read my personal notebook?
It's only after reading it
that I realised, it was personal.
Where are the children?
I've sent them home.
No... because they had a lot of homework...
Math, science...
Really, they did!
Okay.
What's so funny?
Nothing.
Extracted by NARACHI